They're outside.
Alert. Condition: Red.
We're losing power
in the containment chamber.
You hear that?
Something's close.
See? This is what I'm talking about.
My heart is pounding.
Get down, get down.
Cubone.
A Cubone?
We're not catching you a Pokemon, are we?
What?
Tell me you didn't plan this, Jack.
Jack, tell me
- you didn't plan this.    - Are you serious?
How dare you. Okay? Of course not. Come on.
Okay, maybe.
There was a full moon last night
and my mom heard it crying its eyes out.
She thought I was having a nightmare,
so she brought me a glass of warm milk.
Dude, I thought you wanted to, you know, hang out
and relive the good old days.
Like when we were kids.
I do. But just look at it.
That is the perfect Pokemon for you.
Jack, I'm not looking for a Pokemon. I've told you this.
I've thought long and hard about this, okay?
Water-type is not right for you.
Neither is Fire-type. But Cubone is--
Lonely.
Exactly.
Okay, thank you, Jack. Thank you for that.
Are there any other emotional truth-bombs
you wanna drop on me?
Maybe later. But right now the truth is in my hands.
- Just give me the Ball.    - Yes. Yes!
Okay, remember, catching a Pokemon is not about skill.
So you can do this.
Good pep talk.
Okay. It has to choose you, too.
So make it wanna be your partner.
Hey, Cubone. What's up, buddy?
You know,
not everyone can pull off
wearing the skull of their dead relative,
but, you know, you sure can.
Okay, he didn't like that.
He did not like that.
Jack.
Throw it!
Throw the Ball.
Like a man.
Uh-oh. Cubone.
Cubone!
I did it!
Still got it.
The light's not green.
It still hasn't turned green yet, Jack.
That's bad, right?
Run!
- It didn't choose me!    - Run!
- It didn't choose me, Jack!    - I can see that!
I'm not its choice!
Cubone!
That was one angry Cubone.
He reminded me a lot of my mom.
So, um, I don't know if this is gonna sound
corny or whatever--
Just say it, Jack. I'm too tired to be angry.
I'm worried about you.
This again?
Hey, listen, everyone we know has left town
and now I'm leaving, too.
Yeah, but that's okay.
You gotta do what's best for you
with the time that you got.
That's what I'm doing.
You know, I'm crushing it at work.
I'm gonna get a promotion real soon.
What's the promotion for an insurance appraiser?
"Senior insurance appraiser"?
No, actually, that's two steps up
above where I'm at right now.
You're gonna make me throw up.
That's not a real thing.
Oh, I finally have service.
Wait, five voicemails?
Why would I have five voicemails?
Maybe it's an insurance emergency.
Who is it?
Um, it's the Ryme City Police Department.
There was an accident.
Please don't.
Mmm.
I actually meant, "Please do". Thank you.
Thank you. You have a very generous tongue.
Does this Lickitung belong to anyone?
Anybody? No?
Thank you for travelling with us.
Please sit back and watch this short informational video
welcoming you to Ryme City.
Throughout history,
Pokemon have been part of our world.
Squirtle.
Early humans used to catch them
and train them to use their unique powers
for the common good.
This relationship evolved
into what we now refer to as Pokemon battles.
One man changed all of this.
Howard Clifford,
founder and chairman of Clifford Industries.
Diagnosed with a rare degenerative disease,
he resigned from his corporation
and searched the world for a cure.
And it turned out that the cure I was looking for
was for me to evolve into a better version of myself.
And I discovered how to do that
through a partnership with Pokemon.
And he wanted to share that discovery with the world.
This is what inspired
Howard Clifford to build Ryme City,
a place where humans and Pokemon can live side by side.
Unlike other regions, where Pokemon live in the wild,
here, we live and work together.
No battles. No Trainers. No Poke Balls.
A stronger, more harmonious world.
From all our citizens: Welcome to Ryme City.
Char! Charmander!
Fighting fires wouldn't be the same
without their Squirtle partners.
Squirtle, Squirtle. Squirtle, Squirtle.
Snubbull.
Hi, Tim.
Lieutenant Yoshida.
Your dad was the best of the best.
He was a legend in this precinct.
Thank you. Thank you for saying that.
It was a terrible tragedy, losing him and his partner.
His partner?
His Pokemon.
Oh, I didn't…
Snubbull.
I'm sorry, is yours mad at me?
- Snubbull?    - Yeah.
He may look grumpy on the outside,
but I assure you, he is adorable on the inside.
If you don't mind me asking,
how come you don't have a Pokemon?
I thought I remember Harry saying
you wanted to be a Pokemon Trainer when you were young.
Yeah, that didn't really work out.
Uh, I work in insurance now, so…
I understand.
But, Tim,
please don't put this all on yourself.
No one should go through this type of thing alone.
If you are anything like your dad--
I'm not.
I was just really raised by my grandmother.
Do you have the spare keys for his apartment?
I should go wrap things up there.
Of course.
- Here's his address.    - Awesome.
I can take you over if you want.
No. Nope. I'm all good. Thank you so much.
Tim.
This job,
it demands a lot.
But you were on his mind every day.
He loved you more than anything else in the world.
Uh, it was nice to meet you, Lieutenant.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Psyduck!
Psyduck.
Are you trying to rob me, or just annoy me?
- Psyduck.    - He's with me.
- We need to talk.    - We do?
I've been waiting to see
who would open up that mailbox.
You just walked into quite a story.
Stories like this spread fear. And they're afraid of fear.
But I don't fear fear.
I walk the walk and I talk the talk.
And I'm willing to do whatever it takes
to get the honest scoop, and that's the hard truth.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Lucy Stevens. Reporter for CNM.
Oh. You seem kinda young for that.
I work for the CNM blog,
making Pokemon listicles all day, okay?
- Top 10 Cutest Pokemon.    - Yeah, my grandma loves those.
Yeah, news flash: they're all cute.
Such a waste of time
for someone with my nose for a story.
Oh, no, no, not now, Psyduck.
I'm working a source. Just one more minute.
Okay, I'm gonna…
I'm gonna need you to go on record and tell me
everything you know about Harry Goodman.
Wait, what?
Harry was onto something big. Real big.
And then all of a sudden,
his car crashes over a bridge. I think not.
Something's rotten, and I'm gonna get to the bottom of it.
Hey, look, I barely know the guy.
- I haven't seen him in years.    - Where's your Pokemon partner?
I don't have one. Why does everyone keep asking me that?
Loner. Probably hiding something.
Okay. I'm gonna go.
Hey.
I may only be an unpaid intern,
but I can smell a story.
And I'm going to find it.
Okay. You do that.
Come on, Psyduck. Let's go.
Psyduck.
Who is it?
Hello?
It's me. Snakes. I got the stuff.
Leave it on the doorstep
and get the hell out of here.
All right, Johnny, but what about my money?
Still with the old detective movies.
What?
What? What is that stuff?
"Dear Tim. I could do better if you give me a chance.
I'll always have a place for you to stay."
The train on platform…
Your father will pick you up from the station.
I'm not going.
- What?    - I don't wanna go.
This is home. I wanna stay here with you, Grandma.
Oh, man.
This is the most important day of my life.
I know, Tim.
But your mother had to see the doctor. It couldn't wait.
Harry.
Someone there?
Hello?
Oh.
Ahh! That's a sprain.
Okay, okay, okay.
Whoever you are,
I know how to use this.
It's a Pikachu?
Aw, jeez.
Hey, little guy, how did you get in here?
I know you can't understand me,
but put down the stapler,
or I will electrocute you.
Did you just talk?
Whoa. Did you just understand me?
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That is heavy eye contact right there. You heard me.
- No, no, no.    - Yes, you did.
- Oh, my God. This is amazing!    - Stop!
- You can understand me.    - Stop talking. Stop!
I have been so lonely.
- I'm gonna throw up.    - No, kid. I need your help.
- I'm gonna throw up.    - I'm in serious trouble.
I need you to listen.
-No, no, no, no. Excuse me, Aipom,
we're having a private conversation here, please.
Stop talking.
- You're a hallucination!    - You're a hallucination!
And, you! Out! Shoo! Go!
I'd tread lightly there, chief.
That Aipom don't look right.
Ahh!
No! Hey! Hey!
Get off him, whack-job.
Get up, kid. He's coming back around.
Okay, here's what you wanna do.
Okay, you wanna bite him. You wanna scream.
We're playing charades. We're not playing charades.
- Okay, I'm gonna get a knife.    - Not the knife!
Okay, bad idea with the knife. I'll find something else.
Eat this!
You are so welcome. He was just a hungry little guy…
Oh, my God!
Come on, kid. Let's move.
To the roof!
Brilliant idea! You hold the door.
- I'll go get help.    - What?
Help! Help! Oh, my God! Help!
Oh, sh…
Help! Help! Oh, my God, help!
Oh, he's being eaten alive! He's being eaten alive!
A man is dying!
No one's coming. People are so insensitive.
Uh-oh. Put your pants back on
and run like the wind.
Blazing speed! Blazing speed!
No, they seem to be attracted to your increasing nudeness.
Okay.
All right, we're jumping down here.
No! No! I'm not going in the trash chute.
Good call. Let me know how it goes
with the super crazy Pokemon.
You died a hero.
Way to stick the landing, kid.
Leave me alone!
Oh. Looks like someone's back in a good mood.
Run! Rabid Aipom!
Look out! Run!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! They're… Go! They…
I think pants are gonna do you a lot of good right now.
Shoo! Go.
You know, I pictured you
as a bit of a briefs guy, but those are nice.
Me? I don't wear underwear, you know? I'm not modest.
Excuse me, excuse me, hi. Sorry.
Uh, you can hear him, right? You can hear him talking?
- Pika-Pika. Pika. Pikachu.    - Aw.
Yeah. Pika-Pika. Pika. He's adorable.
You're adorable. They can't understand me, kid.
It's me. It's that stuff that I put up my nose.
Not like that. No, it was a gas.
- I was breathing gas.    - Hey, hey, hey.
Accidentally. I was accidentally…
Ix-nay on the gas-ay.
Unless you want Johnny Law to give you
a one-way ticket to the hoosegow, let's move.
No one else can hear him?
This is a first for me, too, kid.
He's saying words.
Try to talk to people all the time.
All they hear is "Pika-Pika".
They pat me or kiss me,
stick a finger in me. It's really gross.
Can no one else hear him?
Can you hear him talking? Do you hear him saying words?
What are you not getting here, kid?
You're the only one who can hear me.
- It's like destiny.    - It's not destiny.
Then why were you in that apartment?
It's my father's place. That's why I was there.
- Why were you there?    - You're Harry's son?
How do you know his name?
You're Harry's Pokemon partner?
You want a coffee?
'Cause I could use a coffee. I mean…
Yeah. Let's get a coffee.
Yeah. Come on.
So there I was in the middle of nowhere
with a bad case of the forgetsies.
The only clue to my past is Harry's name
and address inside this hat.
So I made my way to the apartment
and that's when I found you.
♪Jigglypuff♪
I don't know. Maybe Harry got in too deep.
Deep in what?
You know, mixed up with the wrong crowd,
that kinda thing. Happens to the best of us.
The debts pile up. The walls close in.
Right becomes wrong. Wrong becomes wrong.
- Wait, who you calling?    - No one.
Yeah, that sounds great. This menu looks really nice.
Wait, I'm confused.
Are you hearing other voices besides mine?
All I wanna know is why I can understand you.
Ho! Can't help you there, kid.
Like I said, I have amnesia. Can't remember a darn thing.
Okay, so you're a talking Pikachu
with no memories, who's addicted to caffeine.
I could stop whenever I want. These are just choices.
Another round. Extra shot.
Black as night. Thank you, sweetie.
Ludicolo!
Look, I'm a great detective.
But I can't solve my own mystery if I have no memory.
Then how do you even know you're a detective?
Well, I can feel that in my jellies.
What is that? What is that?
It's the jellies. It's that thing, you know?
You feel it when you really believe in something
despite everyone telling you you're wrong.
Which is why I need to find Harry.
He's the key to my past.
- Ludicolo.    - Thanks, doll.
I got some bad news for you 'cause, uh, Harry's dead.
What? No. No, no, no. No, Harry ain't dead.
No, Harry is dead. You're wrong. I'm sorry.
I saw in the police report that he's dead.
Just 'cause the cops say he's dead--
It means that he's legally dead.
Really? Did they find a body?
Oh, I didn't think so.
And, by the way, did that report also say that I'm dead?
'Cause if I'm still alive and kicking,
that means Harry's out there, too.
Case closed.
But still open until I solve it.
Okay, I'll bite. Solve what?
Oh, I'm glad you're gonna bite.
All right. Here it is.
Harry faked his own death.
Or somebody else faked Harry's death.
Or Harry faked somebody else's death.
That last one doesn't work at all.
- No, it doesn't.    - The first two are contenders.
No, I'm gonna go. We're done here.
- No, we are not done here.    - This is…
Wait. Wait. Wait a minute. Where're you going?
Hold up a sec. We're gonna need each other.
No, we don't. I don't need a Pokemon. Period. Got it?
Then what about a world-class detective?
Because if you wanna find your pops, I'm your best bet.
I think a world-class detective
oughta have figured out by now
that I'm not here to find my father.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Hey, hey. There's no one to say goodbye to.
Look, you can talk to humans. I can talk to Pokemon.
We can talk to each other.
This doesn't happen, kid. It has to mean something.
There's magic that brought us together,
and that magic is called hope.
Hope that Harry is still alive.
Oh, you feel it. You feel it in your jellies, don't you?
There's nothing in my jellies.
We're gonna do this. You and me.
I can't belie…
I will meet you here tomorrow morning.
Great.
- Where're you going?    - To my apartment.
What do you mean, "Your apartment"?
What?
All right, you can sleep on the couch.
No, I'm not gonna sleep on the couch.
Well, then you can sleep on the stove.
Be a dear, would you, and get the door for me.
What am I doing?
I just invited
someone to my apartment.
I never do this. I'm not that kind of Pokemon.
Dust everywhere.
No fingerprints.
Ugh. Doesn't add up.
What is going on in here?
I'm searching the joint, looking for clues.
- Is this your room?    - No.
Does Harry have other children?
No.
He wanted me to live here when I was a kid,
so he made it look like my childhood room.
Should we talk about the fact
that your childhood bed is a Pikachu bed?
It's a coincidence.
I'm sorry. Can you speak up?
I can't hear you.
I've never been so flattered
and creeped out at the same time.
Are you gonna make me into a lampshade?
Oh, I might.
Hang on, hang on, hang on.
All these Pokemon cards and the battle posters…
There's a connection, isn't there?
- You love Pokemon.    - No.
Yeah. Yeah, you do.
That was a long time ago,
before my father moved to the city
and spent more time with Pokemon than his own son.
Mmm, yeah, blame it on your dad.
Okay, look, what about this?
There's pictures of her all over the apartment.
She's obviously connected to Harry.
She might know me.
She could be a lead.
No, she's not.
That's my mom.
She passed away when I was 11.
Oh. I'm sorry. I…
I didn't realize.
Tomorrow morning I'm gonna take you to Yoshida
so we can get some answers.
Ahh, my clues!
What is all this?
Hard work. That's what this is.
And, by the way, we can't go to the cops.
Not till we know who we can trust.
So put my clues back in order, would you?
These aren't clues. This is the work of a serial killer.
They're almost clues.
What does that even mean?
Trying to jog my memory, retrace my steps.
It helps me to see it all laid out.
That's how I found this.
This is what a Frenchman would callcaliente fiesta.
Not French.
Smell my finger.
I will never smell your finger.
Coward.
The point is, I smelled this R stuff
on those Aipom when they attacked us yesterday.
- R?    - Bingo!
La Cucaracha.
See, I'm thinking Harry
caught a break in the case,
forcing our shadowy kingpin
to send out hired goons to deliver the big hush-hush.
We need to retrace Harry's steps.
Either solve the case ourselves
or get far enough along that this
A-number-one bad guy has to reveal himself.
- Or herself!    - Can you stop doing that?
So, what is the way in, huh?
The answer is in this room.
This isn't a room. This is a fire hazard.
It's just junk and papers and…
Newspapers.
What you got, kid?
I literally just met someone.
She was a… She was a junior reporter at CNM.
She was doing a story on Harry.
I think she knows more than she let on.
The smart ones always do.
We gotta go down to her work and press her.
- Okay.    - That's a metaphor.
Yeah, I know what a metaphor is.
Uh, I was drinking that.
I was also drink… Just step anywhere.
It's only my life's work.
No. No, we're not doing that.
Fine, I'll walk.
I'm trying to get in 100,000 steps this hour.
Hello, I'm Roger Clifford, president of CNM
and chairman of Clifford Enterprises.
And I'm Howard Clifford,
the visionary icon behind Ryme City.
Together, in the spirit of harmony,
we're throwing the largest parade
that Ryme City has ever seen.
You won't wanna miss it.
So, at the weekend, we invite the people…
And the Pokemon to be there.
A celebration of the harmony
between humans and Pokemon.
And, cut!
Well, I think that went rather well.
Oh, shut up, Dad!
He seems nice.
Roger, please. This is supposed to be
our gift to the citizens.
"Visionary icon"? Really?
Was "savior of the world" taken?
It was your people who wrote the promo, son.
Oh, is there an unabridged version
where you cure cancer?
Oh, that's right, yeah.
Turn your back on me like you always did.
Ditto!
By the way, no one likes your Pokemon!
There she is.
I can see why you were so excited.
I was… Okay, I was not that excited.
Mr. Clifford! Mr. Clifford!
Mr. Clifford, I may have a story for you.
I've heard rumors of Pokemon attacking people.
But there's been no mainstream coverage.
I'm sorry, we're not a tabloid.
Which means that we don't report
on rumors, gossip or hearsay.
It's not news if it can't be verified.
You want a story, find a source.
Oh, and pro tip:
A reasonable sense of fashion.
Here she comes.
Here she comes. Try to look deep.
What are you doing here?
Hey, again. Uh…
Yeah, I know this seems weird
but I actually needed to ask you something.
Now's not really a good time.
Yeah, I saw that. I'm sorry.
Sorry. It's piping hot.
You found yourself a Pokemon partner.
- Not exactly, no.    - Aw.
He's cute.
She's trying to work me, kid. But, trust me, I can…
Oh, sweet Mother of Arceus, that feels so good.
- So, listen…    - Oh, my God.
What happened?
I found something in Harry's desk,
nearly choked me to death, and I was--
No, not here.
In my office.
In her office? We're going to her office?
This is great.
This isn't an office. It's a coffin with pencils.
Psyduck?
Yeah, that's right. I can talk to the kid,
he can talk to me. We're gifted.
You didn't tell me that she has a Psyduck.
These things explode when they're stressed.
Hey. Hey, keep calm, pal.
Serenity now. Serenity now.
- No.    - Okay.
Okay.
- You got it?    - Here it is.
Where did you find these?
Word on the street was that
Harry had an informant near the docks.
I went there to snoop around,
and that's where I found the vial.
But the docks can be dangerous.
It's not the sort of place
you want to visit alone at night.
I'm actually pretty good at being alone at night.
Nope, that did not land right at all.
That's not… That's not what I meant to say. Um…
- It's okay.    - I'm just gonna…
We should go.
- Yeah, we should go.    - I'm just gonna scoot by ya.
Good God, have you ever talked to a woman before?
- You've got some…    - Psyduck.
Yes, I've talked women before. No, I don't need your help.
Was it during the birth canal, or…
You know what you need?
A shoulder saddle. I bet someone makes one.
Okay. There are other ways for you to get around.
This is humiliating.
Every step for you is 1000 for me,
and my lungs are the size of grapes.
We need to get some ground rules
if this partnership's gonna work.
You're not my partner.
Mentor,sensei,master,
whatever you wanna call it.
Nope, none of those.
Hey, what if it wasn't the gas? What if it's hereditary?
What if Harry could understand your annoying voice, too?
You don't need to talk to us for us to understand.
We can feel what you're saying.
You have to be open to the experience. Try it sometime.
Yeah, I'd rather not.
I got my plate full talking to you.
What is that?
Silent but deadly.
Apologies, my tummy's bad from all the coffee.
No. Ew. Get off.
I meant that.
Oh. Ooh. Ugh.
That.
It's a Mr. Mime. They're the worst.
Silent but annoying.
Does he recognize you? I think he recognizes you.
Well, I was Harry's partner, so I would've been with him.
Harry's informant is a Pokemon!
Get him!
- He's barely moving.    - Don't tell him that.
Oh! He's on a bike.
Come on! He thinks he's getting away.
Look, quick! Get in front of him.
- Cut him off. You can make it.    - Stop.
Oh, no.
He's going down hard, Tim.
Should've worn a helmet.
I hope he makes it.
Come on. This is ridiculous.
I'm good cop, you're bad cop.
We're not cops.
Grow some berries.
You're bigger and tougher looking than I am.
Stand up straight!
Listen up.
We got ways to make you talk. Or mime.
Yeah.
So tell us what we wanna know.
Why was Harry Goodman here
and what did it have to do with the R?
Pipe. Yes, okay. A can!
Shoving. Pushing.
My problem is that I push people away
and then hate them for leaving.
- He's saying you can shove it.    - What? I can shove it?
Okay, that's it. We're switching roles.
I'm bad cop, you're good cop.
- No, no, no, we're not cops!    - Oh!
Oh, God, that's a very hard wall.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, Mr. Mime has the ability
to make invisible walls.
Uh, yes, I know. I happen to be a Pokemon, too, remember?
Look, Harry figured this guy out somehow.
I think the trick is getting inside his head.
I have an idea.
What are you doing?
Oh, what's this?
Oh, there's a door there. I didn't…
Probably because it's invisible.
Huh? Yeah! I'm in your space now, am I right?
You don't like this so much, do you?
What are you doing?
That's a jug. No, you're pouring.
No.
Salt. It's a salt shaker. You're cooking.
- No.    - Real cooking is about
following your heart, not a recipe!
What are you talking about?
Gas. You're pouring gasoline on…
- Mmm-hmm.    - Oh, that went dark fast.
I like this. I like this very much.
All right, all right.
Okay. You wanna play that game?
I can play that game.
You think that's funny?
You think that's funny, huh?
You're not gonna be laughing soon, huh?
Who's laughing now, huh?
Oh. Oh, I smell what you're stepping in.
That's right, Mr. Mime.
You're about to be Mr. Melt
unless you start talking.
Cards, cards. Playing cards. Poker.
No, I think he's talking about the R.
Someone was handing out R.
Use your body words. Where?
Circle house. Moon house. Moon. House.
Enough with the games. Say it.
Just say it!
Talk, you stupid mime!
Okay, just relax.
Uh, round.
Round house. Uh…
The source of the R came from the Roundhouse.
Yeah, nice work, kid. Maybe there's
a little detective in you after all.
Critical hit! Additional damage!
I didn't know they had Pokemon battles in Ryme City.
We're not supposed to.
Gengar uses Shadow Ball!
Come on. Let's take a look around.
Okay, kid. So here's what we know.
Harry traces the R to here.
Then frequents this joint because someone
here knows something about something.
We just need to find the someone and the something.
Hey, hey! Where's that Pikachu's partner? Don't go.
I think the "someone" just found us.
Wow. I'd like to see
this guy's Internet search history.
Who are you?
Let's see where this goes.
Tell him you're my new partner.
I'm his new partner.
Well, that Pikachu's Thunderbolt
almost wrecked my prize Charizard
- last time he was here.    - Oh.
Scar is still fresh.
All I hear are consonants, and all I see are nipples.
And you know what?
He ruined my coat, man. Look at this.
I'm so sorry.
Forget the coat. Where's his shirt?
This! This is my place!
And nobody comes into my place
and does that to my Pokemon.
What are you looking at?
Or to my coat.
Right, the coat. The coat.
What are you doing?
Classic staredown, kid. First one to blink loses.
Now stop distracting me.
Er, look, I just wanna know
why his old partner was here. That's all.
Gengar wins.
Ready for next battle.
And I want a rematch.
You give me my rematch…
I'll tell you everything you want to know. What I know.
- Er…    - Tell him he's on,amigo.
Okay.
A new battle's unfolding.
Pikachu versus Charizard.
Rematch!
Here. Hold my hat.
I'm about to rock this place.
- Okay.    - Charizard! Charizard!
Just doing some light stretching.
You never wanna go into these things tight.
You're gonna win this time, okay?
What are you doing? What is your plan of attack?
I don't operate according to plans, kid.
I deal with things in the moment.
Here. Here we go. Now you'll be ready.
Now, obviously, I've dealt with this putz before,
so I'll just do it again.
Give me my hat back!
That thing just chugged
a year's worth of that R stuff!
Hey, hey, hey. It's like you said, okay?
You did it before.
You just gotta use your powers.
You can use Quick Attack, Discharge, or Electro Ball,
but I think Volt Tackle
is your best move, so start with that.
First of all,
when did you learn how to be a Pokemon Trainer?
And secondly, get me the hell out of here!
Begin!
- Look out!    - Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I forgot everything you said!
I forget things, it's what I do! I have amnesia!
You need to go for a critical hit. Use Volt Tackle!
Volt Tackle will knock me out. I'm going for Thunderbolt.
Come on. You got it, you got it!
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey, bud! What are you doing?
I can't do it when people are watching.
Can everyone just look away, please?
It's not working.
I forgot how to use my powers.
But he didn't!
Pikachu, run!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Taken out with one hit!
Aw, Pikachu. Wanna cry?
You don't wanna do this! I'm adorable.
Pika-Pika?
Are you crazy? Get out of there!
I got it, kid!
What are you doing to my baby?
- Get out of the way!    - Uh-oh.
Uh-oh. That's not good.
Tell me what you know!
The guy you are looking for
wanted to know the source of R.
It comes from the doctor.
That's all I know.
Now let me go!
Nice catch, kid. Let's get out of here.
I got a plan.
What? That's not gonna work. Magikarp is the worst.
Magikarp can evolve into Gyarados.
All it needs is a little kick.
Water in the hole!
In my head, I saw that differently.
Er…
Hey, Tim? I don't float.
Ha! I told you Magikarp weren't useless.
You're under arrest.
I thought you couldn't wait to get home.
Yeah. Well, my plans changed because I found him.
I'm not following.
Harry's not dead. If his Pokemon partner
is still alive, that means he is, too.
That is not proof, son.
Tell him about the chemical R.
Give me a minute.
Harry's last case
had to do with those underground battles.
That's why I was there. There's a chemical.
We ran an investigation.
Harry figured it out and he's in trouble.
That case is closed. Over!
You gotta reopen the investigation!
He's out there, I can feel it.
In your jellies. Go ahead, say it.
I'm not gonna say that.
I can feel it, Lieutenant, in my bones.
- Not as good.    - Stop!
Oh, yeah, and I can understand Pikachu,
like, word perfect, so…
Tim.
It's very difficult coping with loss.
Denial can be a powerful thing.
No, I'm not in denial! I'm right, I know it!
He's… He's out there.
I never wanted to show you this,
but I think it's important you see it.
No one could survive a crash like that.
Not even your dad.
He's gone, Tim.
I should've gotten on that train.
What's that, kid?
After my mom died,
my dad and I drifted apart.
Er…
He moved here and poured himself into his work.
And, eventually, he tried to get me
to come live with him,
but I wouldn't go.
How come?
I didn't think he cared.
I guess I just got used to him not being around
and I couldn't forgive him for it.
Until I got here.
And I realized that he did care.
But I didn't know…
because I never gave him the chance.
And now it's too late.
I really…
I really wish I'd gotten on that train.
Mmm-hmm.
Listen, kid.
Um…
Look, I may not have memories,
um, but I know this much:
It wasn't your fault.
It wasn't anybody's fault.
And I'm sure that if your dad was here,
he would hug you so hard,
your bones would pop.
And he'd tell you
he's sorry for everything.
He'd be damn proud of you, kid.
I haven't been really nice to you.
No, you really haven't.
Well…
We still got one mystery to solve.
What?
Yours.
Let's find out who did this to you.
Get your memory back.
I'd like that.
I'd like that very much.
Well, that's a bad-guy car.
Thank you, Miss Norman.
Yes. Thank you, Miss Norman. That'll be all.
What a blabbermouth.
Please, come in.
Magnificent creatures, aren't they?
Whoa. A Flareon.
Imagine being able to evolve
into the best possible version of yourself.
Hmm. 'Sup?
That greatness inside you, just waiting to be awoken.
Hello, Tim.
He knows you?
I see you've partnered with Harry's Pikachu.
And he knows me, too.
You knew Harry?
The case Harry was working on,
it was for me.
That's a twist. That's very twisty.
This compound threatens everything I've built.
He knows about the R. How does he know about the R?
I hired Harry to trace it to its source.
Imagine my shock when the answer
turned out to be my own son.
I've devoted my life to perfecting the partnership
between Pokemon and humans.
A partnership where Pokemon bring out the best in us.
In doing so, I'm afraid I neglected
my responsibilities as a parent.
Roger resents the Pokemon.
I think he's lived in my shadow for so long,
he actually wants to destroy my legacy.
Well, there's no such thing
as "daddy issues" without "daddy".
But, Mr. Clifford, how could you let him do that?
Ever since my illness put me in this chair,
Roger has taken over more and more of the company.
He controls the board.
He also controls the police and the politicians.
And he owns the press.
Harry is the only one I can trust.
That's why you need to find him.
You haven't heard.
Harry's dead.
Oh, no, Tim.
Your father
is alive.
Look out, kid!
Advanced holographic imaging.
Since being confined to this chair,
I've invested in ways of bringing the world to me.
This was recreated from police footage.
It allows us to see things that they cannot
or don't want us to see.
He's alive.
Pika.
It's me. I was with Harry in the crash.
He needs my help.
If Harry's alive, why didn't they find him?
What is that?
Mewtwo.
A man-made abomination
created in a laboratory using DNA
from the fossil remains of the Ancient Mew.
I can't believe it.
If that thing came from Mew,
then we're looking at
the most powerful Pokemon in the world.
That's it. That's what happened to me.
Mewtwo wiped my memory.
But why?
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait. Wait, wait. Where did it take him?
That's for you to solve now.
Find Mewtwo and you will find your father.
Second chances
are special things, kid.
There's a lot we can make better if we crack this case.
One question, though. Where are we going?
I don't know, I'm just going.
You gotta tell me where. You're the detective.
Okay. If Roger Clifford is the key to all of this…
Then we need someone who has access to him.
And we both know who that is, lover boy.
Okay, come on, that's…
Come on. Let's not start that again.
There she is.
What's with the sunglasses? Can she see us?
I don't think she can see us.
- Hey. Thanks for coming.    - Don't talk to me.
Okay.
- What happens now?    - Just act casual.
But don't look at me.
There's nothing really casual about this.
Look at this.
- Oh, shit.    - Sorry. That was my fault.
- Ow!    - Sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, this is working out great.
Why don't you just have her sit over here.
You wanna just come sit with us?
I should never have encouraged you.
You have no chance.
I got access to Roger's computer.
Oh, wow, how'd you do that?
Spilled a cappuccino on his lap.
Eh, that sounds like a waste of coffee.
I searched through all his records.
I targeted the property rights in the region
and I cross-checked that with city records
for any Clifford-financed businesses until I found it.
May I present PCL:
A Pokemon genetic research facility.
But that's not all.
She's good.
Last week, PCL had an "accident"
and had to shut down their entire facility.
That's the same night Harry Goodman went missing.
No one knows what happened.
Total media blackout.
What does it all mean?
I don't know. This is very exciting.
- Are you excited?    - Yeah.
I think he just peed a little.
Oh, nope. That's me. That was me.
So, um, there's a cover-up?
Mmm-hmm.
But, er, what are they covering up?
What do you say we go find out?
So let me get this right.
We're forced to listen to this spa music
so your head doesn't explode and kill us all.
Psyduck.
Your Pikachu is so unusual.
Hey, you put that down. I am not giving you a massage.
Psyduck.
I have never known a Pokemon to wear a hat.
Yeah, he's weird. He's so weird.
Psyduck.
Of course I care about my partner's life.
Fine, fine. Hand it over.
What are you doing?
What?
Nothing.
I was actually wondering who this was.
It's PCL's chief scientist, Dr. Anne Laurent.
I bet this is the doctor Shirtless was talking about.
She lost her university grant
over experimentation of Pokemon
because she was trying to control their minds.
Oh, wow.
She's essentially a neurologist for Pokemon.
Maybe she could weigh in
on the long-term psychological effects
of being strapped into a baby seat
- next to a bomb.    - Hmm?
This is it.
Look at the signs.
Must have been a really bad accident.
That's what they want you to believe.
Whoever staged this did an excellent job.
Those signs are the perfect scarecrow for suckers.
Yeah, well, they're working on me.
Kid, this dame's looking for danger.
You want to win her over,
you gotta lead her straight to it.
First of all, women don't like to be called "dame".
Second, women appreciate calm, er, level-headed
and responsible decision-making.
What is she doing? Hey, hey!
Hey!
Lucy, what are you doing?
I'm, er, I'm cutting the fence so that we can slip through.
Where did you get those?
Oh, don't worry about it.
After you, sir.
- Psyduck.    - No? Okay.
I'll go first. Whatever's most calming.
Hmm, Psyduck.
Okay.
Psyduck. Psyduck.
Oh.
It's okay. You can stay up there.
I may have amnesia, but I'm pretty sure
this is the worst idea anyone's ever had.
What is that?
I'm not sure.
Psyduck. Psyduck.
It's Greninja.
But they don't look right.
"Test 22."
"Power enhancement"?
They were experimenting on them.
But why?
If Roger Clifford's behind this,
what's he doing experimenting on Pokemon?
A Torterra garden.
"Pokemon evolution test 33.
"Growth enhancement."
They look normal-sized to me.
Maybe it hasn't started yet.
It's like they're trying to manipulate Pokemon evolution.
Is that even possible?
I don't know.
I need to document all of this, though.
You go ahead. I'll catch up to you.
- Are you sure?    - Yeah.
Whoa.
What happened here?
Bad stuff.
Really bad stuff.
Still think this was staged?
Kid, hey! Over here.
It says Dr. Laurent's station.
Looks like it's still working.
Remote access initiated.
Psyduck!
Looks like most of the files are corrupted.
Uh-oh. Another one of those holograms.
Day 42.
After much trial and error
we perfected a stable method
to extract Mewtwo's DNA.
It's Mewtwo. No, wait.
Wait, Mewtwo came from this place?
Day 60. Clinical trials proven successful.
The inhalant results in confusion
and the total loss of free will.
Which, in turn, makes the Pokemon go wild.
We've designated this chemical as serum R.
They used Mewtwo to make R.
And they were testing it at the battles.
Day 68.
The neural link is operational.
Alert.
-Condition: Red. -Oh.
No. No, no, no!
We're losing power in the containment…
That must've been how Mewtwo escaped.
Now we're getting somewhere.
What did that thing want with Harry?
Good question, kid.
I'll try and take us back to the beginning.
Day 1. The lab is almostfully operational.
All that remains now is to capture
the most powerful Pokemon known to mankind:
Mewtwo.
It escaped nearly 20 years ago from the Kanto region.
Fortunately, our benefactor's
hired a specialist to track it down.
Good luck, Detective Goodman.
That's why Mewtwo took Harry.
It was revenge for being captured.
This doesn't make any sense.
Harry would've never been a part of this.
I wanna believe that, kid. But we gotta be honest here.
You haven't seen him in years, and I got amnesia.
Neither of us can say for sure
what Harry would or wouldn't do.
We gotta get back to the city.
Lucy. Lucy, we gotta get back to…
Lucy?
That was not there before, kid.
Ew.
Look behind you.
Whoa!
Kid, the fire alarm!
Psyduck!
Come on! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Psyduck!    - Whoa, whoa, whoa! Go back.
Psyduck!
Get down!
Come on!
Psyduck! Psyduck! Psyduck!
Duck! Duck! Duck!
Psyduck! Psyduck! Psyduck! Psyduck!
- Psyduck!    - It's okay, Psyduck.
Everything's fine.
He's gonna blow his stack, kid.
It's okay, Psyduck, it's okay. Calm down.
Psyduck!
This is no time
for your stupid headaches.
No, wait, this is the perfect time to get a headache.
- Psyduck?    - I hated rubbing your feet.
Calm down, calm down!
I'll never forgive my hands for what they did.
Get a splitting headache now, you neurotic duck!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Psyduck.
Good job, Psyduck. Where's my hat?
Something's wrong.
Is this really happening?
Don't worry.
Psyduck's psionic waves are causing hallucinations.
None of this is real.
Nope.
All of this is real! Run!
Go, go, go!
- What's happening?    - Let's go! Let's go!
At this point,
how could you not believe in climate change?
Oh no, no, no!
I got you.
Tim!
Go! Run! Run!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Okay.
We made it.
I officially hate this forest.
Tim!
Lucy!
Psyduck!
Kid, the walls are closing in.
We have to do something and we gotta do it fast.
I gotta jump for it.
That's a great fifth option. Let's work on the first four.
- You're not gonna make it!    - There's no other choice.
We have a lot of choices.
Falling to our death is not one of…
Tim!
Pull, pull, pull!
Come on!
I thought I was gonna… I thought I was gonna…
I… I…
Eyeball.
Eyeball. Eyeball!
Oh! I get it!
I get it now. This isn't a forest at all.
This is the Torterra garden.
Pikachu!
Psyduck.
He's hurt.
- Is he okay?    - I'm in bad shape, kid.
I'm here, partner. I'm here.
Did you just call me partner?
Yeah, of course. You're my partner.
Yeah, that's right. You've, er…
You've got my back.
Hey, hey, hey. Bud.
Hey! Hey, Pikachu!
Pikachu!
No.
Hey! Hey, help!
Please!
Please.
He's hurt.
He doesn't know what you're saying.
But he knows what I'm feeling.
I need to get Pikachu to a healer Pokemon.
Please.
I'm begging you.
I don't wanna lose him, too.
It's okay.
Hmm?
Tim, look.
Okay.
I'll meet you at the car.
You're gonna be okay, partner.
Here?
Hey! Wait, wait, wait!
Where are you going?
What am I supposed to do?
I've been waiting for you.
Mewtwo.
No, no, no! No, wait!
Where am I?
You're okay!
Yeah.
Somehow, I'm fine.
You brought the son to me, as agreed.
What is he talking about?
I don't know, kid. I'm as lost as you are.
Where's my father?
What'd you do with him?
- Alert.    - Oh.
We're losing power in the containment chamber.
You've done well.
Humanity is evil.
I've always believed Pokemon are…
No!
Wait, wait, wait!
Pikachu! Wait.
Hey. Slow down. We have to talk about this.
You have to go on without me.
What? What are you saying?
Roger has Mewtwo. Mewtwo has my father.
We're running out of time. We have a case to solve.
We already solved mine. I know who I am.
I'm the guy who betrayed Harry.
We don't know that.
We both saw it. I betrayed your father. Which means
I could betray you, too.
You wouldn't do that. I don't care what I saw.
- I know who you are.    - How do you know?
Because, I…
I can feel it in my jellies.
I… I made that up.
There's no jellies. There's no me.
I don't believe that.
You're better off on your own.
- Come on, Pikachu…    - No! No!
I need you. Please.
You have to stay away. It's for your own good.
No. I'm not letting you go.
You see?
I can't help it.
I hurt the people who need me.
That's who I am.
I'm sorry.
Tim.
Where's he going?
Hey, what happened?
Is Pikachu okay?
No, he's not.
Let's go. We gotta get back to the city.
Okay.
Come on.
The 10th anniversary
Ryme City Pokemon parade is set to begin this afternoon.
The whole city is converging on downtown
to watch the day's festivities.
I don't know what happened between you two,
but we need to strategize. Wait!
Where are you going?
We need to tell the public what we found.
This is breaking news.
No. No, you should break the news. You.
I'm gonna go talk to Howard.
How…
Tim!
How am I supposed to break the news
when the guy who runs the news is the breaking news?
Okay, Cynthia. We're live in five, four, three…
Stay in the car, okay?
Psyduck!
Mrs. McMaster. Hi, it's Lucy Stevens,
- the intern.    - Oh.
- At CNM?    - Could you…
Yeah. Erm, I have a story
that's really important that the people need to hear.
And I was really hoping you could help me tell it.
I just need--
Lucy, please. Take my coffee order.
Flat white, extra shot.
You got it, Cynthia.
♪Searching far and wide♪
♪Teach Pokemon to understand♪
♪The power that's inside♪
♪Pokemon!♪
♪Gotta catch 'em all♪
♪It's you and me♪
♪I know it's my destiny♪
♪Pokemon!♪
What… What is this?
I know this place.
This is the scene of the crash.
What is that?
Greninja stars.
Roger must have sent the Greninjas
to cause the crash. Which…
Which means…
Mewtwo was trying to protect us?
Advanced holographic imaging.
It allows us to see things that they cannot
or don't want us to see.
Wait, Howard would have seen this in his hologram.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
Tim!
Howard! Mr. Clifford! Your son,
he has Mewtwo here.
- Wait, why do you…    - Tim.
It's gonna be okay.
Run!
No.
The transfer worked.
My body is in the chair,
but my mind is in Mewtwo.
Howard?
Well done, Tim.
You and Harry's Pikachu led me straight to Mewtwo.
Mewtwo didn't cause the crash.
All your father had to do
was take the money and walk away.
But he started asking questions.
I had to stop him.
You tried to kill him!
I had no choice.
He tracked the R to the battles,
traced it back to Dr. Laurent.
And then he and his Pikachu helped Mewtwo escape.
So, as you can see,
we are more than happy with the turnout today.
So many families…
Thank you so much. Thank you.
That's all for today. Thank you.
Excuse me, please. Hello. Hi.
I have an interview with the mayor.
- Go on through.    - Thank you.
Mr. Mayor, I need to speak with you, please. It's urgent.
A little late for an interview, don't you think?
Please!
Before we begin the parade,
I'd like to thank our benefactor,
Howard Clifford.
This was never about curing me.
I have found a path forward for all of us.
Mewtwo has the power
to transfer the soul of a human
into the body of a Pokemon,
as long as the Pokemon are in a crazed state.
The R gas takes care of that.
The balloons. The R gas is in the balloons.
People of Ryme City!
I've finally discovered a cure.
Not just for me,
but for all of humanity!
Pokemon can evolve into better versions of themselves.
And, now, so can you!
Humans and Pokemon merged into one!
Don't let your Pokemon breathe the purple gas!
Come on! Get out of here!
This is Yoshida requesting backup!
All units should proceed to the…
Snubbull, no!
Don't let your Pokemon breathe the gas!
Don't let your Pokemon…
Oh, no! Don't breathe the gas!
Tell them!
This is Lucy Stevens reporting a citywide emergency.
Do not let your Pokemon breathe…
Psyduck, no! Don't!
Psyduck, Psyduck. Psyduck!
Psyduck?
Okay. Worst parade I've ever seen.
- Psyduck.    - Lucy. Lucy, you're in there?
- Where's Tim?    - Psyduck. Psyduck.
- Howard is Mewtwo?    - Psyduck. Psyduck.
This really blows my bridge discovery out of the water.
All right, I gotta stop this.
Game on!
Okay, Pikachu, your powers are in there somewhere.
Just need a little spark
to get this party started. Let's do this.
Harry's Pikachu.
You think you can stand in the way of the future?
I am the future!
Whoa!
He's back!
The neural link.
Roger?
Behind you!
You're a Ditto.
Ditto.
Bank left! Bank right! Right!
Where did you learn how to fly? The ground?
No, no, no. Stop, stop, stop! Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
Come on. No. That's not fair.
For the record, I have no guilt
hitting a beady-eyed version of the woman
I'm very attracted to.
Uh-oh! Pull up, pull up. Don't breathe the gas.
You breathed the gas, didn't you?
Yeah!
Finish him, Ditto!
Ditto!
No! No, no, no, no!
Pikachu!
Tim!
Harry's son is finished!
No. Tim said Volt Tackle's my best move.
Let's do this Pokemon battle thing right.
No.
Yeah!
Give me your hand! Give me your hand!
What kind of a Ditto was that?
That was one of my father's genetic experiments.
Psyduck. Ditto.
Ditto…
A feeble effort.
A Pikachu cannot defeat Mewtwo in battle.
I didn't need to defeat you.
I just needed to distract you.
Huh.
No!
What have you done?
Pikachu!
No!
- Pikachu!    - Tim!
- Oh!    - Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I pushed you away
just when you needed me the most.
I'm just happy you're back…
partner.
Please tell me you can fix this mess.
I will undo what has been done.
Let's never do that again, okay?
The strange thing is that, no matter what his flaws,
deep down,
I blame myself for not being there for him.
You. You were working on this story.
Had a lead on it before anyone else even knew.
That's correct.
Good. Right, you're going on camera.
I want you giving an in-depth report
for CNM tonight, primetime.
And make sure you close with:
"Roger Clifford pledges to undo
all the harm his father caused
starting with the Pokemon he experimented on."
I can't believe we did it.
Psyduck.
Great work. Hey, calm down. Stay calm. Okay.
Oh, I hope we never
- get to see each other again.    - Hmm.
- Meet me later tonight?    - Cool. I mean, yeah.
Okay.
Come on.
Psyduck. Psyduck. Psyduck.
Way to go, Tim.
There is one last thing I must fix.
My father.
The father you have been looking for
has been with you all along.
What's he talking about?
I don't…
Pika!
Pikachu!
You've done well.
Humanity is evil.
But you have shown me that not all humans are bad.
Harry Goodman,
your Pikachu offers its body to save your mind.
There is a son.
With the son's return, I can repair the father.
Your memory will be gone,
but your heart will know who you are.
I take this body so that you might live.
Return with the son.
Now boarding on track three,
train 453 northbound.
Hey, kid!
Grams will meet you when you arrive.
Okay.
I'll see ya.
See ya.
Pika.
Hey, Dad?
Yeah?
You think I can stay with you for a while?
I'd like that, kid.
Yeah, I'd like that very much.
Me, too.
You wanna get a coffee?
It's the weirdest thing.
That's all I've been thinking about,
is having a coffee right now.
I think I'll have to find a new job.
Oh, yeah? What are you thinking?
Erm… maybe I could give detective work a try?
Pika-Pika!
I think he likes that idea.
♪Walking alone And the shores are longing♪
♪I miss your footprints Next to mine♪
♪Sure as the waves On the sand are washing♪
♪Your rhythm keeps My heart in time♪
♪You, you found me♪
♪Made me into something new♪
♪Led me through The deepest waters♪
♪I promise loud To carry on for you♪
♪You, to carry on for you, for you♪
♪You, to carry on for you♪
♪I'll carry on for you♪
♪Talk to the wind On the open ocean♪
♪I wonder if you hear me too♪
♪Wrapped in my arms With every moment, yeah♪
♪The memories That pull me through♪
♪You, you found me♪
♪Made me into something new♪
♪Oh, yeah♪
♪Led me through The deepest waters♪
♪I promise loud To carry on to you♪
♪Ooh♪
♪You, to carry on for you, for you♪
♪To carry on for you♪
♪I'll carry on for you♪
♪You, you found me♪
♪Oh, yeah♪
♪Made me into something new♪
♪Into something new♪
♪Led me through the deepest waters♪
♪I promise loud To carry on for you♪
♪Oh, carry on for you♪
♪You, to carry on for you, for you♪
♪Keep me running, keep me coming back to you♪
♪Hold me harder, love me like you know you do♪
♪You, you found me♪
♪Made me into something new♪
♪Led me through The deepest waters♪
♪I promise loud To carry on for you♪
♪You, to carry on for you, for you♪
♪You, to carry on for you…♪
♪In the deepest waters♪
♪Oh, I'll carry on for you♪
♪Aye, aye, aye!♪
-♪No, no I could not give up♪ -♪No!♪
♪If you choose me I'll never leave♪
-♪Some of us play with fire♪ -♪Wow!♪
♪Some of us live down in the sea♪
-♪Some only come out at nightfall♪ -♪Yes!♪
♪Daytime is when They get their sleep♪
♪Some need trees And leaves just to breathe♪
♪But I'm different than all, I'm electricity!♪
♪Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!♪
♪I'm different than all, I'm electricity!♪
-♪Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!♪ -♪Yeah!♪
♪Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!♪
♪I'm different than all, I'm electricity!♪
♪Let's go!♪
♪But I'm different than all, I'm electricity!♪
♪Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!♪
♪I'm different than all, I'm electricity!♪
-♪Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!♪ -♪Yeah!♪
♪Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!♪
♪I'm different than all, I'm electricity!♪
♪Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye!♪
♪Let's go!♪