Dad, want some caramel?
Oh, thanks.
Aren't you tired?
Nah.
We're almost there.
Mei, hide!
It wasn't a policeman.
Hi!
Are any of your folks around?
Thanks.
We're the Kusakabes!
We'll be moving in down the road!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Welcome!
Thank you.
Well, this is it.
Hey, wait up!
Mei, there's a bridge!
A bridge?
There's fish too! See those flashes of light?
So, how do you like it here?
Dad, it's so cool!
It's a tunnel of trees!
Is that our house?
Hurry up!
It's a wreck!
A wreck!
Looks like a haunted house!
Haunted?
It's all rotten.
It's gonna fall down!
Mei, look at that!
Huh?
Look!
It's big, isn't it?
Dad, there's a huge tree!
Oh, it's a camphor tree.
A camphor tree!
Whoops!
An acorn.
Let me see!
Hey, another one!
I got one!
Hey, come on. I can't open the storm shutters.
Acorns!
There are acorns falling around in the house.
They dropped from up there!
I wonder if there are squirrels in here?
Or maybe it's rats that like acorns.
What?!
I'd rather have squirrels!
Where do you want to put this?
Oh, over here. I'll get these shutters
opened all the way for you.
Satsuki, can you open up the kitchen
around the back?
Okay!
It should be easy to spot.
Yep.
Come on, this way!
Wait up!
Come on, hurry up!
Let's go.
Yeah.
The bath.
There's nothing here.
Yeah…
That's the bathroom.
Dad, there's something in here.
A squirrel?
I dunno.
There were a whole bunch of black things,
but they weren't roaches or mice.
Well?
I think they were dustbunnies.
“Dustbunnies”?
Like in that picture book?
That's right. Ghosts don't come out
on such nice days like this.
When you're somewhere bright
and you suddenly walk into a dark room,
dustbunnies appear while your eyes
are still adjusting to the darkness.
Oh, I see.
Dustbunnies, come out, come out, wherever you are!
Or else we'll give you the shock of your life!
Okay, let's get to work!
Can you tell me where the stairs
to get to the top floor might be?
Huh?
Go find those stairs
and get the windows up there open.
Okay!
Hey, I'm coming too!
The toilet!
Huh?!
Ow!
Nothing!
Hey, that hurt!
Mei, I found it!
It's pitch black.
It's the dustbunnies.
An acorn.
Are you there, Mr. Dustbunny?
Okay…
And lift…
Dad, there's definitely something in this house!
That's exciting.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've always wanted to live in a haunted house.
That's not good!
I got one! Sis!
Mei.
You sure are full of energy!
This is our neighbor who's been looking after this place.
You can call her Granny.
She's come to help us.
Hello. I'm Satsuki and this is my sister, Mei.
Hello to you, too.
What a well-mannered girl you are!
I'd have cleaned up the place
if I'd known you'd move in this early.
No, you've done plenty.
I've been so busy in the rice paddies lately,
but I've still been able to do a bit of dusting now and then.
Mei, your hands are filthy.
What happened?
The dustbunny got away.
Ah! Your feet too!
Hey, mine are black too!
My, oh my, oh my.
This must be the soot sprites coming out.
“Soot sprites”?
You mean something about this big
that scurry away in a noisy panic?
That's right.
They breed in empty old houses,
running amok and covering them
with soot and dust.
I could see them when I was little.
Oh, so I guess now you can too, huh?
Are they like goblins or something?
Nah, it's nothing scary like that.
If you keep smiling, they won't bother you.
And before you know it, they'll be long gone.
I bet they're up in the ceiling right now,
talking about whether or not to move out.
Mei, they're all gonna run away.
That's no fun.
But what if a huge one comes out?
I wouldn't be scared.
Oh? Then I'm not gonna go with you
to the bathroom at night.
All right, cleaning time.
Can you go and fetch some water
from the stream?
From the stream?
I'm coming too!
Mei, wait there, okay?
Did you catch a fish?
Granny, it's working!
Keep pumping!
Don't stop until the water gets cold.
Okay!
Oh, it's you again.
Can I help you?
M-My Mom… for Granny.
What is it?
Hey, wait! What is this?
Is that you, Kanta?
Hey, you! Your house is haunted!
Kanta!
I remember doing the same sort of thing too.
I hate boys.
But I love your homemade rice cakes heaps,
Granny!
Eat as much as you want.
Thanks for your help!
Thank you for everything.
Dad, I think this wreck is gonna fall down.
That wouldn't be good
since we've only just moved in.
Let's all try laughing.
Then whatever scares you will go away.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared!
That's it. Keep it going.
Keep it going.
All right! The washing's finished!
Here we go!
Granny!
Hello!
You sure are hard at work!
Where're you all heading?
We're going to visit Mom in the hospital!
That's nice!
Say hello for me!
We will!
Ah! It's this way!
Hello.
Hello there.
Mom!
Mei! I'm so glad you came.
Dad took the wrong road.
He did?
Thanks for coming.
Well, it's a school holiday
since it's a rice planting day.
Oh, I see.
Dad's talking to the doctor.
I'm so happy that you all came to see me.
How's the new house?
Have you settled in okay?
Really? A haunted house?
Yep.
Do you like haunted houses, Mom?
Of course I do!
I can't wait to leave the hospital
and meet some ghosts.
Isn't that great, Mei?
Yeah!
Mei was worried that you wouldn't like them.
What about you two?
I love them!
I'm not scared of them!
Are you fixing up Mei's hair, Satsuki?
Yep.
It's really good.
Aren't you lucky, Mei?
But she gets mad at me all the time.
That's because you won't stay still.
Come here, Satsuki.
Isn't yours too short?
I like it this way.
What about me?! What about me?!
Wait your turn!
You still have such frizzy hair.
It's just like mine when I was your age.
Will it be like yours when I grow up?
Probably, since you and I are a lot alike.
Mom looked really well.
You're right. The doctor says
she'll be able to leave the hospital soon.
Soon? Like tomorrow?
There you go again with “tomorrow”.
Tomorrow's probably a little too soon.
Mom said she wants to sleep with me
in my bed.
Oh? Weren't you saying
you're big enough to sleep alone now?
Mom's special!
Dad!
It's morning!
Wake up!
Sorry, I overslept again.
I've got to pack my own lunch from today.
Oops, I totally forgot about that.
It's all right.
I've made something for all of us.
It's burning!
I'll be there in a sec!
This one's yours, Mei.
That's my one?!
Mei, sit down and eat!
Here you go!
Put the lid on yourself, okay?
Satsuki!
Uh-oh.
I'm here!
You made a friend already?
'Cause she's shouting, “Satsuki!”
Yup, that's Michiko.
I'm done!
See ya later!
Morning!
Morning. We better get going!
Yeah.
Hi-ya!
Morning!
Dad!
Do I look like a big girl?
Yep. Now where are you off to
with your lunch bag?
Just a little over thataway.
Dad, is it lunchtime yet?
Huh? Already?
You be the flower shop, Dad.
Pole-tads!
Huh? It's got no bottom.
Gotcha!
Who are you? A dustbunny?
Totoro? Your name's Totoro, isn't it?
Yep, you're Totoro for sure.
Totoro.
See ya!
See you later!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Oh, is it this late already?
Where's Mei? I'm off to Michiko's.
We haven't even had lunch yet.
Isn't Mei playing in the garden?
Mei!
Dad, I found her hat!
Mei. Mei.
Mei! Come on, wake up!
What do you think you're doing
sleeping out here?!
Where's Totoro?
Totoro?
Huh? Where'd he…?
Were you dreaming?
Totoro was here.
“Totoro”? Don't you mean a troll,
like in your picture book?
Yeah, but he said Totoro for sure.
He was all furry and had a huge mouth like this.
There was a little one, a bigger one,
and a huge one like this that was sleeping.
There you are.
Wow, this is amazing.
This'd make a great secret hiding place.
Dad, Mei said that she met Totoro here.
Totoro?
Yeah.
This way!
Hey, wait up!
Huh?
Here?
Nope.
Last time, it went to a big tree.
But there wasn't any other path.
Ah, Mei! Come back!
Mei, I said come back!
But it's true! Totoro was really here!
I'm not lying.
Mei?
Satsuki and I don't think you're lying.
You must've met the guardian of this forest.
You were very lucky.
But you won't always be able to see him.
All right, we should give him a proper greeting.
A greeting?
To Tsukamori Forest we go!
Whew!
You're getting heavy, Mei…
Dad, it's that camphor tree!
It's big, isn't it?
This is it!
This is the tree?
Yep.
Come on, Dad! Hurry up!
The hole's gone.
Are you sure it was here?
Yeah.
She said the hole's disappeared.
See? I told you that you won't be able
to see him whenever you want.
But will we see him again?
I want to meet him too.
If you're lucky, sure.
What a magnificent tree.
This tree must've stood here
for years and years.
You know, trees and people
used to be good friends long ago.
When I saw that tree,
I fell in love with this place.
And I know Mom will like it too.
Okay, let's pay our respects
and then get back home for lunch.
Oh, that's right! I promised
to go over to Michiko's place.
I want to go too!
Attention!
We thank you for looking after Mei.
And we ask that you please continue
to look after us.
And the race home is on!
Hey! That's not fair!
Hey!
Wait up!
Hurry up!
“I've got some really amazing news for you today.
Mei met the giant creature, Totoro.
I'm really hoping to meet him myself, too.”
Kanta, you're going to be late
if you don't hurry it up!
Yeah.
Ahem!
Mei?
Miss!
Yes, Satsuki?
Um, it's my sister.
Granny. Mei.
I'm sorry. She insisted to be with you
and wouldn't listen to me.
But…
Mei, it's Dad's day at the university,
so you promised to be a good girl
and wait at Granny's today.
I still have two hours of school,
and Granny's too busy for this.
She's been so good up 'til now, weren't you?
Granny, I'll go talk to my teacher.
Satsuki's family are going through a tough time
because their mom is in hospital.
So everyone, I want you to be nice to them.
What's that?
It's Totoro.
You're supposed to be quiet, okay?
Okay.
See you later!
I'm going now!
Bye-bye, Mei!
Tell everyone I had to
give the club a miss today.
Okay, we'll let the teacher know.
See you later!
Bye-bye!
We'd better get a move on, Mei.
It's gonna rain.
Okay.
Ah! Here it comes!
Come on.
I didn't cry. Aren't I good?
Yeah…
But this isn't good.
Dear Lord Guardian, please let us
shelter here for a little while.
But…
That was lucky, wasn't it, Sis?
Yeah.
This umbrella's got holes in it.
Looks like Dad didn't take his umbrella.
I'm gonna go too.
I said I forgot it!
What idiot forgets his umbrella
on a rainy day?
That hurt!
I bet you were swinging it around
and it broke.
I did not!
Hello?
Oh, Satsuki, and Mei too.
Grandma!
I'm sorry about today.
Not at all.
I'm sorry we couldn't do more.
Um, Kanta lent us this umbrella.
Huh? He did?
It's a bit worse for wear, isn't it?
Mei was with me, so it was a big help.
But Kanta must've got soaked.
Thank you for everything.
Not at all. He gets himself covered in mud all the time,
so it probably cleaned him up a little.
Are you off to meet your dad?
Yes.
What good girls you are.
Bye-bye, Mei.
Bye-bye.
Who was that?
Beats me!
Just in time!
Are you getting on?
All right, drive on.
Dad wasn't on it.
He'll be on the next one for sure.
Do you want to wait at Granny's?
What's the matter?
Mei?
Are you sleepy?
That's why I told you…
Do you want to go to Granny's now?
It won't be much longer,
so hang in there.
The bus sure is late.
Here.
Totoro?
Oh, just a second.
You can borrow this.
Quick, Mei's slipping off.
You hold it like this.
Here comes the bus!
He took Dad's umbrella…
I'm sorry.
All right, drive on.
The train was late, so I missed the bus.
Were you worried?
He came out, Dad! He really came out!
And a cat bus!
Huh?
It was huge!
With eyes like this!
I met him! I met Totoro!
It was so cool!
Come on!
“Dear Mom, my heart's still racing
from the excitement today.
It was such a mysterious, weird and fun day.
Totoro even gave us a wonderful present.
It was wrapped in a bamboo leaf
and tied up with dragon whiskers.
We opened it when we got home…
and found lots of nuts inside.”
“We thought our garden would be even better
if it turned into a forest,
so we planted them in the garden.
But…”
“…they don't want to sprout.
Mei's there all day, every day,
and keeps saying, ‘Still nothing. Still nothing.’
She looks just like a patient little crab.
It's nearly summer vacation.
Dearest, dear Mom, please get well soon.
Love, Satsuki.”
Hey, come on.
Lights out.
Hang on!
Dad, do you think they'll sprout tomorrow?
Hmm, well I'm sure Totoro would know.
Good night.
Mei!
That's where we planted the nuts.
We did it!
Mei, we're the wind!
The tree's gone.
We did it!
It was a dream!
But it wasn't a dream!
We did it! We did it!
We did it!
Mr. Kusakabe! Telegram!
Mr. Kusakabe!
You've got a telegram!
No one's home?
Granny!
I'm over here.
This one's ready to eat.
What about this one, Granny?
Go for it.
Your garden's like a house of treasures, Granny.
Well, let's take a little break.
Right, these are nice and cold now.
Snack time!
It's good!
You think?
Well, they've been soaking up the sun,
so they're good for you.
Would they help Mom get better too?
Of course.
If she eats my homegrown veggies,
she'll get better in no time.
Mom's coming home this Saturday.
She's gonna sleep with me in my bed!
I see. So she'll finally be out of the hospital.
Nah, it's a temporary thing so she can
get used to the outdoors little by little.
So she has to go back on Monday.
Oh, okay.
Then we'll feed her lots of my veggies
while she's here.
I'll give her this corn I picked.
I'm sure that'll make her very happy.
Yeah!
A telegram. We accepted it
since you weren't home.
For us?
Granny, Dad won't be back
until later this evening.
Then you better open it, just in case it's urgent.
Please contact Shichikokuyama.
Shichikokuyama Hospital!
It's from Mom's hospital!
Maybe something happened to her.
What should I do, Granny?
They want us to contact them.
All right, calm down.
Do you know where your dad is?
I know his office number at the university,
but we don't have a phone.
Kanta, take her back to the main house
and let her use our phone.
Okay.
Mei, stay here!
Mei, you need to stay with Granny!
Hello, I'd like to make
a long-distance call, please.
It's to Tokyo 31-1382.
Yes.
What an adorable girl, Kanta.
Hello?
Okay.
Hello, is this the archaeology department?
Could I speak to my father—
I mean, Mr. Kusakabe.
I'm Satsuki Kusakabe.
Yes.
Dad? It's me, Satsuki!
Oh, what's up?
From the hospital?
Okay, I'll call them right away.
Did something happen to her?
What are we gonna do, Dad?
Don't worry.
I'll call the hospital
and then call you right back.
So just wait there.
Well, I'm hanging up now, okay?
Ma'am, could I please wait here?
My dad's going to call me back.
Sure, stay as long as you like.
Sis!
No you don't! This corn's for my mom!
I said no, I'm giving it to my mom!
Mei, they said Mom's not doing so well,
so she can't come home this weekend.
No!
There's nothing we can do.
You don't want her to overdo it
and get worse, do you?
No!
Come on, we just have to wait a little longer.
So you don't care if she dies, do you?!
No!
You're so stupid!
I've had it with you!
We should go.
She's so stupid!
So stupid…
It's about time we put away the laundry.
Don't be sad.
Granny's here to help, so cheer up.
Your dad said he'll stop by the hospital.
Besides, they said it's just a cold,
so she'll be home next Saturday.
This is just like last time when they said
she wouldn't be in hospital for long.
They said it was just like a cold.
But what if she dies?
Satsuki…
Maybe Mom's…
Don't worry, it'll be okay.
Nobody would ever leave
such sweet girls like you.
There, there. Don't cry.
I'll stay here until Dad comes back, okay?
Mei!
Did she come back?
Wasn't she at the bus stop?
No.
That's strange.
Where could she have gone?
I had a big fight with her earlier.
I mean, she was…
Maybe she's heading to the hospital!
Shichikokuyama Hospital?
Why, that's a three-hour walk
even for grown-ups!
I'll go check!
Kanta!
Quick! Go get your dad!
Mei's missing!
She's so silly—always getting lost.
Mei!
Excuse me, mister. Um…
Huh?
Have you seen a little girl pass this way?
She's my sister.
Let's see… A little girl?
I'm pretty sure
I would've noticed someone like that.
Maybe she wasn't here.
Are you sure she came this way?
I don't know.
Mei!
Please stop!
That was reckless, you idiot!
I'm looking for my sister.
Have you seen a little girl?
Your little sister?
I think she's heading to Shichikokuyama Hospital.
She's only four years old.
Did you see anyone, Yoko?
No. We just came from there,
but we didn't see anyone like that.
Really? Thanks anyway.
Where have you come from?
From Matsugo.
Matsugo?!
Surely she can't have come this far?
Well, bye.
Satsuki!
Kanta!
Find her?
No. And you?
No.
My dad and some others are looking for her.
I'll go to Shichikokuyama for you,
so you should go back home.
She must've taken a wrong turn
on the way to the hospital.
A little while ago,
they found a sandal by the pond.
We're not sure if it's hers or not!
Did you find her?
Lord have mercy on her.
The mud's too deep around there,
better search further away!
Hey, are there any more poles?
Grandma, Satsuki's here!
Granny!
I-It's hers, isn't it?
It's not Mei's.
Thank goodness.
I was sure it was Mei-chan's.
What's that? Granny was just
jumping to conclusions?
Then, uh, where's she gone?
I s'pose we'll start searchin'
all over the place again.
We better hurry, it'll be dark soon.
Sorry, everyone. I know it's a lot to ask,
but we'll have to split up.
It's fine. We're all in this together!
Shouldn't someone notify the police?
Okay, let's do that.
Please,
let me in to Totoro's home.
Mei's missing.
It's almost dark, and she's out there all alone.
Totoro!
Mei's missing, Totoro. We looked everywhere,
but we couldn't find her.
Please help me find her!
I'm sure by now she's crying somewhere.
I don't know what else to do.
No one else can see it.
Mei!
The trees are moving out of the way!
Sis!
Mei!
You silly girl.
I'm sorry.
Did you want to give your corn to Mom?
You'll take us to the hospital?
Thank you!
I'm sorry. The hospital didn't need
to send a telegram just for a cold.
The girls must be worried.
I feel so bad about it all.
No, they'll be fine
once they know what's going on.
You and the girls have all been doing so well
holding out this long.
The good times will be
just around the corner.
I think it's been harder on the girls
than they let on.
I'm especially sorry for Satsuki
because she's been so understanding.
You're right.
Once I'm out of the hospital,
I'm going to spoil those girls rotten.
Oh no!
Mom's laughing.
Looks like she's fine.
Yeah.
Okay, I have to hurry up and get well!
Huh?
Who put this here?
What's up?
I could swear I just saw Satsuki and Mei
laughing up in that pine tree.
It sounds crazy but maybe you did. Look.