Police.
Show me your ID.
- Check his ID.
- Yes sir.
- What's in your bag?
- Headquarter,
- Let me see.
- please verify ID number C532743…
Bracket 1, Kwai Ching-hung.
Open it.
The arrangement for Hong Kong
contained in the agreement
are not measures of expediency.
They are long-term policies
which will be incorporated
in the Basic Law for Hong Kong
and preserved intact for 50 years from 1997.
It is the common interest
as well as shared
responsibilities of China and Britain
to ensure the Joint Declaration is fully
implemented with no encumbrances.
An armed robbery took place this afternoon in Kwun Tong.
4 armed suspects robbed 5 gold shops
on Mut Wah Street.
Fuck you!
In the footage provided by our audience,
the robbers exchanged fire
with the Special Duties Unit.
2 passersby and 3 policemen
were injured in the incident.
The 5 gold shops lost $10M in total.
The police believe the mastermind
is the "Most Wanted" Yip Kwok-foon.
Bro foon, you're unbeatable!
But shit has hit the fan!
I told you to put more newspaper underneath!
Look, there's blood everywhere!
Take it, jerk!
Shit has really hit the fan!
I can give you 20% tops. Sorry.
We agreed on 40%.
Don't you have moral principle?
You're paying $2M for $10M's worth of swag?
We used to get 50%!
Now you fences are getting it all!
We're getting shit!
Times have changed.
The cops are on the prowl!
Especially for your swag, Bro Foon!
It took us 2 years to fence it last time!
Stocks, real estate,
and even chestnuts are more profitable!
Do me a favor.
40%.
Bro Foon, you always have your way!
How about you find another fence?
If I can't take it, I doubt others would dare to!
Fuck you!
Open the safe!
Are you robbing me?
Don't make me do it.
Thanks so much, Bro Foon.
Don't look me up in the future.
There's no more business between us!
We go separate ways!
Light, Bro Foon.