Police.
Show me your ID.
- Check his ID.
- Yes sir.
- What's in your bag?
- Headquarters,
- Let me see.
- Please verify ID number C532743...
Bracket 1, Kwai Ching-hung.
Open it.
The arrangements for Hong Kong
contained in the agreement
are not measures of expediency.
are not measures of expediency
They are long-term policies which will be incorporated
in the Basic Law for Hong Kong
and preserved intact for 50 years from 1997.
It is in the common interests
as well as shared responsibilities of China and Britain
to ensure the Joint Declaration is fully
implemented with no encumbrances.
An armed robbery took place this afternoon in Kwun Tong.
Four armed suspects robbed five gold shops
on Mut Wah Street.
Fuck you!
In the footage provided by our audience,
the robbers exchanged fire
with the Special Duties Unit.
Two passersby and three policemen
were injured in the incident.
The five gold shops lost $10 million in total.
The police believe the mastermind
is the "Most Wanted" Yip Kwok-foon.
Bro Foon, you're unbeatable!
But shit has hit the fan!
I told you to put more newspaper underneath!
Look, there's blood everywhere!
Take it, jerk!
Shit has really hit the fan!
I can give you 20% tops. Sorry.
We agreed on 40%.
Don't you have any moral principles?
You're paying $2M for $10M worth of swag?
We used to get 50%!
Now you fences are getting it all!
We're getting shit!
Times have changed.
The cops are on the prowl!
Especially for your swag, Bro Foon!
It took us two years to fence it last time!
Stocks, real estate,
and even chestnuts are more profitable!
Do me a favor.
40%.
Bro Foon, you always have your way!
How about you find another fence?
If I can't take it, I doubt others would dare to!
Fuck you!
Open the safe!
Are you robbing me?
Don't make me do it.
Thanks so much, Bro Foon.
Don't look me up in the future.
There's no more business between us!
We go separate ways!
Light, Bro Foon.
Fisherman!
Don't worry.
These ships belong to Yi Fa.
What's Yi Fa?
Yi Fa from Panyu, Guangzhou.
They smuggle electric appliances.
So pompously? So brazenly?
They have strong backing. It's legit!
A TV set sells for $2K
in Hong Kong and $8K in China.
They earn millions of dollars in each transaction.
Cash keeps rolling in!
Used notes with no consecutive serial numbers.
I need them today!
You have $80 million over there.
I want it by 5 PM!
You go get it. I want it now!
Manager Shum, how much do we have?
Manager Fok!
We are in love but can't be together.
I wait day by day but you never come back...
I want to forget you but you haunt my memory.
Mr Cheuk,
let's discuss the price.
Was it a bit flat?
No way! Let's start over!
Red face,
red skirt, red scarf,
like white paper...
I said let's start over. Didn't you hear me?
Let's not waste time!
Mr Tycoon,
we agreed on $3 billion.
That's final.
It's impossible to get so much cash
out of the blue.
I've only got $500 million on hand.
Did I say you could go?
Take the $500 million now.
Don't get too greedy.
Then I'll give you back half of your son.
You want the upper or lower half?
Do you really think I won't call the police?
Do the cops know where your son is?
All they can do is arrest and torture me.
But after 48 hours, they have to release me.
By that time, however, your son will be...
Call the Commissioner of Police!
I said let's start over. Didn't you hear me?
You hear me, or not?
If you can't hear me with your ear,
I might as well cut it off, OK?
Please don't!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You should've said so earlier.
What's up?
The Commissioner didn't answer?
You're playing me, right?
Let's play it all the way then!
Leaving so soon, Officer Wu?
Mr Tycoon is looking for you.
Mr Tycoon, didn't you call the cops? Come here!
Mr Ho.
They are sending these dogs after me,
but they are useless.
No wonder it was easy to kidnap your son.
So, you are willing to confess?
Officer,
if I said I'd fucked your mother,
did I really fuck her?
Shouldn't you ask Mr Ho where his son is?
My son...
is all right.
I came here to borrow money from Mr Tycoon.
Is that a crime?
Mr Ho, tell us if he's threatening you.
We can arrest him right away!
No, he's not.
Have you heard it loud and clear, Officer?
I said he's not threatening me!
Calm down, Royal Hong Kong Police!
Mr Tycoon,
how much will you "lend" me?
$3 billion.
Are you in Guangzhou for business or leisure?
Excuse me?
Business? Travel?
Yeah, I am a businessman.
Guangzhou Railway Station
I'd like to reserve a private room
at 8 PM tomorrow.
My name is Chen. Thank you.
Hello, Commander.
8 PM tomorrow at Fengman Restaurant.
Who the fuck am I? I'm Chiu.
Don't make me fucking wait for you.
That's it.
Fengman Restaurant
Almost there, Mr Fong.
OK.
Which room?
OK. Coming.
- Take it.
- What?
Take it. Let me put the tie on.
Da-bao. This way.
Mr Fong.
Where's the vase?
It's just a cheap one.
Never mind. Let's go.
Chief Chen.
This is Zhang Da-bao, Boss Zhang,
who has bought Yi Fa.
This is Chief Chen from Industry and Commerce.
We're buddies.
Nice to meet you, Chief Chen.
Nice to meet you.
Let's have a drink.
Let's drink together.
Have a seat.
Bottoms up!
Boss Zhang cannot drink?
I said bottoms up!
Yes!
Bottoms up!
Da-bao is my buddy.
We've only met quite recently.
But we hit it off right away!
Chief Chen,
please help him.
This vase must be expensive!
Just a modest gift.
Here's how it works:
when Chief Chen grows tired of it,
Boss Zhang can buy it back!
It's worth at least ¥300,000!
Didn't we agree on ¥200,000?
I got the price wrong?
Oh, even Homer sometimes nods.
No way!
Chief Chen is a connoisseur.
What do we know?
If Chief Chen says ¥300,000, then it's ¥300,000.
Come get the business license tomorrow.
I'll have it nicely framed for you.
Thanks so much, Chief Chen.
We're buddies.
Boss Zhang, what would you like to eat?
Braised pork with preserved vegetables.
That's too oily for me.
Let me order.
Shall we have a seafood platter?
Let me order it.
Waiter!
Mr Zhang, best of luck with your business!
Thanks a lot.
Cheers.
Bottoms up!
This guy plays golf every Sunday
in Clear Water Bay.
One-way road. Quiet. No phone signal. It may work.
Hey! Where's our rice?
Next.
This one is easy.
A super playboy.
Drunk every night.
He recently took an actress as a mistress.
Hey!
Where is our rice?
Rice? Give me a second.
Your rice is coming right away.
Sometimes he would send his driver away.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Enjoy your food.
Close the door.
Sir, please follow me.
Give me a cup of tea.
Hey! Haven't you gone to the bathroom just now?
- Wait! Don't puke.
- Hey! The rice is cold!
Give me a second.
- I'm sorry. The rice is cold?
- I want tea.
- Hurry up!
- Tell me the room number...
- I want tea.
- Give me a second. I'll show you the way.
Sure, I'll get you tea.
Give me a second. I will be right back.
Take it easy.
We came to China to shake off those cop dogs.
You went too far last time!
I live life to the full.
C'est la vie.
There's no other way.
We've stolen cars, committed burglaries,
and robbed cash vans.
We even kidnapped the tycoon's son.
Should we do more kidnappings?
What do you have in mind?
Spit it out. We can discuss.
I'm a mountaineer.
After conquering one mountain,
I need to find a higher and harder mountain.
That's it.
Before finding that mountain,
let's find the money first.
Let's keep doing it.
Cheng, 53 years old.
No children. His wife is in charge.
A mobile phone used to cost over ¥10,000.
Who could afford that?
Not everyone is a child of
a high-ranking official.
Now the cheaper, the better.
We have a population of ten million.
Say ¥1,000 a set,
¥10,000 for ten sets.
We will be fatter than Chow Yun-fat!
Beepers are already outdated.
OK, I'll talk to you later.
Excuse me, Boss.
Please go on.
Don't give us a hard time.
We're doing small business.
Big Bro, these kids are great.
The guy who came in first
has a criminal record in Hong Kong.
Don't know why you brought him here.
I told you to bring some decent-looking guys.
They all look like criminals and idiots.
You should be out of business.
What is he staring at?
He is smart and helpful
I don't want the guy in blue either.
You only need two men this time?
Take the others to broaden their horizons.
Got it!
Let me see to it.
What are you fucking looking at?
You, you, get lost!
Stop drinking and scram!
You two come with me.
Faster.
So slow!
Big Bro Chiu,
Wang Lei.
Hong Qi.
Say Big Bro Chiu.
Big Bro Chiu!
They understand Cantonese?
Of course!
Come have a drink.
Spruce them up before sending them to Hong Kong.
Sure will!
Motherfucker.
Sit and eat.
Commander,
who's this Big Bro Chiu?
Who cares if he is Big Bro Chiu or not?
He is a douchebag.
He is a sly,
old fox who changes identities.
He looks just like Kwai Ching-hung,
the invisible King of Thieves in Hong Kong.
Kwai Ching-hung disappeared
after killing cops.
Then Big Bro Chiu popped up.
Big Bro Chiu is just a name.
Is Fai here?
Fai.
What's up?
- Someone is looking for you.
- Hey.
Bro Coke?
Hey!
She's Thai?
Noon, go buy a dozen Cokes.
When did you come back?
Just now.
You are too kind. Come in and have a seat.
Did you just speak Thai?
Do you think I speak French?
You stink!
Really?
Bo.
How can you be so rude?
Come help set the table.
Dinner will be served soon.
Naughty girl.
Go wash your hands.
I did wash my hands.
You ate yesterday. Are you going to eat today?
Bo, slow down. Don't rush.
Bro, Coke.
You want some?
Shall we share it?
Don't let her drink it.
She was coughing.
I don't wanna spend money on meds.
I wasn't coughing. I just had a fever.
It's all right to have a sip.
Not coughing? You are being cheeky!
I say no Coke.