Young master, we are ready
What's a hard job for you, young master
The towel, young master
What did he write?
His name!
Great! Young master knows how to
write his name!
Yes!
Nice calligraphy
Get lost
Nice calligraphy! So Cha Ha Yee Chan!
It's reversed, Master
Chan Yee Ha Cha So
Good boy, but, don't be proud! Got me?
Dad, since the first
emperor of the Ching Dynasty,
our family
has been illiterate
But not, my son, that's your grandson,
he knows how to write his name!
Dad, it's very great!
He knows writing now,
he will be scholar one day
Now, he knows how to write his name,
he will have a son later
Young master, you should try hard to learn
Chan, I think, we should mount it
OK
Professor, show it in some obvious places
By the way, one minute,
why don't you carry it with traditional
decoration in the street?
Let's go!
Chan, come and sit…
I am so pleased that you are that hard
working and filial
Listen to me, I am notorious of being
a spendthrift
My fortune is almost used up
If I die one day,
you should depend on yourself
I used to depend on myself
The cheques worth 100,000 taels!
Don't be an extravagant spender
Give me the imported hat
Where are you going? Chan!
I am having a grand birthday party tonight
How old are you?
25 years old. Come earlier
But you should dress up first
You are like beggar!
How can a beggar be that rich?!
I do want to be a rich beggar!
That fat-headed…
Come over here
What's the matter?
The invitation card of my son is great!
If I hold a birthday party in future,
I want a better invitation card!
Your Majesty, how do you think about
the Cantonese Opera?
For sure, it can't compete with Peking Opera!
But, I am appreciated to view this
Money…
Happy birthday to you, Mr So
I am homeless and sick…
I am poor, I am damn poor!
- Please give me some money
- Kidding? Damn you beggar!
How can you beg here?
Go to hell!
- Give him tips
- Yes, young master
Are you kidding? How can you give him tips?
A beggar is a man too
Everyone can come here
if he has money
Your living,
including the expenditure for hooking,
I will pay for you!
You pay it?
So what?
Nothing!
- Come into my room…
- Please follow me.
Mr So!
Hello…
How are you, Madam Pimp?
It's very bad of you to call me that!
Just be frank, why not?
You should be frank!
Your hat, is like the mourning uniform!
Is your dad passed away?
I feel happy to talk in this way
Mr Chiu, you helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang,
the emperor will give you award for this
I'll appreciate it if you
speak something nice in front of the emperor
Please have the towel
Mr So has come
Congratulation!
This way…
Mr So, today is your big day,
you must be very happy!
We have some new girls,
you must be satisfied with it
What are they? Gold fish, or cooked fish?
What does that mean?
You idiot! Gold fish is for watching only
Cooked fish can be eaten
Cooked fish of course
You, cooked fishes, why don't you
come and serve Mr So?
Mr So, you are the superior master today
What kind of woman do you want? Just tell me
I won't mind, every women is just the same
Nothing special
Mr So, what's the matter?
I am attacked
What?
Who dared so? I will hit that
bastard's mouth for you
She didn't use her mouth
She used her eyes
Tempting, and I smell blood
I haven't seen such eyesight before
Who is she?
Miss Yushang comes to be part time hooker only
Is Mr Chiu interested to sleep with her?
You should ask His Majesty first
How is it? Your Majesty?
We are friends, just go ahead if you want!
Mr Chiu, help yourself
Thank you then
The room service please
Yushang, come and greet Mr Chiu
Sister, he is the one we want
He killed dad
I know, stay calm
Let's go
- May I be excused
- Mr Chiu
Miss Yushang has arrived
How are you? Mr Chiu
A pretty woman!
Mr Chiu, about tonight…
100,000 taels
if Miss Yushang sleeps with our
young master tonight…
You are not welcomed
I am sorry, I am damn sorry
Don't you have any objection?
Let me say something fair
If any of you can offer more than 100,000 taels
Yushang will sleep with whom
Don't quarrel because of such
small amount, isn't it right?
Pal, you are a big spender
The cheque is too simple to me
I have a pearl which is granted by the
Royal family, it's invaluable!
I love the pearl more
Mr Chiu, I will wait you in my room
Does the pearl worth 100,000 taels?
Don't you think that's too little for you?
I love money too. But, I don't like you
You are frank! I love it very much
Mr So…
It doesn't matter,
I think, my hat doesn't match me
Yushang doesn't like me, I deserve it
I am glad you understand this
Don't worry, I have many pretty girls here
I trust your arrangement
None of my business
How bold are you?
Mantis Fist? It seems to be powerful
Music!
Keep this
See my Crane's Fists!
The Tiger's Claws!
How can a mantis fight with a tiger?
I know Tiger Claws and Crane's Fists too!
Well, try my mantis!
Bravo…
Your Tiger's claws are defeated
Actually it's not Tiger's Claws,
it's beggar's fists!
That's why it's too weak
You move fast!
It seems to be powerful…
Kid, you don't know how the wind blows
The general of Canton has arrived
Get lost…
Who dares bully my son, let me teach him a lesson
Master
Don't panic, Chan who bullied you?
It's me who bullied others
What? You bullied others?
How much does he have?
Is he qualified to be bullied by you?
Master, they are the ones
Who are they?
Just take a look
The King of Iron Hat?
Send the gift
Chan
They send you so valuable present,
you'd stop bullying them
- Come on, give tips to the girl here
- Master
King of Iron Hat, Seng-ko-lin-ch'in
is written on the medal
How dare you seize the medal of His Majesty?
Cuff him
Hold it, according to the Ching's law,
Courtier is not allowed hooking
Now, you are in the brothel
Do you know you have committed the laws of Ching?
How about you?
- You mean me?
- Yes!
That's right, I come…
- to arrest…
- You!
- Him!
- Arrest him
I am the general of Canton,
so I should arrest those bad people
By the way…
What else? Go ahead
Today is the birthday of the Ex-Empress Dowager
So your crime is doubled
It may cause to capital punishment
Kill him…
According to the Ching laws,
anyone without a tail should be killed
So you…
Do you want to see my hair?
You can see as much as you want! Fat-headed
Cut the crap, just kill him
OK, it's finished
General So, let's play happily together,
so forget it
I haven't played!
Your Majesty,
a rascal has ruined the atmosphere here,
I should be blamed for poor arrangement
None of your business
Let's go
Master, you can't fool this guy. Let's go
OK, go
Just forget the trouble
Young master, your hat
He is great!
Uncle Mok, the dishes are all poisoned
Chiu assassinated our Master
and some generals of The Taiping Reign
And he framed us, the Beggars Association,
to be the assassinators
Thus made us
being despised by the world
Saying that we became the dogs of the government
I should ask him to pay for it
His initial power is harmful
Don't take action until he is trapped
Because we can't defeat him even
we group together
I will try my best to seduce him to the bed
Senior, somebody is coming
Get ready…
Miss Yushang, we meet again
Why do you come here? Where is Mister Chiu?
The pearl of Mr Chiu is broken
by Mr So and become pearl powder
I have drunk it
Don't judge Mr So from his hair,
he is really romantic and funny
But…
Stop, I have taken his money,
100,000 taels you know?
I won't give it back
About the personality of Mr So…
Cut the crap, pimp!
Leave here first
Yes, you are right
- Miss Seven…
- Just accept this
Who is this guy?
I don't know
Miss, first of all, I have a good news to you
I love you
To me, this is a bad news
I know you will reply like this
Cut the crap
I wish to pay you 100 pearls
for you your company tonight
I don't want to talk to you
Please get out
I haven't chosen a wrong one
OK, I will drink this wine first
No…
It surprised me
Miss
Hands off!
You know Kung-fu?
No, I don't know Kung-fu at all
I beg you, stop bothering me
I won't accompany you
Yushang, no one treats me like this
I have found that I am in love with you
What?
I have been in love with you
Are you kidding?
I am not kidding, I decided to marry you
Are you nuts?
Kidding?
Are there anyone hiding here?
That's good, I want a witness
- Witness?
- Yes
I swear in front of your sword
I do want to marry Miss Yushang
as my wife, I am sincere
If I cheat, I will be killed by thunder
Sister, I feel excited for you
Hey
Don't you know it's that easy to be my husband?
How can I be your husband?
I want him to be the superior Kung-fu master
Be the top of all
Can you do that?
Let me think for one second
I can do it
OK
Do it first and then look for me
Well, I think we should fix a date for our wedding
Because, this is too easy to me
to be the Kung-fu scholar!
OK, but you'd give me some time to consider it
No problem, I will wait for your answer
outside the garden
I won't leave until seeing you
Crazy!
We come for the Beggars Association,
those unrelated persons leave at once
Sir, the timing is fit
The road is safe now, please go
Good, very good
Let's go!
Shit, we are late
That Manchurian should be blamed
Sister…
What's the matter?
The idiot is still there
Let's kill him
Forget it, he doesn't mean to bother us
Let him go
Are you fond of him?
What did you say?
I won't fall in love with anybody
until Chiu is killed
Especially him
Chiu is good at Kung-fu
Mok said, we can't defeat him unless
using the "Dragon Killing Palms"
So, I can never marry!
Let's go, if you want to marry
What evil are you? How dare you scare me?
Mr So, it's me!
You are the pimp?!
Yes!
You have flat figure, where are your busts?
It's early in the morning,
they haven't waken up yet
It's lucky of you for not being killed
Don't go around if you haven't made up yet
I won't do it again
Stop waiting for Miss Yushang, she left
What?
Where is she going?
She… she is going to Peking
Peking?
Men should contribute to the country
Where should I put my pig-tail?
Swing and swing…
I pull it and play it…
Dad!
I decided to join the examination for the
scholar of Martial Arts
Chan
I have been longing for this word for 25 years
For the family of us, you should do that
Don't misunderstand it, I do it not for no one
But for a woman
What a hero!
For a girl, you want to be the scholar
of Martial Arts!
Who is that girl?
The hooker of Yee Hung Brothel, Miss Yushang
For a hooker?
What's wrong with it?
You have different taste, you are great!
I am admiring you!
I will accompany you to Peking
2, 3, 4, 5, 6
I am coming
Young master is going for the examination,
let's move to Peking too
Stop chasing,
we won't take the hens with us
Be careful!
If you break my stuff,
I will teach you good lesson
Be careful!
Good morning dad
Good morning
You want to move everything to Peking?
Sure
Please leave me a clothe
You are only a kid, you don't need this
But I am not small
Are you bigger than mine?
You despise me!
Mine will be bigger than yours one day
Let's find something, say trousers to cover it
I don't want to see it
Why are you standing here for?
Why don't you remove it?
It's a hard job to remove such a big house!
Please, work hard men!
Ready, 1, 2, 3, push!
Push!
Be careful!
Tie it well…
Master, do you want to move the tree too?
Sure,
or how can I eat Lychee in Peking?
Push it over…
Be careful
Take care of my Lychee, you fat headed!
Chiu helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang in Kwangsi
So I bring him here to greet Your Majesty
Fine, I am now appointing you to be
the Deputy Secretary
Hope you will serve our Ching Dynasty
whole-heartedly
Thank you, Your Majesty
Your Majesty, Mr Chiu is a magician
Why don't you ask him to show you something?
Magic?
Mr Chiu, then show me your magic
Yes, Your Majesty
There is nothing surprising, go
Yes
I am sorry for scaring you
If this girl is real, that's fantastic!
Hurry up!
What's the matter?
Come on, go in
Hide in
Get ready, young master
Come on
Freeze, don't move
Sweet smell, are you Piu Hung?
You are great! I love it
Closer
So big! You must be Small!
You are bad, how can you say so to me?
You are big!
What? Pregnant woman? You can't cheat me
You are dad
How bad are you, how can you guess that?
Good boy
I wanted to trick you actually,
you are really smart
Young master has to join the examination tomorrow,
stop playing
Get out…
Chan, have you prepared
for your examination?
What should I prepare?
I must win, don't you know that?
Yes I do!
I have faith in you from seeing your behaviour!
Chan, this is Uncle Cheng
He will be the examiner
Say hello to Uncle Cheng
How are you, Uncle Cheng?
See
Doesn't he seem to be the winner?
It depends on the fate
Cheng, I've asked someone
to finish the papers which you gave me
Will the questions be changed?
Don't worry about the question paper
But about the test of arrows shooting,
riding, boxing and weapons…
He should try his best
Don't worry
My son is keen in martial arts
So, can I deduct some from the payment
of 2 million taels?
We are friends, but that is business
Let the Horse teams be the pioneer
The arrows teams go side ways,
the gunmen stay back
The candidates come in
I can't lift it
I don't want to waste my force
Shameless? Damn you!
Oh, 10 marks
The final race now starts
The candidates,
Po Ye Tat Tor from Mongolia
Bravo…
And So Cha Ha Yee Chan from Canton
Last call
So, one to ten Po, one to one
Are you kidding, how can the betting rates
differ so much?
One to ten for Chan? Kidding?
Why don't you have faith in Chan?
That is, Chan defaulted in weight lifting
Look, Po entered the final race
with full marks, it differs
It's an examination of the Scholar of
Martial Arts, not king of coolie
It's meaningless to be the champion
of weight lifting
- You shouldn't put it that way
- What?
He is smart
I've studied this race for a long time
I feel strange about the rate too
Po is smart and strong
But see the sweat of his neck
I think it's because he is getting tired
Really?
But this So
What do you thing?
He has been disappointing the audience
But he has achieved very hard
What?
He tried very hard
So I want to bet on him
How much do you want to bet?
800,000 taels
Why not 2 million taels?
What? Why are you so optimistic about Chan?
You have good analyse
I feel Chan
will be the champion
Come on
I want to bet more on him
Really?
2 million taels!
How generous!
Why don't you bet?
Why should I bet? He is my son
Shit, I miss one thing out of my calculation
What?
The blood
Here comes the Examiner
What? Isn't Cheng the examiner?
Please take a seat
Seng-ko-lin-ch'in?!
What's the problem?
He is the uncle of Po
Let's start
Start!
They should act 2 more marks for that
powerful shoot
I do think so
So's arrow isn't on the target,
Po won this section
Kidding? Damn you! They are cheating
The candidates please get on the horses
Mr Chiu
Take these with you, may be you will
find them useful
Here comes the 2nd round
They trick again
It's corrupt! May I give up the betting?
Chan won this race
Did you tear the ticket?
Not yet
Are you kidding?
Once again?!
OK, let's start from the very beginning,
I'll fight with single hand and leg
I won't take your advantage
How can you use such dirty stance?
Have you waken?
Bravo! He won
Have some tea
All the best!
What did you say?
It's English
There is no regulation stating that
weapon is not allowed
You fell down first, Po is the winner again
Damn you Cheng! You betrayed me!
I will beat you to death
if I see you again
Forget it, you won't see him anymore
Why?
I am now going to kill him!
I don't have 2 million to lose!
Just kidding
You shameless
Po is the Scholar of Martial Arts
I did win! Objection
What are you doing?
The dart is poisoned
He deserves it!
He was poisoned by his own dart
Well, my son will be the Scholar then
I am going to be rich!
Yes!
You… You…
Thank you, my ancestors!
You have good judgement
Sir, His Majesty wants to
appoint the title himself
OK
I want to take some statement from you as record
You won this time, who are you going to thank?
Miss Yushang!
Is Miss Yushang his mom?
Long life to you!
Please get up
Thank you
Who is the new Scholar of Martial Arts?
Your Majesty, So Chan from Canton
is the Scholar this year
Your Majesty, I am So Cha Ha Yee Chan
Your Majesty, I want to report something
Go ahead
I have found that. So is illiterate
So how could he answer the
question paper of strategy?
That should be tricks
Take the stationery out!
Yes
So Cha Ha Yee Chan, write your name now
Thank God, he knows how to write his name!
He can write his name!
I don't know how to write
That's shit!
Kill him now
No! No!
Your Majesty, I am the one who cheated
It's none of his business
Just chop me to death
No, you should kill me
Sorry dad
I don't know how to write my name
Stop, I have known it already
Your Majesty, I should be killed
- Kill me
- No, kill me
- Kill me.
- Your Majesty, you'd better kill me
Shit, are you giving order?
You two co-operated to cheat me
The Secretary for Justice,
announce the penalty for them
Come out! Hurry up
I am here!
He is the Secretary for Justice
So's family should be sentenced to death
But their ancestors achieved a lot
to Ching, they can be exampled
But, their fortune should be forfeited
Have you carried out any military duty?
I haven't gone back to my camp for
7 years, I haven't done anything
So, he didn't miscarry out any duty
So, the maximum penalty
is forfeiture of property only
What? Are you sure?
I am fair
I judge it from the Law Book
Can I add something?
Sure, since you are the Emperor
I want them to be beggars for the rest
of their lives
Why couldn't you find out
they cheated during the examination?
Luckily Chiu reported it to me on time
Chiu, you would be rewarded
I am wandering…
That's the spirit tablet of my dad,
do you want to take it too?
It's useless for you
How poor are we…
I am thinking of my better half…
Young master,
from now on,
you'd be hard working to learn how to write
But I can't sell the affection…
Professor
I will learn it
I regret that…
Master, I will take good care of little turtle
I am sorry
We haven't given birth to any baby of yours
It doesn't matter
It's all my fault
If I did better, you could have many babies
But I think Chan is enough for me
Why are you standing here? Go now
Master, we are leaving
We are leaving, master
Go, go now
We are free
I feel so happy
How happy are we!
Go in…
Hurry up…
Why are they so happy?
I am very happy
Please go in…
Welcome…
Damn sequestration, I wanna cry, my son
Hold it, don't lose our face
Keep on laughing
Son. Have you kept any money?
No, how about you?
I forgot that
Shit, damn sequestration!
Be merciful, please give money to us
Son, that guy is like dad
You mean the one who sings?
No, the one who pays
He is more disgusting than the one who sings
Not exactly, he is smart
Dad should be blamed
I always called you beggar
Now, it becomes true
What's wrong with you?
The emperor wants us to be beggars
Do you think we'd be beggars?
I am smart, I am keen in kung-fu fighting
Even the Gods won't let me be beggars
That's true
Am I like beggar?
No
Buy something to eat, you beggars
You treat us as beggars?
Damn you!
It's weird! Let's eat
Chan, since we have nothing to do
Let me take a seat, may be we can
have something to eat tonight
You are treating yourself a beggar?
Dad, don't worry
I need no begging for money
How can you get money if you don't beg?
Just ask someone to give us money
Pal, may I know your name?
Nau Tai Chung
Do you have money?
- Yes
- Just give it to me
OK
Thank you
Why should I give you money?
Why do you ask so many questions?
But I should know the reason
Anyway, you should pay it
No, let's fix it up first
Just give it to us, why are you asking so much?
Hands off
You mean robbing?
Robbery…
I am not robbing, I am begging
Begging? How dare are you, you beggar,
you are cheating me!
Don't you think I am stupid? I am smart, you know?
Hey, two days passed,
It's cold and I am hungry now
Have you had any idea?
I have a friend's girl-friend
who is living in Peking
She always admires you
Really?
Yes, if you are willing to date her
I think she will help us to go back to Canton
But, you have to sacrifice
Do you mean…
For our family, just as you said
I know it's very hard for you
Cut the crap, let's go and find her
I have arranged it
The one wearing red dress who stands
under the lantern, that's her
Ghost!
It's a benefit of you!
Why don't you go yourself?
Chan, I haven't tried this before
Be careful!
Don't worry
I'll take care of you
You want to earn money for shark-fins, right?
Right…
Get lost…
No show here
We just want to earn some money
to go back to Canton
Don't be that mean to us
It's the Royal instruction that,
the So's family'd be beggars for life
You two can only be beggars
I am carrying my duty only Men!
- Yes!
- Remove all the things
Yes
Help!
Master Chiu, it's hard for one to carry it
Ask more men to remove it
Yes
What do you want?
- No, we can't move it
- Let me do it
You want a fight, don't you?
Last time you can escape from Yee Hung Hostel
But you won't be that lucky this time
He is powerful!
I've to defeat him by one powerful strike
I can't give him another chance to counter attack
Chan…
Your legs and hands are all broken by me
You will be cripple for the rest of your life
You want to fight? Not now!
But, you can beg for money
Be a good beggar
Go, go away…
Don't panic, Chan, it's OK
Don't panic, you'll be alright… Chan!
Don't panic
I went to the examination hall
with my son,
don't you know who was the examiner?
He is Seng-ko-lin-ch'in, that bastard
He was the enemy of us!
About our story…
Let me stop here first, I want a smoke
It's better to smoke now
Yes, it's better
We let him go in
the Yee Hung Brothel
But he framed us in return
He tricked my son
during the examination
But, my son was really smart and great
To be the greatest Kung-fu fighter, invincible
Be the top
Can you do that?
Sure!
Well
Come back to me if you can do that
I think we should fix our wedding date first
Because being the scholar is too simple to me
Write your name at once
I don't know how to write
Chan, what's wrong with you?
Nightmare again?
Don't think so much!
Although you have taken 2 months' rest,
your legs and hands have not been
totally recovered
- Mr. Ha Yee
- Coming
I am going to beg for food
I will make the last herbal tea for you later
Dad, you go begging again?
This job should leave to me
You are the Scholar…
Chan, to be a beggar,
there is some lessons!
You can't just show your hand and beg for money
At least you should have a bowl,
that represents your class
Is it ridiculous?
Hurry up
I am coming
We can't beg for good if we are late!
Yes…
You not a master now.
Give me money please
Go, go, I won't give you money
Go, don't stop me from doing business
Chan, dad is leaving
Thank you…
Are you that mean?
Why don't you write it yourself?
You are off duty, so I just want to lend it
Don't you think I am idiot?
Dad!
What are you doing?
I am cold… I am cold… Chan
No, your body is as hot as fire
Are you sick?
I am not…
It's late
I have to search for food
Lie down, I will go this time
Are you go for begging?
I have my own way to get food
Take a rest now
I will take you to the doctor after
getting some money
You bastard, why don't you eat?
You should eat more so as to be strong!
Finish it
No, I am full
You should take all the food
OK, just forget it, let's go home
Come on, eat them all
Little kid!
What?
- May I… - No
Be merciful!
Be merciful to me please
My dad is dying!
Beggar, do you want the broken carbon?
Thank you
Can you give me some coins?
It's you!
No, you have mistaken
Sister, it's him
No, no
Sister, he is So Chan
Wait!
Miss, who are you looking for?
I am sorry, I have mistaken
Tracy, take some dumpling out
You have mistake, he is not So Chan
You are like my friend
Come to get some dumplings if you
get nothing to eat
We always have surplus
Dumpling
Take it
Thank you…
Sister,
he wouldn't be that poor if not were you
Dad, what are you doing?
I can't stand the hunger
So I bit the dumpling of the kid
I have dumpling, take it back
Could I pay you another head
if I chopped yours
Are you the Scholar?
Yes, are you the Scholar?
I was nearly the Scholar
He is the Scholar!
We should give him face
Thank you
Hold it
Are they going to treat me some food?
The dog's rice
Sir, I will let your dad go if you eat
the dog's rice now
What's the matter?
Come on
Chan, don't eat that
You can't face the others if you eat this
Let's forget about me
Sir, I was a general in Canton
So what?
Stop fighting
Stand properly
The Scholar eats the dog's food
Dad. It's quite delicious
Try some. Come on
It's delicious, isn't it?
Dad, look!
There is a slice of meat here
It's pock chop!
They are as hungry as dogs!
Enjoy the dog food!
Hurry, finish it
That's too delicious!
I want to save it for midnight snack
It's very clever of you!
You deserve to be beggars
The Scholar is eating dog's food
Come on, let's go and eat the man's food
Uncle So!
You are…
My dad was the Master of the
Beggar's Association
Why don't you join our Beggar's Association
Uncle Mok, isn't it a good idea?
Good
Isn't it the association for beggars?
Yes!
That's right, we are being beggars
It's wise to join the Beggars' Association
so as to be taken care
Chan… where is that fool going?
Where is Chan?
OK, we will join you!
Chan… Chan…
Yushang, good year!
Uncle Mok, happy new year!
This is for you
Thank you
One clothe is for you
and the other is for Chan
Thank you. Put it down first
Do you have any coins?
Yes!
- Give them to me, come on
- What for?
It's new year, you should receive red pocket
Come on, happy new year
Good year!
- Wish you ever beauty
- Thank you
Uncle Mok, we needn't give red
pocket to each other
How about Chan
Chan?
He is still sleeping
Don't wake him up
I will cook you some new year cake
Let me help you
How can he sleep on the 1st day of this year?
He is useless
Are you all here?
To fight against Chiu, we need a union of
the Beggar's Association
So we must choose a new master to
in-charge the association
Yushang…
To defeat the Lotus position of the three seniors
You should try your best
Uncle, I don't have faith to defeat them
Judging from my kung-fu now,
how can I defeat them and become the new master?
Take this Taiwan pill, after this,
your power will be improved
No, this is the only medicine to cure
your inner injury
How can I take this?
Don't worry,
you can ask my son to fight for you
He was a scholar of Martial Arts
before…
Before…
Look at him, he is so lazy,
he knows sleeping only
He is not even qualified to be beggar!
Don't be that frank, can you?
Don't shout that loudly, OK?
Chan, no matter how they despise you,
I have faith on you
Although you lost your power
With your background,
only you try hard,
you can achieve something
But I am now powerless,
I don't want to fight again
You have power!
Come on, beat me
See, that was powerful
Well, being a people…
Forget it, don't waste time
Why don't you let me sleep?
Why did you lock the door?
Enjoy sleeping
Son, I tried very hard to get this for you
Try hard to practise, be good
Why do you go up?
Even you want me to practise Kung-fu,
you should give me a waddy first
I am sorry, catch it
Before being appointed important task,
God will give you severe
training for soul and flesh.
Did you write it?
It's ugly, it's right to wipe it away
Hey, beggar?
Yes
Me too
Congratulation
- Are there anything to eat?
- No
Luckily, I have
See your look, it's a waste for you not to beg
None of your damn business
You are too lazy to be a beggar!
Your fellows despise you
I was always respected by others
But now, I am despised
Dislike from you,
no one respected me before
Listen to me. Don't go!
I remembered once in Canton
A fool paid my living, including hooking
What a weird man
Kid, I remembered you
Me too
Hey, hurry up
Repay my money, I am in urgent need
If I had money,
I wouldn't be beggar!
But, don't worry, you were my benefit or,
I will repay you one day
Thank you very much
But, you can't buy back what you lost
even you have money again
What did I lose?
Pride and faith
And your woman too
Who are you?
I am Hung Yat-sun, nicked name Old Bag Sun
I am the most senior one among the beggars
It's good to be beggar
You can do everything you want
You can do the same
Tell me, what do you want?
I will make your wish come true
I want to be human again
Don't you think you are not human like?
Not at all
So you have to be beggar now
Very good! Very good!
But I won't cheat you, from your head to toes
Every parts of you are beggar like
So what?
That means, you will be beggar for your life
I don't want to talk to you, I want a sleep first
Don't go, you can achieve in your profession
From my judgement,
you will be the king of beggars
King of beggars, what does that mean?
That is beggar
I won't care who you are,
I just want to stop the conversation
Please step aside, don't stop me from sleeping
Damn you!
No… I just want to sleep
with you
Idiot!
Kid, see you in the dream
Before the Buddha, the Disciples
returns to your position
To suppress the dragon and tight
So Chan, you enjoyed the prosperity of the world
And you tasted the bitter fruit of the world too
Now you regretted
On behalf of Master Hung
I appoint you to be the "Sleeping Disciple"
Now, I will teach you the
"Sleeping Disciple's Fist"!
Hope you can make good use of it Come on
Senior…
The bitter pasted
Long life to you…
Here comes the white Goat
My mother, give me power
To save the people!
Tomorrow the Emperor will go hunting
I will send him a pretty girl,
so as to get close to him
Yuen Ling, you should seduce him tomorrow
Yes
If we can kill the Emperor,
I can take over his reign
I will give you a share of wealth!
Long life to you
Senior!
Let's go back now
Let's go!
Senior!
- Let's chase them
- Stop!
The Emperor is setting off soon
You killed woman…
You should replace her to be
a gift to the Emperor!
No one dares come up to fight for the leadership?
Ask Mok to give us the "Dog Hitting Waddy"!
Where have they been?
I don't know,
I saw them chat,
then they went away
Are there any affair between them?
Now, we are going to choose the new leader
Uncle Mok…
I am scared,
I think you won't come back
- How is it?
- Where is sister?
Your sister is caught by Chiu
We'd find someone to compete for the leadership
Who should go?
I'll do it
Uncle Mok
Why don't you let me try?
Chan,
you are not qualified, come down
Since you don't have a good candidate,
I'll give you some advantage
Chan, it's not a game
You will be killed, come down
It doesn't matter, I have forgotten
my life already
Bullshit, throw him to death
Well, I will make your wish come true
What is he doing?
Sleeping
Isn't this stance…
Uncle Sun's "Sleeping Disciple's Fists'?
Set the position!
Is it dawn?
I am sorry!
I won
What is the use for defeating us?
You don't know how to use the
"Dog Hitting Waddy".
You are not qualified to be the leader of us
"Dog Hitting Waddy"?
It's for hitting dogs
I do know how to use this waddy!
But it's dislike from the standard stances!
It's quite powerful!
He broke the waddy!
He broke the treasure of our Association,
let's kill him!
I am Master Hung, who dares go against me?
I set the rules of the association
Any student who defeated the Lotus Position
could be the leader
Have you all forgotten?
We becomes the biggest association
because of being united
I left you the "Dog Hitting Waddy",
is just for memory
The waddy is meaningless
But you fools take this as treasure
And fight among yourselves for this damn waddy!
In these five years, you have had no
leader, don't you feel shy?
So Chan broke the waddy,
so you won't fight for this anymore
He is correct to do so
This youngster is so junior,
but he is a genius, a smart ass
He is being taught by my disciple Hung Yat Sun
Who doesn't respect him is going against me too
You should respect him,
your new leader, and you'd love him,
whole-heartedly, to care much for him,
maybe, treat him dinner
Then, although I am in heaven,
I will bless all of you, all the best
Isn't it true?
You'd better trust it
Master Hung's soul talked to us,
we are blessed
They are easily to be cheated,
I am really a genius!
We'll have better living
What happened?
Let's greet the new Master
Bravo…
Uncle Mok, my son is really great!
I can't guess you have learnt the
"Sleeping Disciple's Fists"?!
From now on, you are the new leader of us
This is the book of "Dragon Suppressing Stances"
And, I will give you the Taiwan Pill
Hope you will be a good leader
I just want to save Yushang as soon as possible
Yushang didn't make a wrong choice
Bravo! Bravo!
Uncle Mok, how are you?
Uncle Mok!
Uncle Mok…
Chan,
do you understand everything written in this book?
Don't think that I am so foolish
After getting the help of Taiwan Pill
My initial power is increased
I can control the 17th stances
But the last stance,
there is no picture or description of it
I can't understand at all
But Uncle Mok is dead, what'll we do now?
Just go ahead
No matter how, I have to save Yushang first
Check whether the camp is ready or not?
Yes!
Chiu,
why do you bring this woman here?
I know the Emperor loves pretty woman
So I want to send him this gift
And I want to meet him too
There is no order from the Emperor
Men, come and take this woman to the camp
Yes
Go!
Sir, you look great!
I think you should go back
to your own position
Yes
Your Majesty,
Officer Chiu brings this woman to you
Woman?
Chiu knows my hobby!
I want to take a bath first, bring her to me later
Yes
This bastard wants to see the Emperor,
if I let him see His Majesty oftenly,
my post will be taken away
Men
Sir
- Check what had happened
- Yes
Sir, there are many people coming from the forest
Who are they?
I don't know!
Release the alarm smoke
Be alert
Yes
There is smoke ahead, let's get armed
Damn you beggars
So Chan, what are you doing?
Nothing, I just want to beg for money
Shit, do you want to be killed
It's you who will be killed
Chiu wants to raise a rebel,
he is going to assassinate the king
You fat-headed
Who do you think you are?
How dare you frame the courtier?
I will kill you if you step forward
Chan, how can we fight with them?
- Senior
- Yes
Where are the rest of our men?
They are coming
We have no time,
you stay here to wait for the others
I will go first
I will follow
Be serious
Master, don't worry
Am I going to die?
Say something lucky, OK?
Sure! Happy birthday to you…
Happy birthday to you…
That's enough
I haven't finished
- Go on after I left
- Sure
There is smoke ahead,
someone must have alarmed them
- Get ready the Unicorn Smoke
- Yes
Attack the main camp
Rebel! Help!
They should be killed
The one who didn't kill you should be killed
Shit, the poisoned smoke
is blowing to the Royal camp
No, the wind direction changed
Yes, wait for me
If the beggars don't retreat now,
we will kill with no mercy
Have a look
The Unicorn Smoke of the Tin Li Sect
Be calm, urine is the antidote to the poison
Come and piss
How about me?
Don't worry, I can give you some urine
Come on, hold it
Rush in!
How is the situation?
Thanks for Your Majesty's luck,
the wind direction changed
The smoke is going to the other direction
How about our armies?
They are all dead
Take me the sword
Don't… don't!
Get lost! Get lost!
Your Majesty, it's dangerous, don't go!
Get lost, don't you want
to wait for death, get lost
You are ordered to get away
You can't go!
Protect me
Chan?
Yushang
How did you get here?
It's a long story
We left our base last night
We reached the Great Wall
this morning
We stayed one hour for lunch
I pissed once
- Really?
- Yes
Then I want to eat a sweet potato
But only dumpling left
You know, I don't like eating dumpling
I am late to save you, please forgive me
To protect the Emperor
Yes
You betrayer!
Catch him
Your Majesty
You bastard, give your kingdom to me
What are you telling him?
It's you
Yes, I am Beggar So
Why don't you sleep in your hut?
Well, I am a little bit sleepy
"Sleeping Disciple"?
Yes. Look at you, you are like beggar too
Are you interested to join us?
I can't guess you could recover!
Yes, it's all because of you
Did you generate all your force? I didn't
Fool, only the "Dragon Suppressing
Stances" scare me
I won't give a damn to any other stances
"Dragon Suppress Stances"
"Dragon in the sky"
"Dragon swings its tail"
"Dragon steals the heart"
Dragon swims, dragon in the field,
dragon dances…
Dragon's descendant,
dragon's wish…
Dragon's spirit, dragon's couple
Finished
You can't finish the last stance,
you can defeat me
after learning the 18th stance
But you have no chance
Chan!
I've got it. Just mix the 17 stances,
it's the 18th stance then
I am too smart!
The 18 stance, "It's a regret to kill the Dragon"!
Chan, are you alright?
See, don't you think I am alright?
Your post is really smart
But your look is awful!
Idiot, I am fine
I can marry tonight
You are great!
Chan! Are you okay?
Where is Chiu?
He is around
Around?
He became ash
Damn it!
Master
Chiu's fellows are all caught by us
Thank you, buddies
Yushang
We have an agreement, do you remember?
Yes, be the top of all
Invincible
But, I can't be the Scholar
But I don't like Scholar at all
I love beggar
You first, I will go after you
Seng-ko-lin-ch'in,
you are really a fool
You bring a thief to harm me
Now, you are titled to be a beggar
You have potential to be beggar
Report duty in the temple tomorrow
If there anyone bullies you,
just tell them my name
Thank you, thank you master
So Chan, what do you want as reward?
Don't you have anything to tell me?
Nothing special, let's go
Pick me up
Mister
So!
Put me down
Although you have saved me,
if you don't respect me, I will kill you
If so, you needn't squat and talk to me
Don't move, it'll attract their attention
Actually we have no relation,
we have nothing to chat
You have billions of fellows
Your force makes me worry
The number of fellow doesn't depend on me,
but you
What?
If you are great, making the
society peace and wealthy,
no one wishes to be beggar, right?
- It's reasonable
- Be smart
But,
give me some face
Yes
Long life…
- …to Your Majesty
- Get up
Pal, do you know me?
Of course! You beggar
You beg with your girl, you think I'll
give you money out of mercy?
Yes, please give me money
No mercy, go away
No, you should pay me
It's a must, pal
A must? Kidding?
It's true, be quick
It's bad luck to meet you
Stop
What?
See my family? Give more
How much?
Not less than a thousand, got me?
Say thank you now
Thank you, uncle
Hurry up
Follow me… go…