Young master, we are ready
What's a hard job for you,
young master
The towel, young master
What did he write?
His name!
Great! Young master knows how to
write his name!
Yes!
Damn!
Nice calligraphy
Get lost
Nice calligraphy!
So Cha Ha Yee Chan!
It's reversed, Master
Chan Yee Ha Cha So
Good boy, but, don't be proud!
Got me?
Dad, since the first
emperor of the Ching Dynasty,
our family
has been illiterate
But not, my son,
that's your grandson,
he knows how to write his name!
Dad, it's very great!
He knows writing now,
he will be scholar one day
Now, he knows how to write his name,
he will have a son later
Young master,
you should try hard to learn
Chan, I think,
we should mount it
OK
Professor, show it in
some obvious places
By the way, one minute,
why don't you carry it with traditional
decoration in the street?
What?
Let's go!
Chan, come and sit…
I am so pleased that you are that hard
working and filial
Listen to me, I am notorious of being
a spendthrift
My fortune is almost used up
If I die one day,
you should depend on yourself
I used to depend on myself
The cheques worth 100,000 taels!
Don't be an extravagant spender
Give me the imported hat
Where are you going?
Chan!
I am having a grand
birthday party tonight
How old are you?
25 years old. Come earlier
But you should dress up first
You are like beggar!
How can a beggar be that rich?!
I do want to be a rich beggar!
That fat-headed…
Come over here
What's the matter?
The invitation card
of my son is great!
If I hold a birthday party in future,
I want a better invitation card!
Your Majesty, what do you think about
the Cantonese Opera?
For sure, it can't compete
with Peking Opera!
But, I appreciate
to view this
Money…
Tips. Tips…
Happy birthday to you, Mr So
I am homeless and sick…
I am poor, I am damn poor!
Please give me some money
Kidding? Damn you beggar!
How can you beg here?
Go to hell!
Give him tips
Yes, young master
Are you kidding?
How can you give him tips?
A beggar is a man too
Everyone can come here
if he has money
Your living,
including the expenditure for hooking,
I will pay for you!
You pay it?
So what?
Nothing!
Please follow me
Come into my room…
Mr So!
Hello…
How are you, Madam Pimp?
It's very bad of
you to call me that!
Just be frank, why not?
You should be frank!
Your hat is like
the mourning uniform!
Has your dad passed away?
I feel happy to talk in this way
Mr Chiu, you helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang,
the emperor will
give you an award for this
I'll appreciate it if you
speak something nice in front of
the emperor
Please have the towel
Mr So has come.
Congratulations!
This way…
Mr So, today is your big day,
you must be very happy!
We have some new girls,
you must be satisfied with them
What are they?
Goldfish, or cooked fish?
What does that mean?
You idiot! Goldfish is
for watching only
Cooked fish can be eaten
Cooked fish of course
You, cooked fishes, why don't you
come and serve Mr So?
Mr So, you are the
superior master today.
What kind of woman do you want?
Just tell me.
I won't mind,
every woman is just the same
Nothing special
Mr So, what's the matter?
I am attacked.
What? Who dared so?
I will hit that
bastard's mouth for you.
She didn't use her mouth
She used her eyes
Tempting, and I smell blood.
I haven't seen such eyesight before
Who is she?
Miss Yushang comes to be part-time
hooker only
Is Mr Chiu interested to sleep with her?
You should ask His Majesty first
How is it? Your Majesty?
We are friends,
just go ahead if you want!
Mr Chiu, help yourself
Thank you then
The room service, please
Yushang, come and greet Mr Chiu
Sister, he is the one we want.
He killed dad.
I know, stay calm.
Let's go.
May I be excused?
Mr Chiu, Miss Yushang has arrived.
How are you, Mr Chiu?
A pretty woman!
Mr Chiu, about tonight…
$100,000
if Miss Yushang sleeps with our
young master tonight…
You are not welcome
I am sorry, I am damn sorry
Don't you have any objection?
Let me say something fair
If any of you can offer
more than $100,000
Yushang will sleep with whom
Don't quarrel because of such
small amount,
isn't it right?
Pal, you are a big spender
The cheque is too simple to me
I have a pearl which is granted by the
Royal family, it's invaluable!
I love the pearl more
Mr Chiu, I will wait
for you in my room
Does the pearl worth $100,000?
Don't you think that's
too little for you?
I love money too
But, I don't like you
You are frank!
I love it very much
Mr So…
It doesn't matter,
I think, my hat doesn't match me
Yushang doesn't like me,
I deserve it
I am glad you understand this
Don't worry,
I have many pretty girls here
I trust your arrangement
None of my business
How bold are you?
Mantis Fist?
It seems to be powerful
Music!
Keep this
See my Crane's Fists!
The Tiger's Claws!
How can a mantis fight with a tiger?
I know Tiger Claws
and Crane's Fists too!
Well, try me, mantis!
Bravo…
Your Tiger's Claws are defeated
Actually it's not Tiger's Claws,
it's beggar's fists!
That's why it's too weak
You move fast!
It seems to be powerful…
Kid, you don't know how
the wind blows
The general of
Canton has arrived
Get lost…
Who dares bully my son,
let me teach him a lesson
Master
Don't panic, Chan who bullied you?
It's me who bullied others
What? You bullied others?
How much does he have?
Is he qualified to be bullied by you?
Master, they are the ones
Who are they?
Just take a look
The King of Iron Hat?
Send the gift
Chan
They send you so valuable a present,
you'd stop bullying them
Come on, give tips to the girls here
Master
King of Iron Hat, Seng-ko-lin-ch'in,
is written on the medal
How dare you seize the medal
of His Majesty?
Cuff him
Hold it, according to the Ching's law,
Courtier is not allowed hooking
Now, you are in the brothel
Do you know you have committed
the laws of Ching?
How about you?
- You mean me?
- Yes!
That's right, I come…
- to arrest…
- You!
- Him!
- Arrest him!
I am the general of Canton,
so I should arrest
those bad people
By the way…
What else? Go ahead
Today is the birthday of
the ex-Empress Dowager
So your crime is doubled
It may cause capital punishment
Kill him…
According to the Ching laws,
anyone without a tail should be killed
So you…
Do you want to see my hair?
You can see as much as you want!
Fat-headed
Cut the crap, just kill him
OK, it's finished
General So, let's play happily together,
so forget it
I haven't played!
Your Majesty,
a rascal has ruined
the atmosphere here,
I should be blamed
for poor arrangement
None of your business
Let's go
Master, you can't fool this guy
OK, go
Just forget the trouble
Young master, your hat
He is great!
Uncle Mok, the dishes
are all poisoned
Chiu assassinated our Master
and some generals of
the Taiping Reign
And he framed us, the Beggars Association,
to be the assassins
Thus made us
being despised by the world
Saying that we became the dogs
of the government
I should ask him to pay for it
His initial power is harmful
Don't take action
until he is trapped
Because we can't defeat him even
if we group together
I will try my best to seduce
him to the bed
Senior, somebody is coming
Get ready…
Miss Yushang, we meet again.
Why do you come here?
Where is Mister Chiu?
The pearl of Mr. Chiu is broken
by Mr. So and become pearl powder
I have drunk it.
Don't judge Mr. So from his hair,
he is really romantic and funny.
But…
Stop, I have taken his money,
100,000 taels, you know?
I won't give it back.
About the personality of Mr. So…
Cut the crap, pimp!
Leave here first.
Yes, you are right.
Miss Seven…
Just accept this.
Who is this guy?
I don't know
Miss, first of all, I have a good
news for you
I love you
To me, this is bad news
I know you will reply like this
Cut the crap
I wish to pay you 100 pearls
for your company tonight
I don't want to talk to you
Please get out
I haven't chosen a wrong one
OK, I will drink this wine first
No…
It surprised me
Miss
Hands off!
You know Kung-fu?
No, I don't know Kung-fu at all
I beg you, stop bothering me
I won't accompany you
Yushang, no one treats
me like this
I have found that
I am in love with you
What?
I have been in love with you
Are you kidding?
I am not kidding,
I decided to marry you
Are you nuts?
Kidding?
Is there anyone hiding here?
That's good, I want a witness
Witness?
Yes, I swear in front of your sword
I do want to marry Miss Yushang
as my wife, I am sincere
If I cheat,
I will be killed by thunder
Sister, I feel excited for you
Hey
Don't you know it's not that easy
to be my husband?
How can I be your husband?
I want him to be the superior
Kung-fu master
Be the top of all
Can you do that?
Let me think for one second
I can do it
OK
Do it first and then look for me
Well, I think we should fix a date
for our wedding
Because this is too easy for me
to be the Kung-fu scholar!
OK, but you'd give me some time
to consider it.
No problem, I will wait for your answer
outside the garden
I won't leave until seeing you
Crazy!
We come for the Beggars Association,
those unrelated persons leave at once
Sir, the timing is right
The road is safe now, please go
Good, very good
Let's go!
Shit, we are late
That Manchurian should be blamed
Sister…
What's the matter?
The idiot is still there
Let's kill him
Forget it,
he doesn't mean to bother us
Let him go
Are you fond of him?
What did you say?
I won't fall in love with anybody
until Chiu is killed
Especially him
Chiu is good at Kung-fu
Mok said, we can't defeat him unless
using the “Dragon Killing Palms”
So, I can never marry!
Let's go, if you want to marry
What evil are you?
How dare you scare me?
Mr So, it's me!
You are the pimp?!
Yes!
You have a flat figure,
where are your busts?
It's early in the morning,
they haven't woken up yet
It's lucky of you
for not being killed
Don't go around if you haven't
made up yet
I won't do it again
Stop waiting for Miss Yushang,
she left
What?
Where is she going?
She… she is going to Peking
Peking?
Men should contribute to the country
Where should I put my pigtail?
Swing and swing…
I pull it and play it…
Dad!
I decided to join the examination for the
scholar of Martial Arts
Chan
I have been longing for this word
for 25 years
For the family of us, you should do that
Don't misunderstand it,
I do it not for no one
But for a woman
What a hero!
For a girl, you want to be the scholar
of Martial Arts!
Who is that girl?
The hooker of Yee Hung Brothel,
Miss Yushang
For a hooker?
What's wrong with it?
You have different taste,
you are great!
I am admiring you!
I will accompany you to Peking
2, 3, 4, 5, 6
I am coming
Young master is going for the examination,
let's move to Peking too
Stop chasing,
we won't take the hens with us
Be careful!
If you break my stuff,
I will teach you a good lesson
Be careful!
Good morning dad
Good morning
You want to move
everything to Peking?
Sure
Please leave me a cloth
You are only a kid,
you don't need this
But I am not small
Are you bigger than mine?
You despise me!
Mine will be bigger
than yours one day
Let's find something,
say trousers to cover it
I don't want to see it
Why are you standing here for?
Why don't you remove it?
It's a hard job to remove
such a big house!
Please, work hard men!
Ready, 1, 2, 3, push!
Push!
Be careful!
Tie it well…
Master, do you want to
move the tree too?
Sure,
or how can I eat Lychee in Peking?
Push it over…
Be careful
Take care of my Lychee,
you fathead!
Chiu helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang in Kwangsi
So I bring him here
to greet Your Majesty
Fine, I am now appointing you to be
the Deputy Secretary
Hope you will serve our Ching Dynasty
whole-heartedly
Thank you, Your Majesty
Your Majesty, Mr Chiu is a magician
Why don't you ask him to
show you something?
Magic?
Mr Chiu, then show me your magic
Yes, Your Majesty
There is nothing surprising, go
Yes
I am sorry for scaring you
If this girl is real,
that's fantastic!
Hurry up!
What's the matter?
Come on, go in
Hide in here
Get ready, young master
Come on
Freeze, don't move
Sweet smell, are you Piu Hung?
You are great!
I love it.
Closer
So big!
You must be Small!
You are bad, how can
you say that to me?
You are big!
What? Pregnant woman?
You can't cheat me
You are Dad
How bad are you,
how can you guess that?
Good boy
I wanted to trick you actually,
you are really smart.
Young master has to join
the examination tomorrow,
stop playing
Get out…
Chan, have you prepared
for your examination?
What should I prepare?
I must win, don't you know that?
Yes I do!
I have faith in you from seeing
your behaviour!
Chan, this is Uncle Cheng
He will be the examiner
Say hello to Uncle Cheng
How are you, Uncle Cheng?
See
Doesn't he seem to be the winner?
It depends on the fate
Cheng, I've asked someone
to finish the papers
which you gave me
Will the questions be changed?
Don't worry about
the question paper
But about the test
of arrows shooting,
riding, boxing and weapons…
He should try his best
Don't worry
My son is keen in martial arts
So, can I deduct some from the payment
of 2 million taels?
We are friends,
but that is business
Let the Horse teams
be the pioneer
The arrows teams go sideways,
the gunmen stay back
The candidates come in
I can't lift it
I don't want to waste my force
Shameless? Damn you!
Oh, 10 marks
The final race now starts
The candidates,
Po Ye Tat Tor from Mongolia
Bravo…
And So Cha Ha Yee
Chan from Canton
Last call
So, one to ten
Po, one to one
Are you kidding, how can the betting rates
differ so much?
One to ten for Chan? Kidding?
Why don't you have
faith in Chan?
That is, Chan defaulted
in weight lifting
Look, Po entered the final race
with full marks, it differs
It's an examination of the Scholar
of Martial Arts, not king of coolie
It's meaningless to be the champion
of weight lifting
You shouldn't put it that way
What?
He is smart
I've studied this
race for a long time
I feel strange about the rate too
Po is smart and strong
But see the sweat of his neck
I think it's because
he is getting tired
Really?
But this So
What do you think?
He has been disappointing
the audience
But he has achieved very hard
What?
He tried very hard
So I want to bet on him
How much do you want to bet?
800,000 taels
Why not 2 million taels?
What? Why are you so optimistic
about Chan?
You have good analysis
I feel Chan
will be the champion
Come on
I want to bet more on him
Really?
2 million taels!
How generous!
Why don't you bet?
Why should I bet?
He is my son
Shit, I miss one thing out
of my calculation
What?
The blood
Here comes the Examiner
What? Isn't Cheng the examiner?
Please take a seat
Seng-ko-lin-ch'in?!
What's the problem?
He is the uncle of Po
Let's start
Start!
Bravo…
They should add 2 more marks for that
powerful shot
I do think so
So's arrow isn't on the target,
Po won this section
Kidding? Damn you!
They are cheating
The candidates please
get on the horses
Mr Chiu
Take these with you, maybe you will
find them useful
Here comes the 2nd round
They trick again.
It's corrupt!
May I give up the betting?
Chan won this race
Did you tear the ticket?
Not yet
Are you kidding?
Once again?!
OK, let's start from the very beginning,
I'll fight with a single hand and leg
I won't take your advantage
How can you use
such a dirty stance?
Have you woken?
Bravo! He won
Have some tea
All the best!
What did
you say?
It's English
There is no regulation stating that
weapons are not allowed
You fell down first,
Po is the winner again
Damn you Cheng!
You betrayed me!
I will beat you to death
if I see you again
Forget it, you won't
see him anymore
Why?
I am now going to kill him!
I don't have 2 million to lose!
Just kidding
You shameless
Po is the Scholar of Martial Arts
I did win! Objection
What are you doing?
The dart is poisoned
He deserves it!
He was poisoned by his own dart
Well, my son will
be the Scholar then
I am going to be rich!
Yes!
Thank you, my ancestors!
You have good judgement
Sir, His Majesty wants to appoint
the title himself
I want to take some statements
from you as record
You won this time, who are you
going to thank?
Miss Yushang!
Is Miss Yushang your mom?
Long life to you!
Please get up
Thank you
Who is the new Scholar
of Martial Arts?
Your Majesty, So Chan from Canton
is the Scholar this year
Your Majesty,
I am So Cha Ha Yee Chan
I want to report something
Go ahead
I have found that
So is illiterate
So how could he answer the
question paper of strategy?
That should be tricks
Take the stationery out!
Yes
So Cha Ha Yee Chan,
write your name now
Thank God, he knows how to
write his name!
He can write his name!
I don't know how to write
That's shit!
Kill him now
No! No!
Your Majesty,
I am the one who cheated
It's none of his business
Just chop me to death
No, you should kill me
Sorry dad
I don't know how to write my name
Stop, I have known it already
Your Majesty, I should be killed
Kill me
No, kill me
Your Majesty, you'd better kill me
Shit, are you giving order?
You two cooperated to cheat me
The Secretary for Justice,
announce the penalty for them
Come out! Hurry up
I am here!
He is the Secretary for Justice
So's family should be
sentenced to death
But their ancestors achieved a lot
to Ching, they can be exempted
But, their fortune should be forfeited
Have you carried out any military duty?
I haven't gone back to my camp for
7 years, I haven't done anything
So, he didn't miscarry any duty
So, the maximum penalty
is forfeiture of property only
What? Are you sure?
I am fair
I judge it from the Law Book
Can I add something?
Sure, since you are the Emperor
I want them to be beggars for the rest
of their lives
Why couldn't you find out they cheated during the examination?
Luckily Chiu reported
it to me on time
Chiu, you would be rewarded
I am wandering…
That's the spirit tablet of my dad,
do you want to take it too?
It's useless for you
How poor are we…
I am thinking of my better half…
Young master,
from now on,
you'd be hard working to learn
how to write
But I can't sell the affection…
Professor
I will learn it
I regret that…
Master, I will take good care of
Little Turtle
I am sorry
We haven't given birth to any
baby of yours
It doesn't matter
It's all my fault
If I did better,
you could have many babies
But I think
Chan is enough for me
Why are you standing here?
Go now
Master, we are leaving
We are leaving, master
Go, go now
We are free
I feel so happy
How happy are we!
Go in…
Hurry up…
How is it?
Why are they so happy?
What happened?
I am very happy
Please go in…
Welcome…
Damn sequestration,
I wanna cry, my son
Hold it, don't lose our face
Keep on laughing
Son
Have you kept any money?
No, how about you?
I forgot that
Shit, damn sequestration!
Be merciful,
please give money to us
Son, that guy is like dad
You mean the one who sings?
No, the one who pays
He is more disgusting
than the one who sings
Not exactly, he is smart
Dad should be blamed
I always called you beggar
Now, it becomes true
What's wrong with you?
The emperor wants
us to be beggars
Do you think we'd be beggars?
I am smart, I am keen
in kung-fu fighting
Even the Gods won't
let me be beggars
That's true
Am I like beggar?
No
Buy something to eat, you beggars
You treat us as beggars?
Damn you!
It's weird! Let's eat
Chan, since we have
nothing to do
Let me take a seat,
maybe we can have something
to eat tonight
You are treating
yourself a beggar?
Dad, don't worry
I need no begging for money
How can you get money
if you don't beg?
Just ask someone
to give us money
Pal, may I know your name?
Nau Tai Chung
Do you have money?
Yes
Just give it to me
OK
Thank you
Why should I give you money?
Why do you ask so many questions?
But I should know the reason
Anyway, you should pay it
No, let's fix it up first
Just give it to us, why are you
asking so much?
Hands off
You mean robbing?
Robbery…
I am not robbing, I am begging
Begging? How dare you, you beggar,
you are cheating me!
Don't you think I am stupid?
I am smart, you know?
Hey, two days passed,
It's cold and I am hungry now
Have you had any ideas?
I have a friend's girlfriend
who is living in Peking
She always admires you
Really?
Yes, if you are
willing to date her
I think she will help us to
go back to Canton
But, you have to sacrifice
Do you mean…
For our family,
just as you said
I know it's very hard for you
Cut the crap,
let's go and find her
I have arranged it
The one wearing the red dress who stands
under the lantern, that's her
Ghost!
It's a benefit for you!
Why don't you go yourself?
Chan, I haven't tried this before
Be careful!
Don't worry
I'll take care of you
You want to earn money for
shark-fins, right?
Right…
Get lost…
No show here
We just want to earn some money
to go back to Canton
Don't be that mean to us
It's the Royal instruction that
the So's family'd
be beggars for life
You two can only be beggars
I am carrying my duty only.
Men!
Yes!
Remove all the things
Yes
Help!
Master Chiu, it's hard
for one to carry it
Ask more men to remove it
Yes
What do you want?
No, we can't move it
Let me do it
You want a fight, don't you?
Last time you could escape from
Yee Hung Hostel
But you won't be
that lucky this time
He is powerful!
I've got to defeat him
by one powerful strike
I can't give him another chance
to counterattack
Chan…
Your legs and hands
are all broken by me
You will be a cripple for the
rest of your life
You want to fight? Not now!
But, you can beg for money
Be a good beggar
Go, go away…
Don't panic, Chan, it's OK
Don't panic, you'll be
all right… Chan!
I went to the examination hall
with my son,
don't you know who
was the examiner?
He is Seng-ko-lin-ch'in,
that bastard.
He was the enemy of us!
About our story…
Let me stop here first,
I want a smoke.
It's better to smoke now.
Yes, it's better.
We let him go in
the Yee Hung Brothel.
But he framed us in return.
He tricked my son
during the examination.
But, my son was really
smart and great
He finally won the race
To be the greatest Kung-fu
fighter, invincible
Be the top
Can you do that?
Sure!
Well
Come back to me
if you can do that
I think we should fix our
wedding date first
Because being the scholar is
too simple to me
Write your name at once
I don't know how to write
Chan, what's wrong with you?
Nightmare again?
Don't think so much!
Although you have taken
2 months' rest,
your legs and hands have not been
totally recovered.
Coming
I am going to beg for food
I will make the last herbal tea
for you later
Dad, you go begging again?
This job should be left to me
You are the Scholar…
Chan, to be a beggar,
there are some lessons!
You can't just show your hand
and beg for money
At least you should have a bowl,
that represents your class
Is it ridiculous?
Hurry up
I am coming
We can't beg for good
if we are late!
Yes…
Give me money, please
Go, go, I won't give you money
Go, don't stop me
from doing business
Chan, dad is leaving
Thank you…
Are you that mean?
Why don't you write it yourself?
You are off duty, so I just
want to lend it.
Don't you think I am an idiot?
Dad!
What are you doing?
I am cold… I am cold… Chan
No, your body is as hot as fire
Are you sick?
I am not…
It's late
I have to search for food
Lie down, I will go this time
Are you going for begging?
I have my own way to get food
Take a rest now
I will take you to the doctor after
getting some money
You bastard, why don't you eat?
You should eat more so as
to be strong!
Finish it
No, I am full
You should take all the food
OK, just forget it,
let's go home
Come on, eat them all
Little kid!
What?
May I…
No
Be merciful!
Be merciful to me, please
My dad is dying!
Beggar, do you want
the broken carbon?
Thank you
Can you give me some coins?
It's you!
No, you are mistaken
Sister, it's him
No, no
Sister, he is So Chan
Wait!
Miss, who are you looking for?
I am sorry, I have mistaken.
Tracy, take some dumplings out
You have mistaken,
he is not So Chan
You are like my friend
Come to get some dumplings if you
get nothing to eat
We always have surplus
Dumplings
Take it
Thank you…
Sister, he wouldn't
be that poor
if it were not for you
Dad, what are you doing?
I can't stand the hunger.
So I bit the dumpling of the kid.
I have dumpling, take it back.
Could I pay you another head
if I chopped yours?
Are you the Scholar?
Yes, are you the Scholar?
I was nearly the Scholar
He is the Scholar!
We should give him face
Thank you
Hold it
Are they going to treat me
some food?
The dog's rice
Sir, I will let your dad go if you eat
the dog's rice now
What's the matter?
Come on
Chan, don't eat that
You can't face the
others if you eat this
Let's forget about me
Sir, I was a general in Canton
So what?
Stop fighting
Stand properly
The Scholar eats the dog's food
It's quite delicious
Try some. Come on
It's delicious, isn't it?
Dad, look!
There is a slice of meat here
It's pork chop!
They are as hungry as dogs!
Enjoy the dog food!
Hurry, finish it
That's too delicious!
I want to save it
for a midnight snack
It's very clever of you!
You deserve to be beggars
The Scholar is eating dog food
Come on, let's go and
eat the man's food
Uncle So!
You are…
My dad was the Master of the
Beggars' Association
Why don't you join our Beggars'
Association
Uncle Mok, isn't it a good idea?
Good
Isn't it the association
for beggars?
Yes!
That's right,
we are being beggars
It's wise to join the Beggars' Association
so as to be taken care of
Chan…
where is that fool going?
Where is Chan?
OK, we will join you!
Chan… Chan…
Yushang, good year!
Uncle Mok, happy new year!
This is for you
Thank you
One cloth is for you
and the other is for Chan
Thank you. Put it down first
Do you have any coins?
Yes!
Give them to me, come on
What for?
It's new year,
you should receive red pocket
Come on, happy new year
Good year!
Wish you ever beauty
Thank you…
Uncle Mok, we needn't give red
pockets to each other
How about Chan
Chan?
He is still sleeping
Don't wake him up
I will cook you some new year cakes
Let me help you
How can he sleep on the
1st day of this year?
He is useless
Are you all here?
To fight against Chiu, we need a union of
the Beggars' Association
So we must choose a new master to
in-charge the association
Yushang…
To defeat the Lotus position
of the three seniors
You should try your best
Uncle, I don't have
faith in defeating them
Judging from my kung-fu now,
how can I defeat them and become
the new master?
Take this Taiwan pill, after this,
your power will be improved
No, this is the only medicine to cure
your inner injury
How can I take this?
Don't worry,
you can ask my
son to fight for you
He was a scholar
of Martial Arts before…
Before…
Look at him, he is so lazy,
he knows sleeping only
He is not even
qualified to be a beggar!
Don't be that frank, can you?
Don't shout that loudly, OK?
Chan, no matter
how they despise you,
I have faith in you
Although you lost your power
With your background,
only if you try hard,
you can achieve something.
But I am now powerless,
I don't want to fight again
You have power!
Come on, beat me
See, that was powerful
Well, being a people…
Forget it, don't waste time
Why don't you let me sleep?
Why did you lock the door?
Enjoy sleeping
Son,
I tried very hard
to get this for you
Try hard to practise, be good
Why do you go up?
Even you want me
to practise Kung-fu,
you should give me a waddy first
I am sorry, catch it
Before being appointed an
important task,
God will give you severe
training for soul and flesh.
Did you write it?
It's ugly, it's right
to wipe it away.
Hey, beggar?
Yes
Me too
Congratulations
Is there anything to eat?
No
Luckily, I have
See your look,
it's a waste
for you not to beg
None of your damn business
You are too lazy to be a beggar!
Your fellows despise you
I was always respected by others
But now, I am despised
Dislike from you,
no one respected me before
Listen to me. Don't go!
I remembered once in Canton
A fool paid my living,
including hooking
What a weird man
Kid, I remembered you
Me too
Hey, hurry up
Repay my money,
I am in urgent need
If I had money,
I wouldn't be a beggar!
But, don't worry,
you were my benefactor,
I will repay you one day
Thank you very much
But, you can't buy
back what you lost
even if you have money again
What did I lose?
Pride and faith
And your woman too
What are you?
I am Hung Yat-sun,
nicknamed Old Bag Sun
I am the most senior
one among the beggars
It's good to be a beggar
You can do everything you want
You can do the same
Tell me, what do you want?
I will make your wish come true
I want to be human again
Don't you think you
are not human-like?
Not at all
So you have to be a beggar now
Very good! Very good!
But I won't cheat you,
from your head to toes
Every part of you is beggar-like
So what?
That means, you will be a beggar
for your life
I don't want to talk to you,
I want to sleep first
Don't go, you can achieve
in your profession
From my judgement,
you will be the King of Beggars
King of Beggars,
what does that mean?
That is beggar
I won't care who you are,
I just want to stop the conversation.
Please step aside,
don't stop me from sleeping.
Damn you!
No… I just want to sleep with you.
Idiot!
Kid, see you in the dream
Before the Buddha, the Disciples
return to your position
To suppress the dragon and tiger
So Chan, you enjoyed the
prosperity of the world
And you tasted the bitter
fruit of the world too
Now you regret it
On behalf of Master Hung
I appoint you to be the
“Sleeping Disciple”
Now, I will teach you the
“Sleeping Disciple's Fist”!
Hope you can make good use of it
Come on
Senior…
The bitter past
Long life to you…
Here comes the White Goat
My mother, give me power
To save the people!
Tomorrow the Emperor
will go hunting
I will send him a pretty girl,
so as to get close to him
Yuen Ling, you should
seduce him tomorrow
Yes
If we can kill the Emperor,
I can take over his reign
I will give you a share of wealth!
Long life to you
Senior!
Let's go back now
Let's go!
Senior!
Let's chase them
Stop
The Emperor is setting off soon
You killed a woman…
You should replace her as
a gift to the Emperor!
No one dares come up to fight for
the leadership?
Ask Mok to give us the
“Dog Hitting Waddy”!
Ask that old bag to
hand us the waddy
Where have they been?
I don't know,
I saw them chat,
then they went away
Are there any affairs between them?
Now, we are going to choose
the new leader
Uncle Mok…
I am scared,
I think you won't come back.
How is it? Where is sister?
Your sister is caught by Chiu
We'd find someone to compete
for the leadership.
Who should go?
I'll do it
Uncle Mok
Why don't you let me try?
Chan,
you are not qualified, come down
Since you don't have a good candidate,
I'll give you some advantage
Chan, it's not a game
You will be killed, come down
It doesn't matter, I have forgotten
my life already
Bullshit, throw him to death
Well, I will make
your wish come true
What is he doing?
Sleeping
Isn't this stance…
Uncle Sun's "Sleeping Disciple's Fists"?
Set the position!
Is it dawn?
I am sorry!
I won.
What is the use for defeating us?
You don't know how to use the
“Dog Hitting Waddy”.
You are not qualified to be
the leader of us.
“Dog Hitting Waddy”?
It's for hitting dogs
I do know how to use this waddy!
But it's unlike
from the standard stances!
It's quite powerful!
He broke the waddy!
He broke the treasure of our Association,
let's kill him!
I am Master Hung,
who dares go against me?
I set the rules of the association
Any student who defeated
the Lotus Position
could be the leader
Have you all forgotten?
We become the
biggest association
because of being united
I left you the
“Dog Hitting Waddy”,
is just for memory
The waddy is meaningless
But you fools take
this as treasure
And fight among yourselves for
this damn waddy!
In these five years, you have had no
leader, don't you feel shy?
So Chan broke the waddy,
so you won't fight
for this anymore
He is correct to do so
This youngster is so junior,
but he is a genius, a smart ass
He is being taught by my disciple
Hung Yat Sun
Who doesn't respect him is going
against me too
You should respect him,
your new leader,
and you'd love him,
whole-heartedly, to care much for him,
maybe treat him dinner
Then, although I am in heaven,
I will bless all of you,
all the best
Isn't it true?
You'd better trust it
Master Hung's soul talked to us,
we are blessed
They are easily cheated,
I am really a genius!
We'll have a better living
What happened?
Let's greet the new Master
You should have faith,
you won, bravo…
Uncle Mok, my son is really great!
I can't guess you have learnt the
“Sleeping Disciple's Fists”?!
From now on, you are the new leader of us
This is the book of
“Dragon Suppressing Stances”
And, I will give you the Taiwan Pill
Hope you will be a good leader
I just want to save Yushang as
soon as possible
Yushang didn't make a wrong choice
Bravo! Bravo!
Uncle Mok, how are you?
Uncle Mok!
Uncle Mok…
Do you understand everything
written in this book?
Don't think that I am so foolish
After getting the
help of Taiwan Pill,
My initial power is increased
I can control the 17th stance
But the last stance,
there is no picture
or description of it.
I can't understand it at all
But Uncle Mok is dead, what'll we do now?
Just go ahead
No matter how, I have to save
Yushang first
Check whether the camp is ready or not?
Yes!
Chiu,
why do you bring this woman here?
I know the Emperor
loves pretty women
So I want to send him this gift
And I want to meet him too
There is no order from the Emperor
Men, come and take
this woman to the camp
Yes
Go!
Sir, you look great!
I think you should go back
to your own position
Yes
Your Majesty,
Officer Chiu brings this woman to you
Woman?
Chiu knows my hobby!
I want to take a bath first,
bring her to me later
Yes
This bastard wants
to see the Emperor,
if I let him see His Majesty often,
my post will be taken away
Men
Sir
Check what has happened
Yes
Sir, there are many people coming
from the forest
Who are they?
I don't know!
Release the alarm smoke
Be alert
Yes
There is smoke ahead,
let's get armed
Yes
Damn you beggars
So Chan, what are you doing?
Nothing, I just want
to beg for money
Shit, do you want to be killed
It's you who will be killed
Chiu wants to raise a rebel,
he is going to
assassinate the king
You fat-headed
Who do you think you are?
How dare you frame the courtier?
I will kill you if you step forward
Chan, how can we fight with them?
- Senior
- Yes
Where are the rest of our men?
They are coming
We have no time,
you stay here to wait for the others
I will go first
I will follow
Be serious
Master, don't worry
Am I going to die?
Say something lucky, OK?
Sure! Happy birthday to you…
Happy birthday to you…
That's enough
I haven't finished
Go on after I left
Sure
There is smoke ahead,
someone must have alerted them
Get ready the Unicom Smoke
Yes
Attack the main camp
Rebel! Help!
They should be killed
The one who didn't kill you
should be killed
Shit, the poisoned smoke
is blowing to the Royal camp
No, the wind direction changed
Yes, wait for me
If the beggars don't retreat now,
we will kill with no mercy
Have a look
The Unicom Smoke of
the Tin Li Sect
Be calm, urine is the antidote
to the poison
Come and piss
How about me?
Don't worry,
I can give you some urine
Come on, hold it
Rush in!
How is the situation?
Thanks for Your Majesty's luck,
the wind direction changed
The smoke is going
in the other direction
How about our armies?
They are all dead
Bring me the sword
Don't… don't!
Get lost! Get lost!
Your Majesty, it's dangerous,
don't go!
Get lost, don't you want
to wait for death, get lost
You are ordered to get away
You can't go!
Protect me
Chan?
Yushang
How did you get here?
It's a long story
We left our base last night
We reached the Great Wall
this morning
We stayed one hour for lunch
I pissed once
Really?
Yes, then I want to
eat a sweet potato
But only dumplings left
You know, I don't
like eating dumplings
I am late to save you,
please forgive me
To protect the Emperor
Yes
You betrayer!
Catch him
Your Majesty
You bastard, give your kingdom to me
Are you telling him?
It's you
Yes, I am Beggar So
Why don't you sleep in your hut?
Well, I am a little bit sleepy
“Sleeping Disciple”?
Yes. Look at you, you are
like a beggar too
Are you interested in joining us?
I can't guess you could recover!
Yes, it's all because of you
Did you generate all your force?
I didn't
Fool, only the “Dragon Suppressing
Stances” scare me
I won't give a damn
to any other stances
“Dragon Suppress Stances”
“Dragon in the sky”
“Dragon swings its tail”
“Dragon steals the heart”
Dragon swims,
dragon in the field,
dragon dances…
Dragon's descendant,
dragon's wish…
Dragon's spirit, dragon's couple
Finished
You can't finish the last stance,
you can defeat me
after learning the 18th stance
But you have no chance
Chan!
I've got it
Just mix the 17 stances,
it's the 18th stance then
I am too smart!
The 18 stance, “It's a regret to
kill the Dragon”!
Chan, are you alright?
See, don't you
think I am alright?
Your post is really smart
But your look is awful!
Idiot, I am fine
I can marry tonight
Sister!
Tracy!
Where is Chiu?
He is around
Around?
He became ashes
Damn it!
Master
Chiu's fellows are
all caught by us
Thank you, buddies
Yushang
We have an agreement,
do you remember?
Yes, be the top of all.
Invincible
But, I can't be the Scholar
But I don't like Scholar at all.
I love beggar.
You first, I will go after you.
Seng-ko-lin-ch'in,
you are really a fool
You bring a thief to harm me
Now, you are titled to be a beggar
You have potential to be a beggar
Report duty in the temple tomorrow
If there is anyone bullies you,
just tell them my name
Thank you, thank you master
So Chan, what do you want as reward?
Don't you have anything to tell me?
Nothing special, let's go
Mister So!
Put it down
Although you have saved me,
if you don't respect me, I will kill you
If so, you needn't
squat and talk to me
Don't move, it'll
attract their attention
Actually we have no relation,
we have nothing to chat about
You have billions of fellows
Your force makes me worry
The number of fellows doesn't
depend on me,
but you
What?
If you are great, making the
society peaceful and wealthy,
no one wishes to be a beggar, right?
It's reasonable
Be smart
But,
give me some face
Yes
Long life to Your Majesty
Get up
Pal, do you know me?
Of course! You beggar
You beg with your girl, you think I'll
give you money out of mercy?
Yes, please give me money
No mercy, go away
No, you should pay me
It's a must, pal
A must? Kidding?
It's true, be quick
It's bad luck to meet you
Stop
What?
See my family? Give more
How much?
Not less than a thousand, got me?
Say thank you now
Thank you, uncle