Young master, we are ready
What's a hard job for you, young master
The towel, young master
What did he write?
His name!
Great! Young master knows how to
write his name!
Yes!
Nice calligraphy
Get lost
Nice calligraphy! So Cha Ha Yee Chan!
It's reversed, Master
Chan Yee Ha Cha So
Good boy, but, don't be proud! Got me?
Dad, since the first
emperor of the Ching Dynasty,
our family
has been illiterate
But not, my son, that's your grandson,
he knows how to write his name!
Dad, it's very great!
He knows writing now,
he will be scholar one day
Now, he knows how to write his name,
he will have a son later
Young master, you should try hard to learn
Chan, I think, we should mount it
OK
Professor, show it in some obvious places
By the way, one minute,
why don't you carry it with traditional
decoration in the street?
Let's go!
Chan, come and sit…
I am so pleased that you are that hard
working and filial
Listen to me, I am notorious of being
a spendthrift
My fortune is almost used up
If I die one day,
you should depend on yourself
I used to depend on myself
The cheques worth 100,000 taels!
Don't be an extravagant spender
Give me the imported hat
Where are you going? Chan!
I am having a grand birthday party tonight
How old are you?
25 years old. Come earlier
But you should dress up first
You are like beggar!
How can a beggar be that rich?!
I do want to be a rich beggar!
That fat-headed…
Come over here
What's the matter?
The invitation card of my son is great!
If I hold a birthday party in future,
I want a better invitation card!
Your Majesty, how do you think about
the Cantonese Opera?
For sure, it can't compete with Peking Opera!
But, I am appreciated to view this
Money…
Happy birthday to you, Mr So
I am homeless and sick…
I am poor, I am damn poor!
- Please give me some money
- Kidding? Damn you beggar!
How can you beg here?
Go to hell!
- Give him tips
- Yes, young master
Are you kidding? How can you give him tips?
A beggar is a man too
Everyone can come here
if he has money
Your living,
including the expenditure for hooking,
I will pay for you!
You pay it?
So what?
Nothing!
- Come into my room…
- Please follow me.
Mr So!
Hello…
How are you, Madam Pimp?
It's very bad of you to call me that!
Just be frank, why not?
You should be frank!
Your hat, is like the mourning uniform!
Is your dad passed away?
I feel happy to talk in this way
Mr Chiu, you helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang,
the emperor will give you award for this
I'll appreciate it if you
speak something nice in front of the emperor
Please have the towel
Mr So has come
Congratulation!
This way…
Mr So, today is your big day,
you must be very happy!
We have some new girls,
you must be satisfied with it
What are they? Gold fish, or cooked fish?
What does that mean?
You idiot! Gold fish is for watching only
Cooked fish can be eaten
Cooked fish of course
You, cooked fishes, why don't you
come and serve Mr So?
Mr So, you are the superior master today
What kind of woman do you want? Just tell me
I won't mind, every women is just the same
Nothing special
Mr So, what's the matter?
I am attacked
What?
Who dared so? I will hit that
bastard's mouth for you
She didn't use her mouth
She used her eyes
Tempting, and I smell blood
I haven't seen such eyesight before
Who is she?
Miss Yushang comes to be part time hooker only
Is Mr Chiu interested to sleep with her?
You should ask His Majesty first
How is it? Your Majesty?
We are friends, just go ahead if you want!
Mr Chiu, help yourself
Thank you then
The room service please
Yushang, come and greet Mr Chiu
Sister, he is the one we want
He killed dad
I know, stay calm
Let's go
- May I be excused
- Mr Chiu
Miss Yushang has arrived
How are you? Mr Chiu
A pretty woman!
Mr Chiu, about tonight…
100,000 taels
if Miss Yushang sleeps with our
young master tonight…
You are not welcomed
I am sorry, I am damn sorry
Don't you have any objection?
Let me say something fair
If any of you can offer more than 100,000 taels
Yushang will sleep with whom
Don't quarrel because of such
small amount, isn't it right?
Pal, you are a big spender
The cheque is too simple to me
I have a pearl which is granted by the
Royal family, it's invaluable!
I love the pearl more
Mr Chiu, I will wait you in my room
Does the pearl worth 100,000 taels?
Don't you think that's too little for you?
I love money too. But, I don't like you
You are frank! I love it very much
Mr So…
It doesn't matter,
I think, my hat doesn't match me
Yushang doesn't like me, I deserve it
I am glad you understand this
Don't worry, I have many pretty girls here
I trust your arrangement
None of my business
How bold are you?
Mantis Fist? It seems to be powerful
Music!
Keep this
See my Crane's Fists!
The Tiger's Claws!
How can a mantis fight with a tiger?
I know Tiger Claws and Crane's Fists too!
Well, try my mantis!
Bravo…
Your Tiger's claws are defeated
Actually it's not Tiger's Claws,
it's beggar's fists!
That's why it's too weak
You move fast!
It seems to be powerful…
Kid, you don't know how the wind blows
The general of Canton has arrived
Get lost…
Who dares bully my son, let me teach him a lesson
Master
Don't panic, Chan who bullied you?
It's me who bullied others
What? You bullied others?
How much does he have?
Is he qualified to be bullied by you?
Master, they are the ones
Who are they?
Just take a look
The King of Iron Hat?
Send the gift
Chan
They send you such a valuable present,
you'd stop bullying them
- Come on, give tips to the girl here
- Master
King of Iron Hat, Seng-ko-lin-ch'in
is written on the medal
How dare you seize the medal of His Majesty?
Cuff him
Hold it, according to the Ching's law,
Courtier is not allowed hooking up.
Now, you are in the brothel
Do you know you have violated the laws of Ching?
How about you?
- You mean me?
- Yes!
That's right, I come…
- to arrest…
- You!
- Him!
- Arrest him
I am the general of Canton,
so I should arrest those bad people
By the way…
What else? Go ahead
Today is the birthday of the Ex-Empress Dowager
So your crime is doubled
It may lead to capital punishment.
Kill him…
According to the Ching laws,
anyone without a tail should be killed
So you…
Do you want to see my hair?
You can see as much as you want! Fat-headed
Cut the crap, just kill him
OK, it's finished
General So, let's play happily together,
so forget it
I haven't played!
Your Majesty,
a rascal has ruined the atmosphere here,
I should be blamed for poor arrangement
None of your business
Let's go
Master, you can't fool this guy. Let's go
OK, go
Just forget the trouble
Young master, your hat
He is great!