Young master, we are ready
What's a hard job for you,
young master
The towel, young master
What did he write?
His name!
Great! Young master knows how to
write his name!
Yes!
Damn!
Nice calligraphy
Get lost
Nice calligraphy!
So Cha Ha Yee Chan!
It's reversed, Master
Chan Yee Ha Cha So
Good boy, but, don't be proud!
Got me?
Dad, since the first
emperor of the Ching Dynasty,
our family
has been illiterate
But not, my son,
that's your grandson,
he knows how to write his name!
Dad, it's very great!
He knows writing now,
he will be a scholar one day
Now, he knows how to write his name,
he will have a son later
Young master,
you should try hard to learn
Chan, I think,
we should mount it
OK
Professor, show it in
some obvious places
By the way, one minute,
why don't you carry it with traditional
decoration in the street?
What?
Let's go!
Chan, come and sit...
I am so pleased that you are that
hard-working and filial
Listen to me, I am notorious for being
a spendthrift
My fortune is almost used up
If I die one day,
you should depend on yourself
I used to depend on myself
The cheque is worth 100,000 taels!
Don't be an extravagant spender
Give me the imported hat
Where are you going?
Chan!
I am having a grand
birthday party tonight
How old are you?
25 years old. Come earlier
But you should dress up first
You are like a beggar!
How can a beggar be that rich?!
I do want to be a rich beggar!
That fat-headed...
Come over here
What's the matter?
The invitation card
of my son is great!
If I hold a birthday party in the future,
I want a better invitation card!
Your Majesty, how do you think about
the Cantonese Opera?
For sure, it can't compete
with Peking Opera!
But, I appreciate
to view this
Money...
Tips. Tips...
Happy birthday to you, Mr So
I am homeless and sick...
I am poor, I am damn poor!
Please give me some money
Kidding? Damn you beggar!
How can you beg here?
Go to hell!
Give him tips
Yes, young master
Are you kidding?
How can you give him tips?
A beggar is a man too
Everyone can come here
if he has money
Your living,
including the expenditure for hooking,
I will pay for you!
You pay it?
So what?
Nothing!
Please follow me
Come into my room...
Mr So!
Hello...
How are you, Madam Pimp?
It's very bad of
you to call me that!
Just be frank, why not?
You should be frank!
Your hat, is like
the mourning uniform!
Has your dad passed away?
I feel happy to talk in this way
Mr Chiu, you helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang,
the emperor will
give you award for this
I'll appreciate it if you
speak something nice in front of
the emperor
Please have the towel
Mr So has come
Congratulations!
This way...
Mr So, today is your big day,
you must be very happy!
We have some new girls,
you must be satisfied with them
What are they?
Gold fish, or cooked fish?
What does that mean?
You idiot! Gold fish is
for watching only
Cooked fish can be eaten
Cooked fish of course
You, cooked fishes, why don't you
come and serve Mr So?
Mr So, you are the
superior master today
What kind of woman do you want?
Just tell me
I won't mind,
every woman is just the same
Nothing special
Mr So, what's the matter?
I am attacked
What? Who dared so?
I will hit that
bastard's mouth for you
She didn't use her mouth
She used her eyes
Tempting, and I smell blood.
I haven't seen such eyesight before.
Who is she?
Miss Yushang comes to be a part-time
hooker only
Is Mr Chiu interested to sleep with her?
You should ask His Majesty first
How is it? Your Majesty?
We are friends,
just go ahead if you want!
Mr Chiu, help yourself
Thank you then
The room service please
Yushang, come and greet Mr Chiu
Sister, he is the one we want
He killed dad
I know, stay calm
Let's go
May I be excused?
Mr Chiu, Miss Yushang has arrived
How are you, Mr Chiu?
A pretty woman!
Mr Chiu, about tonight...
$100,000
if Miss Yushang sleeps with our
young master tonight...
You are not welcome
I am sorry, I am damn sorry
Don't you have any objection?
Let me say something fair
If any of you can offer
more than $100,000
Yushang will sleep with whomever
Don't quarrel because of such
small amount,
isn't it right?
Pal, you are a big spender
The cheque is too simple to me
I have a pearl which is granted by the
Royal family, it's invaluable!
I love the pearl more
Mr Chiu, I will wait for
you in my room
Is the pearl worth $100,000?
Don't you think that's
too little for you?
I love money too
But, I don't like you
You are frank!
I love it very much
Mr So...
It doesn't matter,
I think, my hat doesn't match me
Yushang doesn't like me,
I deserve it
I am glad you understand this
Don't worry,
I have many pretty girls here
I trust your arrangement
None of my business
How bold are you?
Mantis Fist?
It seems to be powerful
Music!
Keep this
See my Crane's Fists!
The Tiger's Claws!
How can a mantis fight with a tiger?
I know Tiger Claws
and Crane's Fists too!
Well, try me, mantis!
Bravo...
Your Tiger's claws are defeated
Actually it's not Tiger's Claws,
it's beggar's fists!
That's why it's too weak
You move fast!
It seems to be powerful...
Kid, you don't know how
the wind blows
The general of
Canton has arrived
Get lost...
Who dares bully my son?
Let me teach him a lesson.
Master
Don't panic, Chan who bullied you?
It's me who bullied others
What? You bullied others?
How much does he have?
Is he even qualified to be bullied by you?
Master, they are the ones
Who are they?
Just take a look
The King of Iron Hat?
Send the gift
Chan
They sent you such a valuable present,
you should stop bullying them.
Come on, give tips to the girls here
Master
King of Iron Hat, Seng-ko-lin-ch'in,
is written on the medal.
How dare you seize the medal
of His Majesty?
Cuff him
Hold it, according to the Ching's law,
Courtiers are not allowed to partake in hooking
Now, you are in the brothel
Do you know you have violated
the laws of Ching?
How about you?
- You mean me?
- Yes!
That's right, I come...
- to arrest...
- You!
- Him!
- Arrest him!
I am the general of Canton,
so I should arrest
those bad people
By the way...
What else? Go ahead
Today is the birthday of
the Ex-Empress Dowager
So your crime is doubled
It may result in capital punishment
Kill him...
According to the Ching laws,
anyone without a tail should be killed
So you...
Do you want to see my hair?
You can see as much as you want!
Fathead.
Cut the crap, just kill him
OK, it's finished
General So, let's play happily together,
so just forget it.
I haven't played!
Your Majesty,
a rascal has ruined
the atmosphere here,
I should be blamed
for poor arrangement
None of your business
Let's go
Master, you can't fool this guy.
Let's go.
OK, go
Just forget the trouble
Young master, your hat
He is great!
Uncle Mok, the dishes
are all poisoned
Chiu assassinated our Master
and some generals of
The Taiping Reign
And he framed us, the Beggars Association,
to be the assassins
Thus made us
to be despised by the world
Saying that we became the dogs
of the government
I should ask him to pay for it
His initial power is harmful
Don't take action
until he is trapped
Because we can't defeat him even
if we group together
I will try my best to seduce
him to the bed
Senior, somebody is coming
Get ready...
Miss Yushang, we meet again
Why do you come here?
Where is Mister Chiu?
The pearl of Mr. Chiu is broken
by Mr. So and became pearl powder
I have drunk it
Don't judge Mr So from his hair,
he is really romantic and funny
But...
Stop, I have taken his money,
100,000 taels you know?
I won't give it back
About the personality of Mr So...
Cut the crap, pimp!
Leave here first
Yes, you are right
Miss Seven...
Just accept this
Who is this guy?
I don't know
Miss, first of all, I have good news for you
I love you
To me, this is a bad news
I know you will reply like this
Cut the crap
I wish to pay you 100 pearls
for your company tonight
I don't want to talk to you
Please get out
I haven't chosen the wrong one
OK, I will drink this wine first
No...
It surprised me
Miss
Hands off!
You know Kung-fu?
No, I don't know Kung-fu at all
I beg you, stop bothering me
I won't accompany you
Yushang, no one treats
me like this
I have found that
I am in love with you
What?
I have been in love with you
Are you kidding?
I am not kidding,
I decided to marry you
Are you nuts?
Kidding?
Is anyone hiding here?
That's good, I want a witness
Witness?
Yes, I swear in front of your sword
I do want to marry Miss Yushang
as my wife, I am sincere
If I cheat,
I will be killed by thunder
Sister, I feel excited for you
Hey
Don't you know it isn't that easy
to be my husband?
How can I be your husband?
I want him to be the superior
Kung-fu master
Be the top of all
Can you do that?
Let me think for one second
I can do it
OK
Do it first and then look for me
Well, I think we should fix a date
for our wedding
Because this is too easy for me
to be the Kung-fu scholar!
OK, but you should give me some time
to consider it
No problem, I will wait for your answer
outside the garden
I won't leave until seeing you
Crazy!
We come from the Beggars Association,
Those unrelated,  leave at once.
Sir, the timing is right
The road is safe now, please go
Good, very good
Let's go!
Shit, we are late
That Manchurian should be blamed
Sister...
What's the matter?
The idiot is still there
Let's kill him
Forget it,
he doesn't mean to bother us
Let him go
Are you fond of him?
What did you say?
I won't fall in love with anybody
until Chiu is killed
Especially him
Chiu is good at Kung-fu
Mok said, we can't defeat him unless
using the "Dragon Killing Palms"
So, I can never marry!
Let's go, if you want to get married
What evil are you?
How dare you scare me?
Mr So, it's me!
You are the pimp?!
Yes!
You have a flat figure,
where is your bust?
It's early in the morning,
it hasn't woken up yet.
You're lucky
not to have been killed.
Don't go around if you haven't
put on your makeup yet.
I won't do it again
Stop waiting for Miss Yushang,
she left
What?
Where is she going?
She... she is going to Peking
Peking?
Men should contribute to the country
Where should I put my pigtail?
Swing and swing...
I pull it and play it...
Dad!
I decided to join the examination for the
Scholar of Martial Arts.
Chan
I have been longing for this word
for 25 years
For our family, you should do that.
Don't misunderstand it,
I'm not doing this for anyone,
but for a woman
What a hero!
For a girl, you want to be the Scholar
of Martial Arts!
Who is that girl?
The hooker of Yee Hung Brothel,
Miss Yushang
For a hooker?
What's wrong with it?
You have different taste,
you are great!
I admire you!
I will accompany you to Peking
2, 3, 4, 5, 6
I am coming
Young master is going for the examination,
let's move to Peking too
Stop chasing,
we won't take the hens with us
Be careful!
If you break my stuff,
I will teach you a good lesson.
Be careful!
Good morning, Dad.
Good morning
You want to move
everything to Peking?
Sure
Please leave me a cloth.
You are only a kid,
you don't need this
But I am not small.
Are you bigger than mine?
You despise me!
Mine will be bigger
than yours one day
Let's find something,
say trousers to cover it
I don't want to see it
Why are you standing here for?
Why don't you remove it?
It's a hard job to remove
such a big house!
Please, work hard men!
Ready, 1, 2, 3, push!
Push!
Be careful!
Tie it well...
Master, do you want to
move the tree too?
Sure,
or how can I eat lychee in Peking?
Push it over...
Be careful
Take care of my lychee,
you fathead!
Chiu helped me to terminate
the Hairy Gang in Kwangsi
So I bring him here
to greet Your Majesty
Fine, I am now appointing you to be
the Deputy Secretary
Hope you will serve our Ching Dynasty
wholeheartedly.
Thank you, Your Majesty
Your Majesty, Mr Chiu is a magician
Why don't you ask him to
show you something?
Magic?
Mr Chiu, then show me your magic
Yes, Your Majesty
There is nothing surprising. Go.
Yes
I am sorry for scaring you
If this girl is real,
that's fantastic!
Hurry up!
What's the matter?
Come on, go in
Hide inside
Get ready, young master
Come on
Freeze, don't move
Sweet smell, are you Piu Hung?
You are great!
I love it
Closer
So big!
You must be small!
You are bad, how can
you say so to me?
You are big!
What? Pregnant woman?
You can't cheat me
You are a dad.
How bad are you,
how can you guess that?
Good boy
I wanted to trick you actually,
you are really smart
Young master has to join
the examination tomorrow,
stop playing
Get out...
Chan, have you prepared
for your examination?
What should I prepare?
I must win, don't you know that?
Yes I do!
I have faith in you from seeing
your behaviour!
Chan, this is Uncle Cheng
He will be the examiner
Say hello to Uncle Cheng
How are you, Uncle Cheng?
See
Doesn't he seem to be the winner?
It depends on the fate
Cheng, I've asked someone
to finish the papers
which you gave me
Will the questions be changed?
Don't worry about
the question paper
But for the test
of arrow shooting,
riding, boxing and weapons...
He should try his best
Don't worry
My son is keen in martial arts
So, can I deduct some from the payment
of 2 million taels?
We are friends,
but that is business
Let the horse teams
be the pioneers
The arrow teams go sideways,
the gunmen stay back
The candidates come in
I can't lift it
I don't want to waste my force
Shameless? Damn you!
Oh, 10 marks
The final race starts now
The candidates,
Po Ye Tat Tor from Mongolia
Bravo...
And So Cha Ha Yee
Chan from Canton
Last call
So, one to ten
Po, one to one
Are you kidding, how can the betting rates
differ so much?
One to ten for Chan? Kidding?
Why don't you have
faith in Chan?
That is, Chan defaulted
in weight lifting
Look, Po entered the final race
with full marks, it differs
It's an examination for the Scholar
of Martial Arts, not king of coolies.
It's meaningless to be the champion
of weight lifting
You shouldn't put it that way
What?
He is smart
I've studied this
race for a long time
I feel strange about the rate too
Po is smart and strong
But see the sweat of his neck
I think it's because
he is getting tired
Really?
But this So
What do you think?
He has been disappointing
the audience
But he has worked very hard.
What?
He tried very hard
So I want to bet on him
How much do you want to bet?
800,000 taels
Why not 2 million taels?
What? Why are you so optimistic
about Chan?
You have good analysis.
I feel Chan
will be the champion
Come on
I want to bet more on him
Really?
2 million taels!
How generous!
Why don't you bet?
Why should I bet?
He is my son
Shit, I missed one thing in
my calculation.
What?
The blood
Here comes the Examiner
What? Isn't Cheng the examiner?
Please take a seat
Seng-ko-lin-ch'in?!
What's the problem?
He is the uncle of Po
Let's start
Start!
Bravo...
They should add 2 more marks for that
powerful shot
I do think so
So's arrow isn't on the target,
Po won this section
Kidding? Damn you!
They are cheating
Candidates, please get on the horses.
Mr Chiu
Take these with you, maybe you will
find them useful
Here comes the 2nd round
They're tricking us again.
It's corrupt!
May I give up my bet?
Chan won this race
Did you tear the ticket?
Not yet
Are you kidding?
Once again?!
OK, let's start from the very beginning.
I'll fight with a single hand and leg.
I won't take your advantage
How can you use
such dirty stance?
Have you woken up?
Bravo! He won!
Have some tea
All the best!
What did
you say?
It's English
There is no regulation stating that
weapons are not allowed.
You fell down first,
so Po is the winner again.
Damn you Cheng!
You betrayed me!
I will beat you to death
if I see you again
Forget it, you won't
see him anymore
Why?
I am now going to kill him!
I don't have 2 million to lose!
Just kidding
You are shameless
Po is the Scholar of Martial Arts
I did win! Objection!
What are you doing?
The dart is poisoned
He deserves it!
He was poisoned by his own dart
Well, my son will
be the Scholar then
I am going to be rich!
Yes!
Thank you, my ancestors!
You have good judgement
Sir, His Majesty wants to appoint
the title himself
I want to take a statement
from you for the record
You won this time, who are you
going to thank?
Miss Yushang!
Is Miss Yushang your mom?
Long life to you!
Please get up
Thank you
Who is the new Scholar
of Martial Arts?
Your Majesty, So Chan from Canton
is the Scholar this year
Your Majesty,
I am So Cha Ha Yee Chan
I want to report something
Go ahead
I have found that
So is illiterate
So how could he answer the
question paper of strategy?
That must be a trick.
Take the stationery out!
Yes
So Cha Ha Yee Chan,
write your name now
Thank God, he knows how to
write his name!
He can write his name!
I don't know how to write
That's shit!
Kill him now
No! No!
Your Majesty,
I am the one who cheated
It's none of his business
Just chop me to death
No, you should kill me
Sorry dad
I don't know how to write my name
Stop, I already know it.
Your Majesty, I should be killed
Kill me
No, kill me
Your Majesty, you'd better kill me
Shit, are you giving orders?
You two cooperated to cheat me.
The Secretary for Justice,
announce the penalty for them
Come out! Hurry up
I am here!
He is the Secretary for Justice
So's family should be
sentenced to death
But their ancestors achieved a lot
for the Ching. They can be exempted.
But, their fortune should be forfeited
Have you carried out any military duty?
I haven't gone back to my camp for
7 years, I haven't done anything
So, he didn't miscarry out any duty
So, the maximum penalty
is forfeiture of property only