Why are we not there yet?
Don't be like that. We'll get there when your candy's gone.
This is my eighth candy. You're just fooling me.
Dad, when will we get there?
Have another caramel.
Once we turn this corner, we're there.
The air here is so fresh.
It's the perfect place for Mom to recover.
Who is that?
It's the postman. He'll be here any minute.
Hello, Mr. Postman!
I'm Satsuki Kusakabe! How do you do?
Pleased to meet you.
Mei, sit still.
There are lots of curves here.
I'm dizzy! I'm dizzy!
Hello there, little one.
Is your family home?
They're working across the way.
Thank you.
How is everyone?
I'm Kusakabe. We just moved here.
Please take good care of us.
A young lady shouldn't be so shameless.
Are you that close to him?
Thank you.
Ha... I'll tickle you... tickle you... ha...
We're finally here.
Wonderful!
Ah... wait for me...
Don't be in such a hurry.
This river is so beautiful.
Yeah!
Do you see any fish?
Why can't I see them?
You're so nearsighted. Be careful with your glasses.
Careful! Don't fall in the river!
Let's see if the house is pretty first.
Move aside, move aside! I want to look first!
It's so pretty. Let's go over and see.
Ha... ha... this is great!... ha...
Hurry up!
It's so old, it looks like a haunted house.
Ha! This is great!
This is great! It's exciting!
It's so flimsy, like it's about to collapse.
Great!
Mei, look at that tree...
It's so tall and big. Look.
Dad said that what we kids achieve
should one day be like this tree,
so tall and big!
Dad, what kind of tree is this?
It's an oak tree!
An oak tree?
A tree turned from a big dumb elephant?
Careful!
There's an acorn!
Satsuki, let me see!
No, no, no!
Catch me and I'll buy you a drumstick!
I found a drumstick too!
Chicken legs? How could there be chicken legs here?
These!
I found a seed, Dad.
I found one too!
Acorns? How could there be acorns in the house?
Yeah! How could that happen?
Maybe squirrels brought them in.
Do squirrels know how to move house?
Sir, where should I put these things?
Sorry, please bring them in. Excuse us.
Go open the back door and air the place out.
Be a good girl and hurry up.
Come on... come on... come on...
These two little girls are very smart.
Come on, hurry up.
Catch me, catch me!
Ha!... Come on... come on... come on...
Open it!
Let's take a look first.
Oh...
Mm, no problem!
Dad said if you see ghosts, you scare them away.
They're gone?
Where'd they go?
Let's go look.
Really? Let's see if there are any left.
None!
That's the bathroom.
We just saw some ghosts.
What?
The two of us scared those ghosts off.
They ran into the bathroom, and now they're gone.
Let me take a look.
Did you see them?
No, those were just soot sprites.
Soot sprites, not ghosts?
You just came in from the bright outdoors,
so your eyes got dazzled!
I'm telling you, once the sunlight shines into the house,
all the ghosts and goblins will run away.
They run the minute they see the light!
The soot sprites ran off. All the ghosts are gone.
That's good... Ha...
Stop playing around. Hurry up and get to work.
Do you know how to get to the second floor?
Go up to the second floor and open all the windows.
Yes!
...I want to go too...
The stairs!
Not here.
Nope.
The stairs!
Where are they?
They're not here.
Not here, not here.
Could they be here?
Hey, I found it!
It's so dark. Do you think there might be...
Dustbunnies again?
What's that sound?
A chicken leg?
The soot sprites ran away.
Use your secret move!
How dare you make fools of us like that.
I'll deal with you.
There are soot sprites.
Mei, help me out!
Come on.
It's heavy. Be careful.
Dad! Dad!
There are ghosts in the house again.
If you open the windows, you won't be afraid of those ghosts.
Dad is big and strong, and wise and heroic.
That's not good!
Great, I caught one!
Daddy, help!
Satsuki! Satsuki!
What lively little darlings.
This is Granny, our neighbor.
She's very kind. Say hello.
How are you, Granny?
I'm Satsuki.
Hello, Miss Satsuki.
You moved in earlier than expected.
I didn't have time to help you clean up.
I'm terribly sorry.
You're too polite.
We're neighbors, after all.
We should help each other.
Mei, why are your hands so dirty?
I caught a soot sprite.
Look at your feet.
Why are they like that?
So you saw the soot sprites.
Let me tell you, there are lots of soot sprites here.
Soot sprites?
Those things that fly around and pop in and out?
They're really called soot sprites?
Don't be scared. According to the legend here,
only good children
can see the soot sprites.
When I was little, I used to see them all the time too.
When I was little, I was even prettier than you two.
These mountains really are special.
The soot sprites won't hurt children.
As long as you smile at them,
they'll help you.
Even if you ask them for something,
they'll help you with that too.
If you scare them like that,
they've probably flown away already.
I told you, there's nothing to be scared of.
You're not even scared of soot sprites that big.
You don't have to scare me.
Don't wake me up in the middle of the night to go to the bathroom with you.
What cute children.
Go bring back some water so I can clean this place up.
Okay, Granny.
Great, we get to play with water.
Great!
Come on, hurry up!
Okay.
Granny, there's water!
Keep pumping. Don't let it stop.
Okay!
Granny...
Oh, it's you.
Who are you looking for?
I-I-I-I'm here to see Granny.
Your granny?
Here, take it.
What are you doing?
Scaredy-cat.
Don't call me a scaredy-cat.
Especially not in front of an ugly girl like this.
How rude.
Your grandson is so shy, just like I was when I was little.
The rice cakes he brought are delicious.
They're just as good as the ones Mom makes.
Then have some more.
Goodbye.
Thank you, Granny.
Goodbye, Granny.
This place... everything here
seems so full of life.
The wind sounds like ghosts howling. It's scary.
Silly, there's nothing to be afraid of in the wind.
Granny says if you see something scary,
just smile at it and you'll be fine.
If you're laughing like that, it means you're really scared.
Are you scared too?
No, don't! I'm ticklish!
Pedal...
Keep it going, Dad.
Here it comes, okay?
All right, that's done.
We're going to visit Mom.
That's great.
We're going to the hospital to visit Mom.
Here it comes!
All right, let's get going.
How are you, Granny?
Granny, we're heading out.
Where're you all heading?
We're going to visit Mom in the hospital.
To ask the doctor when she can leave the hospital
and come home to recuperate?
Okay, goodbye.
It's over there!
Over there!
Daddy, that's the hospital.
Hello, Auntie. How are you?
We came to visit Mom.
Mom!
Mei, have you been good?
Dad says Satsuki and I have been good.
Really, Satsuki?
Mom, you look really well.
Do I?
Dad is talking to the doctor about your discharge.
Yes, I'll be able to leave the hospital soon.
How's the new house?
Have you finished unpacking?
Silly, don't be so paranoid.
Mom, are you afraid of soot sprites?
If there are no ghosts in your heart, how could you see any ghosts?
Yeah.
We hope your pneumonia gets better soon
so you can come home.
You really miss Mom that much?
Yeah.
I miss you even more.
Mei's hair...
Did you brush it for her, Satsuki?
Very nice. You're improving.
But Satsuki always scolds me.
That's because you won't behave.
Satsuki,
come here.
Why did you cut your hair so short?
I like it.
I want mine brushed too.
You wait a minute.
All right, don't keep fighting over it.
Let me finish brushing Satsuki's first, then I'll do yours, okay?
When I grow up,
will my hair be like yours, Mom?
Yes, because you look like Mom.
Dad, Mom looks a lot better.
Yes, that's right.
The doctor said she'll be able to leave the hospital and come home soon.
You mean tomorrow?
Silly, how could it be that soon?
The soonest would be next week.
After Mom comes home, I want her to hold me while I sleep.
Didn't you say you'd grown up
and didn't need anyone to sleep with you anymore? Forgot?
Can't I be naughty for a few more days?
Lazy Dad, wake up!
Wake up, sleepy Daddy...
What a mess.
I've got everything ready.
I forgot to make your lunch to take to school.
I've already made it, so don't worry.
It smells like something's burning.
Don't be silly. What I cook is delicious.
Satsuki, you're amazing.
You two are such good girls.
Mei, this lunch box is yours.
Satsuki, it's time for school.
Ashin's looking for me.
Coming...
You made a friend already?
Big sis is really popular with her classmates.
His name is Ashin. I'm off to school.
Bye.
Be careful on the way.
Morning, Ashin.
Hurry up.
We're late.
Morning...
Dad!
I'm going out!
Remember, don't go too far.
Okay!
Dad, is it lunchtime yet?
We just finished breakfast, and now lunch? You're silly.
Flowers, sir?
What are these things?
Get a bucket to catch it.
There it is.
It has a hole in it.
Chicken drumstick?
One more!
Two more!
Three more!
Four more!
There are lots of them!
There are so many!
Chirp, chirp...
Don't go!
BOm BOm Bart
Bom bom ba!
Chitty chitty...
Don't go...
Get it!
Run, Bom Bom Bart!
A pink monster is chasing us!
Hurry back to your master!
Poke.
This is fun!
It's soft as a mattress.
You look just like a giant drumstick.
Are you Totoro, the king of the forest?
Someone didn't brush their teeth.
Totoro, my name is Mei. I like you a lot.
Let's be good friends.
Okay?
Chitter chatter...
Bom bom bart...
See ya, then.
See you later!
I'm home!
Welcome back. It's gotten so late.
Where's Mei? Where did Mei go?
She was just outside playing.
It's almost dinnertime.
Mei! Mei!
Mei!
Dad, Mei's hat is here!
Mei, Mei.
Mei, wake up.
How can you sleep out here?
Big drumstick.
Big drumstick?
Where's the big drumstick?
Are you still dreaming?
I saw a Totoro that looked like a big drumstick.
Totoro? Those only exist in picture books.
Totoro really does exist.
He was all furry, and his mouth was like this.
There was one this big, and one bigger.
And an even bigger one was sleeping.
There you are.
This is a nice spot, just like a secret base.
Dad,
Mei said she saw Totoro here.
Totoro?
Coming...
Wait for me!
Right here?
I just saw it sleeping here.
But there's only one path here.
Mei, come back!
Where's Totoro?
I'm not lying. I really saw him.
You don't believe me?
Mei.
None of you believe me.
Daddy and Satsuki both believe you.
You must have seen the master of this forest.
He's called Totoro.
That's what the legend here says.
Not every child gets to see him.
Seeing him brings you good luck.
All right, why don't we take a walk nearby?
Okay!
Let's see what beautiful scenery there is.
Riding on your shoulders is fun!
Dad, hurry!
You're getting heavier and heavier, Mei.
Dad, look at that camphor tree!
It's huge!
This is the tree.
Yep.
Dad.
Dad, hurry up!
I saw Totoro here.
Why is the hole gone?
Was it this tree?
She said the hole disappeared.
You can't see it all the time.
Why? Why can't we see it?
People in the country say you can't see it all the time.
Unless... you're lucky.
Daddy grew up in this forest when he was little.
I've missed this place so much.
I hope Mom can recover here.
And get well soon.
This big forest is full of spirit.
If we live well here,
it'll bring us good luck.
Come on, let's say goodbye to Totoro.
It's time to go home for lunch.
Mei, you're sure to have good luck.
You'll see Totoro too.
Attention!
Let's say goodbye to Totoro.
Goodbye, Totoro.
Let's see who can get there first.
Daddy, that's cheating! Wait for me!
Daddy!
Hurry up!
Wait for me!
Mom, Mei saw Totoro today,
and Daddy said it can bring good luck.
I hope you have good luck too, Mom, and get well soon.
You go on to school. I can manage.
Be good, okay? Bye.
Bye.
Shy boy, aren't you going to school yet?
In a minute.
Pay attention.
Mei, Miss Yamabuki.
What is it?
My little sister is outside.
Her little sister...
Let's see...
Granny, what's wrong with her?
Mei threw a tantrum this morning.
She wanted to come and have class with her sister.
Mei.
You know Dad has to go back to the university today.
You should be a good girl and stay at Granny's.
Don't make a fuss.
I still have two classes to go,
and Granny is very busy too.
Does Mei want to come to school too?
Okay, Granny, I'll talk to Ms. Yamabuki.
Everyone, Satsuki's mother is in the hospital,
and her father has to work, too.
so her little sister will be joining us in class today.
Yes.
What are you drawing?
It's Totoro.
You can't be so noisy.
See you later!
I'm skipping club today.
See you tomorrow, then.
We'd better get a move on. It's gonna rain.
Oh no, it's raining.
It's really pouring.
Hurry up, Mei, come on!
You're so careless. Come on.
I didn't even cry when I fell. Aren't I great?
This is really a problem.
Lord Guardian, please make the rain stop soon.
But...
That was lucky, wasn't it, Sis?
But this umbrella's got holes in it.
Dad went out without taking his umbrella.
Let's go pick him up at the station.
I said the wind broke the umbrella, so I threw it away.
You liked that umbrella so much. Why would you throw it away?
I said I already threw it away.
I'll buy you a new one tomorrow.
I don't want one.
Hello?
Oh, Satsuki and Mei. Granny.
Sorry to trouble you today.
Trouble? We didn't help you with anything.
We did. That shy boy lent us his umbrella.
He did?
Don't mention it. It's just an old umbrella.
It was raining really hard then.
Good thing he lent us his umbrella.
But he got completely soaked.
It's all right.
That fool comes home soaked all over every day anyway.
He only just got home.
Are you going to meet your dad after work now?
Yes.
You're such a good girl.
Bye-bye.
Did someone come by?
No.
A bus is pulling in.
Are you getting on?
All right, drive on.
Dad wasn't on this bus?
He must be on the next one.
Why don't you go to Granny's house?
No.
What are you doing?
Mei, are you tired?
I told you to go to Granny's earlier.
The bus will be here soon, so hang in there a little longer.
Why is the bus taking so long?
I'll carry you.
Totoro?
Wait a second.
You can borrow this.
Quick, Mei's slipping off.
You do it like this.
Here comes the bus!
What is that?
Totoro took Dad's umbrella away.
Did you come to pick me up?
Dad.
It's so windy and rainy, and you still came to the station for me.
You two are such good girls.
I saw him.
I saw him. I finally saw him.
Totoro, and the Catbus!
The Catbus?
Such a huge Catbus!
This is great. I finally got to see Totoro.
So great.
So great, Totoro.
So that's what Totoro is like.
So great.
What a fuss over nothing.
Mom, tonight I finally saw Totoro.
Tonight was really mysterious.
You could say it was both scary and fun.
Totoro even gave us
a present wrapped in a bamboo leaf.
When we got home, we opened it,
and it turned out to be full of acorns.
So we planted the acorns in the backyard,
hoping that someday they'd grow into an oak forest.
But...
they just wouldn't sprout, no matter how long we waited.
Every day, Mei would stare at the dirt, looking disappointed.
It was the first time I'd ever seen that disappointed look on her face,
and it made me feel really uneasy.
It's nearly summer vacation. I hope you'll get well soon.
Your eldest daughter, Satsuki.
Come on, lights out.
No.
Dad, will those chicken legs sprout tomorrow?
How should I know?
Ask Totoro. Totoro would know.
Go to sleep now.
Chitter chatter...
Bom bom bart...
Hey, Mei.
Bom bom ba-bart...
Chitty chah...
What are they doing?
Why don't we go outside and take a look?
We did it!
Great!
I'll come too.
Wait for me!
Flying is so much fun!
What about the tree?
Wonderful!
It's sprouted!
It sprouted!
Wonderful.
Wonderful... It's sprouting...
Anybody home? Telegram!
Hello? Anybody home?
Mr. Kusakabe, telegram for you!
Why is no one home?
Granny!
Granny.
It's you two.
Yes, Mei, do you eat corn?
Granny, I want some.
Okay.
Granny, this vegetable patch is like a treasure mountain.
Yeah. Come on, let's take a little break.
These have gotten nice and cold.
Thanks, then.
It's really good.
Yeah.
Because the sunshine and soil here are both very good,
so eating them is very good for your body.
Then will it help Mom's illness too?
Of course it will.
If she eats the vegetables Granny grows,
she'll be completely well again in no time.
Mom's getting out of the hospital on Saturday.
Then I can cuddle up to Mom again.
I see.
So she can finally get out of the hospital.
She's not really being discharged.
She still has to go back on Monday.
It's to let her get used to it first.
Then she should eat more of the fruit and vegetables here.
The corn Mei picked should be saved for Mom to eat.
Mom will definitely be very happy.
You have a telegram.
Since there was nobody at your house,
they brought it over here.
For us?
Yes.
But Dad said he won't be back until later.
Open it and see. It might be urgent.
Please contact Shichikokuyama at once.
It's from the hospital.
It's the hospital where Mom is staying.
It's Mom. I don't know what's happened.
Granny, what do I do? How do I contact them?
Calm down. Don't panic.
Can you find your father?
I know the number for his research lab.
But we don't have a phone at home.
You shy boy.
Hurry and take her to the village headman's house to borrow the phone.
Mei, don't go with Satsuki.
Mei, hurry back to Granny's!
Hello, I'd like to make a long-distance call to the suburbs of Tokyo, please.
The number there is 1382, yes.
You shy boy, your girlfriend's really cute.
Is this... the archaeology department?
Could you please get... get my father...
No, I mean Mr. Kusakabe.
I'm his daughter.
Satsuki, yes.
Dad, it's Satsuki.
Satsuki, what is it?
Yes.
From the hospital?
I understand. I'll call them right away.
Did something happen to Mom? What are we gonna do, Dad?
Don't worry.
I'll ask and then call you right back.
Wait there for a little while.
Satsuki, I'm hanging up now.
Ma'am,
could I wait here for my dad's call?
Sure, make yourself at home.
Satsuki!
No, you can't have it. This corn is for my mom.
No, I have to give it to my mom.
Satsuki,
Mei, Mom's condition isn't very good right now.
So she has to come home later?
No!
Mom's health is what matters.
Don't throw a tantrum. You're getting more and more disobedient.
No!
Y-You want Mom to die?
I don't!
What's the matter? She's only coming home a few days later.
If you're not good, I'm not talking to you.
You should go back.
Satsuki's so mean.
I brought in the laundry for you.
Don't be so down. Cheer up.
Granny's here to help you now.
Your dad's already gone to the hospital to see her.
Your mom will be fine.
She'll be home next Saturday.
You're lying.
That's what you said last time too.
You said she'd only stay in the hospital for two days.
Who knew she'd end up staying this long?
What if she dies?
She won't, Satsuki.
But what if Mom really...
Don't worry, it'll be okay.
With such a lovely daughter,
how could she bear to die?
Don't cry. Granny's here with you.
I'll stay with you till your father comes back, okay?
Mei.
Mei!
Did Mei come back?
No, she hasn't come back yet.
That's strange. Where could Mei have gone?
Could it be because I scolded her earlier?
I don't know if she might've...
gone to the hospital where Mom is?
How would she get to the hospital?
It's very far.
She's so little. How would she know how to take a bus to the hospital?
I'll go look for her.
Kanta, quick, go get your dad to help!
Mei's missing?
Mei, this is bad.
She always gets lost.
Mei, Mei!
Excuse me, sir, may I ask you something?
Have you seen a little girl with pigtails pass by?
She's my little sister.
No, I haven't. I've been here most of the day.
I haven't seen any little girl go by.
Where on earth did she go?
Why don't you look somewhere else?
Mei, please be all right.
Mei, I shouldn't have yelled at you.
Please forgive me. Please be all right.
Mei!
Stop!
You idiot! You could've killed yourself!
I'm looking for my little sister.
Have you seen a little girl come by?
A little girl?
She may have gone to Shichikokuyama Hospital.
My sister is only four years old.
Did you notice her?
We came from Shichikokuyama.
But we didn't see any little girl along the way.
Yes, thank you very much.
Where did you come from?
From Totoro Mountain.
Totoro Mountain?
You must be mistaken. That's very far.
How did you get here from so far away?
Well, good luck looking.
Satsuki!
Kanta, you shy boy, did you find her?
Not yet. She's not in there.
My dad and the others are searching all around.
I'll go to Shichikokuyama with you.
For now, you go back home first, okay?
Mei must have, on the way to the hospital,
gotten lost on the road.
A little while ago, they found a shoe by the river.
Go check by the river and see if it's Mei's.
Not yet.
Mei, don't die!
Mei, please don't die.
Namu Amida Butsu...
Over there! Hurry, go drag that side!
Kusakabe's on her way.
Mei!
We found Mei's shoe.
These shoes aren't Mei's.
Thank goodness, it wasn't Mei's.
That scared me to death.
So those shoes weren't a child's after all.
No need to keep looking there. It was a false alarm.
She didn't fall into the water.
That's a relief...
That really scared me...
Kusakabe, where are you going?
Please, let me see Totoro.
Mei is lost, and it'll be dark soon.
But we still haven't found her.
Totoro!
Totoro, Mei's lost.
I just can't find her.
Please, help me find her.
I'm sure she's somewhere crying.
I don't know what to do anymore.
So it's a Catbus.
Please stand clear of the doors.
Please stand
clear of the doors.
Mei.
Even the trees are moving aside!
Mei!
Sis!
Satsuki!
You silly girl, I was so worried about you.
I'm sorry.
Did you want to take the corn to the hospital for Mom to eat?
You'll take us to the hospital?
That's great.
I'm sorry. The doctor says I can leave the hospital early,
so I was so anxious that I sent you a telegram.
I'm really sorry I scared you.
If the children knew... that you can leave the hospital tomorrow,
I think they'd be very happy.
They've been hoping for your discharge for a long time.
I've been in the hospital so long
and made them suffer a lot.
It breaks my heart that no one's there to look after them.
They're very sensible.
Once I'm out of the hospital,
the two of them won't have to work so hard.
It's not so hard. They keep saying all day
they want to find Totoro and have him bring medicine to make you well.
Children really are so innocent.
Mom seems fine now.
She looks full of energy, too.
Yeah.
I feel so energetic, like I took Totoro's medicine.
Really?
Who brought this corn here?
Could it be they really found Totoro
and brought this corn to cure me?
I think maybe so. Look.
We love you the most.