Police.
Show me your ID.
- Check his ID.
- Yes sir.
- What's in your bag?
- Headquarter,
- Let me see.
- please verify ID number 0532743…
Bracket 1, Kwai Ching-hung.
Open it.
The arrangement for Hong Kong
contained in the agreement
are not measures of expediency.
They are long-term policies
which will be incorporated
in the Basic Law for Hong Kong
and preserved intact for 50 years from 1997.
It is the common interests
as well as shared
responsibilities of China and Britain
to ensure the Joint Declaration is fully
implemented with no encumbrances.
An armed robbery took place this afternoon in Kwun Tong.
4 armed suspects robbed 5 gem shops
on Mut Watt Street.
Fuck you!
In the footage provided by our audience,
the robbers exchanged fire
with the Special Duties Unit.
2 passersby and 3 policemen
were injured in the incident.
The5gold shops lost $1 OM in total.
The police believe the mastermind
is the “Most Wanted” Yip Kwok-foon.
Bro foon, you're unbeatable!
But shit has hit the fan!
I told you to put more newspaper underneath!
Look, there's blood everywhere!
Take it, jerk!
Shit has really hit the fan!
I can give you 20% tops. Sorry.
We agreed on 40%.
Don't you have moral principle?
You're paying $2M for $10M's worth of swag?
We used to get 50%!
Now you fences are getting it all!
We're getting shit!
Time has changed.
The cops are on the prowl!
Especially for your swag, Bro foon!
It took us 2 years to fence it last time!
Stocks, real estate,
and even chestnuts are more profitable!
Do me a favor.
40%.
Bro foon, you always have your way!
How about you find another fence?
If I can't take it, I doubt others would dare to!
Fuck you!
Open the safe!
Are you robbing me?
Don't make me do it.
Thanks so much, Bro foon.
Don't look me up in the future.
There's no more business between us!
We go separate ways!
Light, Bro foon.
Fisherman!
Don't worry.
These ships belong to Yi Fa.
What's Yi Fa?
Yi Fa from Panyu, Guangzhou.
They smuggle electric appliances.
So pompously? So brazenly?
They have strong backing. It's legit!
A TV set sells for $2K
in Hong Kong and $8K in China.
They earn millions of dollars in each transaction.
Cash keeps rolling in!
Used notes with no consecutive serial numbers.
I need them today!
You have $80M over there.
I want it by 5pm!
You go get it. I want it now!
Manager Shum, how much do we have?
Manager Fok!
We are in love but can't be together.
I wait day by day but you never come back…
I want to forget you but you haunt my memory.
Mr Cheuk,
let's discuss the price.
Was it a bit flat?
No way! Let's start over!
Red face,
red skirt, red scarf,
like white paper…
I said let's start over. Didn't you hear me?
Let's not waste time!
Mr Tycoon,
we agreed on $3 billion.
That's final.
It's impossible to get so much cash
out of the blue.
I've only got $500M on hand.
Did I say you could go?
Take the $5OOM now.
Don't get too greedy.
Then I'll give you back half of your son.
You want the upper or lower half?
Do you really think I won't call the police?
Do the cops know where your son is?
All they can do is arrest and torture me.
But after 48 hours, they have to release me.
By that time, however, you son will be…
Call the Commissioner of Police!
I said let's start over. Didn't you hear me?
You hear me, or not?
If you can't hear me with your ear,
I might as well cut if off, OK?
Please don't!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You should've said so earlier.
What's up?
The Commissioner didn't answer?
You're playing me, right?
Let's play it all the way then!
Leaving so soon, Officer Wu?
Mr Tycoon is looking for you.
Mr Tycoon, didn't you call the cops? Come here!
Mr Ho.
They are sending these dogs after me,
but they are useless.
No wonder it was easy to kidnap your son.
So, you are willing to confess?
Officer,
if I said I'd fucked your mother,
did I really fuck her?
Shouldn't you ask Mr Ho where his son is?
My son…
is all right.
I came here to borrow money from Mr Tycoon.
Is that a crime?
Mr Ho, tell us if he's threatening you.
We can arrest him right away!
No, he's not.
Have you heard it loud and clear, Officer?
I said he's not threatening me!
Calm down, Royal Hong Kong Police!
Mr Tycoon,
how much will you “lend” me?
$3 billion.
Are you in Guangzhou for business or leisure?
Excuse me?
Business? Travel?
Yea, I am a businessman.
Guangzhou Railway Station
I'd like to reserve a private room
at 8pm tomorrow.
My name is Chen. Thank you.
Hello, Commander.
8pm tomorrow at Fengman Restaurant.
Who the fuck am I? I'm Chiu.
Don't make me fucking wait for you.
That's it.
Fengman Restaurant
Almost there, Mr Fong.
OK.
Which room?
OK. Coming.
- Take it.
- What?
Take it. Let me put the tie on.
Da-bao. This way.
Mr Fong.
Where's the vase?
It's just a cheap one.
Never mind. Let's go.
Chief Chen.
This is Zhang Da-bao, Boss Zhang,
who has bought Yi Fa.
This is Chief Chen from Industry and Commerce.
We're buddies.
Nice to meet you, Chief Chen.
Nice to meet you.
Let's have a drink.
Let's drink together.
Have a seat.
Bottoms up!
Boss Zhang cannot drink?
I said bottoms up!
Yes!
Bottoms up!
Da-bao is my buddy.
We've only met quite recently.
But we hit it off right away!
Chief Chen,
please help him.
This vase must be expensive!
Just a modest gift.
Here's how it works:
when Chief Chen grows tired of it,
Boss Zhang can buy it back!
It's worth at least RMB¥300K!
Didn't we agree on RMB¥200K?
I got the price wrong?
Oh, even Homer sometimes nods.
No way!
Chief Chen is a connoisseur.
What do we know?
If Chief Chen says RMB¥300K, then it's RMB¥300K.
Come get the business license tomorrow.
I'll have it nicely framed for you.
Thanks so much, Chief Chen.
We're buddies.
Boss Zhang, what would you like to eat?
Braised pork with preserved vegetables.
That's too oily for me.
Let me order.
Shall we have a seafood platter?
Let me order it.
Waiter!
Mr Zhang, best of luck with your business!
Thanks a lot.
Cheers.
Bottoms up!
This guy plays golf every Sunday
in Clear Water Bay.
One-way road. Quiet. No phone signal. It may work.
Hey! Where's our rice?
Next.
This one is easy.
A super playboy.
Drunk every night.
He recently has an actress as a mistress.
Hey!
Where is our rice?
Rice? Give me a second.
Your rice is coming right away.
Sometimes he would send his driver away.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Enjoy your food.
Close the door.
Sir, please follow me.
Give me a cup of tea.
Hey! Haven't you gone to the bathroom just now?
- Wait! Don't puke.
- Hey! The rice is cold!
Give me a second.
- I'm sorry. The rice is cold?
- I want tea.
- Hurry up!
- Tell me the room number…
- I want tea.
- Give me a second. I'll show you the way.
Sure, I'll get you tea.
Give me a second. I will be right back.
Take it easy.
We came to China to shake off those cop dogs.
You went too far last time!
I live life to the full.
C'est la vie.
There's no other way.
We've stolen cars, committed burglaries,
and robbed cash vans.
We even kidnapped the tycoon's son.
Should we do more kidnaps?
What do you have in mind?
Spit it out. We can discuss.
I'm a mountaineer.
After conquering one mountain,
I need to find a higher and harder mountain.
That's it.
Before finding that mountain,
let's find the money first.
Let's keep doing it.
Cheng, 53 years old.
No children. His wife is in charge.
A mobile phone used to cost over RMB¥10K.
Who could afford that?
Not everyone is a child of
a high-ranking official.
Now the cheaper, the better.
We have a population of 10 million.
Say RMB¥1K a set,
RMB¥10K for 10 sets.
We will be fatter than Chow Yun-fat!
Beepers are already outdated.
OK, I'll talk to you later.
Excuse me, Boss.
Please go on.
Don't give us a hard time.
We're doing small business.
Big Bro, these kids are great.
The guy who came in first
has criminal record in Hong Kong.
Don't know why you brought him here.
I told you to bring some decent-looking guys.
They all look like criminals and idiots.
You should be out of business.
What is he staring at?
He is smart and helpful
I don't want the guy in blue either.
You only need two men this time?
Take the others to broaden their horizons.
Got it!
Let me see to it.
What are you fucking looking at?
You, you, get lost!
Stop drinking and scram!
You two come with me.
Faster.
So slow!
Big Bro Chiu,
Wang Lei.
Hong Qi.
Say Big Bro Chiu.
Big Bro Chiu!
They understand Cantonese?
Of course!
Come have a drink.
Spruce them up before sending them to Hong Kong.
Sure will!
Motherfucker.
Sit and eat.
Commander,
who's this Big Bro Chiu?
Who cares if he is Big Bro Chiu or not?
He is a douchebag.
He is a sly,
old fox who changes identities.
He looks fucking like Kwai Ching-hung,
the invisible King of Thieves in Hong Kong.
Kwai Ching-hung disappeared
after killing cops.
Then Big Bro Chiu popped up.
Big Bro Chiu is just a name.
Is Fai here?
Fai.
What's up?
- Someone is looking for you.
- Hey.
Bro Coke?
Hey!
She's Thai?
Noon, go buy a dozen of Cokes.
When did you come back?
Just now.
You are too kind. Come in and have a seat.
Did you just speak Thai?
Do you think I speak French?
You stink!
Really?
Bo.
How can you be so rude?
Come help set the table.
Dinner will be served soon.
Naughty girl.
Go wash your hands.
I did wash my hands.
You ate yesterday. Are you going to eat today?
Bo, slow down. Don't rush.
Bro Coke.
You want some?
Shall we share it?
Don't let her drink it.
She was coughing.
I don't wanna spend money on meds.
I wasn't coughing. I just had a fever.
It's all right to have a sip.
Not coughing? You are being cheeky!
I say no Coke.
Fai, I'm not gonna eat. I'm running late.
You're going now?
Yes.
Be a good girl.
Bro Coke, dig in.
She's not eating with us?
She has to work night shift.
She's a legit masseuse.
Eat some barbecued pork.
Bo, eat some veggies.
You seldom eat veggies.
Shall we go to Ocean Park?
Shall we ride the roller coaster?
Shall we fly higher and farther?
Tickle, tickle.
Stop making noise, or the landlady will be nasty.
She's nasty because you haven't paid the rent.
You're being cheeky. Come down.
What a dragon lady, arguing with your father!
This girl plays too much! Wear your slippers.
Have you finished your homework? Homework first.
Quick!
- I'll spank you.
- Good girl.
This naughty girl!
I've quit smoking.
Quit?
"Whoring, gambling, drinking, roaming…
and smoking are the hobbies of a king."
Your mantra.
I'm on dialysis. I have to quit.
Told you you're impotent.
You feel dizzy when you squat.
Fuck!
What have you been up to?
What can I do?
I used to do temporary construction work.
Now I'm a full-time babysitter.
What about you?
Me?
I sell this in China.
People won't use beepers anymore.
Every Chinese will own
a mobile phone in the future.
One sells for RMB¥1K, 10 for RMB¥10K.
I'll be fatter than Chow Yun-fat.
Fat with loads of money?
Great.
You're doing great. You're becoming a boss.
Going straight is better than going astray.
We're not fierce enough to be Kings of Thieves.
All we did were some petty crimes.
Our life was insecure. We couldn't sleep well.
And we didn't earn that much.
So what's the point?
I'd like to stay here for a few days.
What?
I can sleep on the couch.
What's that for?
Take it. It will lessen your wife's burden.
Dad, I can't find my school manual!
Dad, Dad.
Coming!
That's fine
(Gold shop)
(Jockey Club)
Panyu Yi Fa Market
30 sets of 29-inch TVs. RMB¥12K apiece.
Plus 80 VCD players. RMB¥4K a piece.
RMB¥680K, thank you.
You pay me RMB¥700K.
I will notify you once the goods are delivered.
Next.
RMB¥30K for Chief Chen. Please count it.
Business License
RMB¥30K. The amount is correct.
Will notify you once the goods are onboard.
Please extend my thanks to Chief Chen.
My VCD player is broken.
I'll give you a new one. Kam.
Yes.
The latest 33-inch TV set.
Good stuff.
I'll give it to you, too.
Thanks so much, Boss Zhang.
You're welcome.
Gui, Guang, a 33-inch TV set and a VCD player.
Sure.
Da-bao Electronics
She is greedy.
That's business.
Don't pull a long face all daylong.
Boss Zhang, Boss Zhang.
No worries. They will take care of it.
- Quick
- What's wrong?
Boss Zhang.
What's wrong?
Something wrong with the goods?
No, close the door.
Close the door.
Want to play tough guy? Call your wife now.
Call your wife now.
Tell your folks you're OK, asshole.
If you kill me, you won't get a cent.
Are you threatening me?
Cheuk, be patient.
If he doesn't talk, don't give him food or water.
You're so noisy.
Hey, what are you doing?
Get him back! Get him back!
This is the gold shop.
Usually there's a police wagon at the entrance.
Jockey Club is across the street.
We keep a close eye on the police wagon.
As soon as it leaves at 8pm,
we rob the gold shop right away.
It's the racing night. It will be crowded.
After it's done…
- There's not much money in this.
- Follow me closely.
What did you just say?
You've committed big crimes.
Why pick this small gold shop?
Yes,
I've heard the 3 Kings
of Thieves would join forces.
At least millions of dollars will be involved.
What 3 Kings of Thieves?
Say it!
Bro foon, are you making a comeback?
This time with Cheuk Tze-keung
and Kwai Ching-hung.
The 3 Kings of Thieves are collaborating?
Someone has seen you three meeting in China.
Where did you hear this?
Everyone is saying that.
And you believe it?
Didn't Big Bro say you couldn't
make money by toting guns?
If I'm Kwai,
I don't have
to eat lunch boxes with you.
Idiots.
That's ridiculous!
Yip is all noise and fury.
Kwai is hush and shush.
We are so different. How can it work?
Smuggle more goods with me.
Let's make more money together!
Got it.
Brilliant!
Sometimes I feel like toting my gun again.
Robbery! Robbery!
That's so cool!
You call that cool?
Big Bro wielding AK-47 is cool!
Not like this.
AK-47 recoil is powerful.
Don't hold it.
Press it.
Stand firm.
Shoot the hell out of him.
What the fuck?! Join me
or go home and eat shit.
Big Bro Chiu,
how much can we earn from robbing this gold shop?
You're calling or not?
If the 3 Kings of Thieves join forces,
even if we open a fish ball stall together,
we will create a stir, right?
What shall I call our stall?
Are you calling your family or not?
Hey, wake up!
Gold depository?
Racecourse?
Kidnap Hong Kong Governor Chris Patten?
The Head of Hong Kong and Macau Affairs, Lu Ping?
No way.
What are you listening?
The 4 Heavenly Kings singing on stage together.
What are they singing?
I can't hear a thing. What's so good about it?
When the 4 Heavenly Kings sing together,
it's terrific no matter what they sing.
Water, give me water.
I will make the call.
How's my husband? I beg you!
He's not in good health. Don't hurt him.
We are not as loaded as it may seem.
Mr Cheuk, can you let my husband go?
Name a price. I'll pay you from my own pocket…
Hello?
I have $80M in cash.
Is it OK?
$80M it is!
Find Yip and Kwai!
What the hell?
The 3 Kings of Thieves
join forces for the first time.
It will be terrific no matter what we do!
You don't even have a plan yet,
and you want 2 wanted men around you?
You know I will
come up with a plan!
This is the mountain I'm looking for.
Himalaya!
Having night snack?
There's Coke in the fridge.
OK, I'll get it myself.
Fai, how long is your friend staying?
3 or 4 nights.
We have a daughter.
I don't feel comfortable…
with a guy suddenly staying with us.
What does he do?
He sells mobile phones.
Don't worry.
Go to sleep.
OK.
I'll go to bed after sewing.
I will arrive with clients in 3 minutes.
Got it.
Gui, Guang, unload the goods. Be quick.
Big Bro, we have a situation!
Panyu Customs!
Kam! Kam!
Chung, pull over!
Take a look over there.
Take a look again over there.
Don't move. Hands on your head.
Let's go.
What about Kam?
Find Mr Fong.
Chinese customs
Comrade.
What do you want?
We're looking for Chief Long.
We're wondering
if he can discharge the Lianhuashan goods and men?
We know Mr Fong.
In 4 days, the goods will be confiscated
and the men will be executed.
Yes, we understand.
Chief, someone wants to see you.
OK.
Chief Long is busy today.
Come again tomorrow.
All right. Yes…
Chief Long is not seeing guests today.
Come again tomorrow.
Asshole.
Who do you think you are?
You don't want to save Kam anymore?
Yes, yes.
Chief Long said he wanted to talk over dinner.
Find a restaurant and wait for him.
Good.
Fengman Restaurant.
Hello?
I am in Fugui Restaurant with Chief Long.
Coming right away.
Let's go.
Remember to bring a vase.
Take the vase.
Quick!
Okay!
Hurry up!
Chief Long of Customs.
He's my buddy.
Chief Long, nice to meet you.
I'm an official but you made me wait!
Sorry,
I went to Fengman Restaurant.
Is the food there edible?
He knows nothing about food!
Chief Long is a foodie.
Yes, you're right.
Chief Long, he's my buddy.
Help him this time.
Thank you.
He's your buddy, not mine.
I only help my friends!
If we hit it off, we're friends.
I'm hungry!
Let's order first.
Yes, let's order.
What would you like?
Braised pork with preserved vegetables.
It's not refined enough for me.
Let's order delicacies.
Waiter!
Thanks a lot.
What's your name?
Boss Zhang.
Boss Zhang, right?
You're a fun guy! A fun guy!
Thank you.
Chief Long, thanks for your help.
Let's sing karaoke first.
OK, karaoke first.
Chung
Give me name cards of karaoke bars and the phone.
Let's go for more fun.
I can't…
Let's take a bath.
It's good to take a bath.
Find a sauna.
Don't forget the vase.
Yes.
Chinese customs
Thanks to connections,
I didn't need to rot in jail.
We stayed in a motel,
with a bed, TV, OK food,
though no whores!
It's not bad, huh? What do you say?
Yes, yes.
Asshole, you didn't need to carouse
with those officials!
Don't complain about carousing,
for money's sake.
Hey! Come here.
Our goods!
Come.
Your goods are here.
Take a look. Any problems?
Thanks so much.
Let me take a look.
Sign here if there's no problem.
Thanks so much.
OK.
Your mole hasn't found Kwai's dossier
in the police station?
No news about Yip in China?
What about his underlings? His fences?
His fellow illegal immigrants? His village mates?
Can't find them?
Nothing at all?
Good.
Fuck you!
The cops have offered a $1M reward on him.
But there's no news over these years.
Give me some time.
Reward money is a good idea.
The cops offer $1M; I'll up it to $10M!
If it's not enough, then $1OOM!
I'll set up a special phone line.
Whoever knows their
whereabouts will get the money.
So brazenly? The cops will tap the phone.
Those assholes will prevent the 3 Kings
from meeting up.
Not necessarily.
The cops want them too.
They will send loads of people after us.
Find a way to shake them off.
Hello?
Are you Cheuk?
Yes.
Noon tomorrow. Bring a purple umbrella
to Temple Street.
I'll have you picked up.
Get on.
Take off your clothes.
Take them all off.
I worked with Kwai once. He's so average.
I know Yip. He lived in Guangdong.
Kwai's real name is Xing Zhennan.
His ancestral house was built by me.
Yes.
OK.
I drove for Yip and was chased by the cops.
I fenced for Yip.
I was present in Yip's every heist.
We wielded AK-47 together.
Mr Cheuk, I envy you. I admire all your works.
Yip bought sex from me.
He was loud and proud.
Heists? Hong Kong kids?
These barking dogs are sneaky wussies.
I imported the Chinese
retired soldiers to Hong Kong.
What did I teach them before a heist?
Moral principle!
Father of the Chinese retired soldiers,
can you cut to the chase?
Do you know Yip or Kwai?
Don't interrupt me when I talk.
If I talk too fast, you won't understand!
Where was I?
Moral principle.
I once brought 3 Mainlanders
to a showdown with the cops. Bang!
One of them, Wei,
was so scared he dropped his gun!
You know what? I rushed to save him!
He owes me a lot.
Know who Kun-xi is?
Yip's former boss?
Quincy is Wei's godson.
Want to meet him?
'MM'.!
You better check him out thoroughly.
Check me out? Motherfucker.
It's just $1M.
Act fast.
Quincy will stand in front of you tomorrow.
Give me the dough.
Hey.
Thanks so much!
Let's go have some fun?
Are you tight in cash lately, Taishan Boy?
How can 3 pieces be enough?
Guns are for firing, not for sniffing.
Our commander taught us: safety first.
Have you sniffed that Cheuk
is looking for Yip and Kwai?
Mr Cheuk says he wants to meet those two.
Look, he has set up a special phone line.
Info for money.
How generous!
Both of them are very dangerous.
Which kingpin is not dangerous?
They are being so brazenly?
The Handover is imminent.
Because the Handover is imminent,
you have to do big!
After the Handover,
it will be slim pickings, Idiot.
Listen.
Sniff out their whereabouts.
The restoration of this
Association depends on you!
Keep me posted, kiddo.
Keep me posted!
Stand still, sir.
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
Home.
Your ID, please.
Bo!
Why didn't you come home right after school?
I told you so many times.
Where have you been?
We've been looking for you everywhere.
Bro Coke, you should've told us beforehand.
- I thought I was on my way.
- You've scared the hell out of us.
Shut up!
Still drinking? Bad girl!
What happened?
She's naughty.
Teach your girl at home, not on the street.
- I'm sorry.
- You've frightened her.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Let's go home.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry.
Darling.
Daddy loves you.
My good girl.
3 Days!
Chief Song helped us recover the goods in 3 days.
Chief Song, my buddy!
You rock!
It's incumbent on the police to maintain order.
Boss Zhang,
can you do me a favor?
Go!
Let him vent his anger.
Stop!
Chief Song, you're a tea connoisseur.
Enough.
I need you to do me a favor.
What do you mean?
They are the sons of my ex-commander's friend.
Forgive them.
Give me face.
They robbed me.
What have you lost?
They robbed me! Me!
We're good buddies.
Who do you think you are?
A pet it bourgeois!
A greedy, smuggling, tax-evading pet it bourgeois!
Don't think too highly of yourself.
We're good buddies.
Take them away!
Shoot him,
I'll act according to the law!
Great, there's a vase in the toilet…
We're lucky…
It's small but it will do.
We're good buddies.
RMB¥2M, thank you!
I receive RMB¥1.3M from you. Thanks.
I'll notify you once we have the goods.
Next.
Take your time.
It's insane!!
Everyone out.
Get out!
It's insane!!
What happened?
Bro foon, Cheuk has gone mad!
He set up a special phone line to look for you.
Inspector Wu.
You're difficult to tail.
I had to wait here for you!
I caught this guy for you.
He said you gave him $1M for Kun-xi's whereabouts.
Is it a crime to look for someone?
No.
But have you checked him out?
He's been in jail for 20 years.
The phone numbers back then only had 6 digits!
He's out of touch now!
Out of touch?
If I go to China, Wei will pick me up!
Wei?
He was shot dead two years ago!
Kun-xi betrayed him!
Have you been conned?
I can arrest him now if you have.
An eye for an eye.
That's moral principle.
Calm down!
I'm very calm.
Or I'd have kicked you too!
Want to report the crime?
If not, I'll let him go.
Well?
If not, I'll let him go!
Get lost!
- Are you assaulting a police officer?
- Don't play tricks.
So what? Motherfucker!
Don't give up,
keep searching for him.
The Royal Hong Kong Police relies
on your phone calls.
Why don't you just drop it?
Don't ruin your impeccable record.
I'd help you if I could!
Even if you were to hit me,
I must say it's a dead end!
I know, I know!
We've come to the climax of tonight.
The last leg of the Triple Trio.
The $170M jackpot pool.
Plus the total bet amount. A single winner
can collect over $300M.
Many horse racing fans are placing bets.
The whole city is abuzz!
A single winning ticket will make
you richer than any kings.
See if you can win.
Bets are placed on Wind Chaser.
Gold Weather is the horse least expected to win.
The odds are 99.
Win & Place.
Motherfucker, almost $400M in the pool.
Hong Kong citizens are robbed by the Triple Trio.
What does Triple Trio mean?
The $170M jackpot pool
has attracted many fans queuing
to place their bets.
No more clothes pegs?
No.
Go get some in the room.
Sure.
The race is about to start.
The $170M jackpot pool.
A single winner
can collect over $300M!
Who will be the lucky one?
A dark horse will increase the size
of the betting pool.
The horses are in the stalls and ready to go.
Which horse will take off first?
It's Wind Chaser.
It runs faster and faster.
The rest can hardly catch up.
Go'. Go'. Go'.!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
No one wins. The warehouse
must be filled with money.
Big Bro Chiu.
Hey.
Mr Cheuk, you know who Kun-xi is?
It's Kun-xi speaking.
Look me up in Guangdong. I won't let you down.
You're really quitting? It's a cushy job.
You're telling me!
Talk to Big Bro yourself.
I have invested all I got in the goods.
You already know all those officials
and connections well…
What did you say?
Fisherman!
Yes, Bro foon.
Give me Cheuk's number.
Bro foon.
You got something to say?
No.
Give me the number!
Sure.
Fuck! Thought I would be famous overnight.
What a waste of time!
Fame is not an issue.
I can't just go back empty-handed.
Not to mention having to chew this bread here.
Big Bro Chiu,
coming to Hong Kong has not been easy for us.
We can't just go back like this.
Big Bro Chiu, you really want us to leave?
If you guys have something big in mind,
count us in!
We can do anything.
I can keep a secret.
If you say you're Big Bro Chiu, then so be it.
I understand. Don't worry.
I know the rules. It's between you and me.
We have moral principle.
Share it.
Seriously, we can make it work.
The 3 Kings of Thieves join forces…
Mind your own business.
Aren't you on dialysis? Still smoking?
Old habits die hard.
Are you still angry with me?
You're planning to rob the gold shop downstairs?
I thought you're paying me a visit.
You're here just for the location.
Listen to me…
No more!
I treat you as my brother. You treat me as a fool!
I never treat you as a fool.
Forget it! Just shut up!
I have a wife and a daughter now.
My life is great.
Can you leave my family alone?
I'm in the wrong this time.
You know it's hard to make a living.
We're sworn brothers.
I owe you this time.
Forget what happened these past few days.
Keep it to yourself.
I'll leave early tomorrow morning.
You won't see me again.
Uncle Coke.
Not in bed yet?
Guangdong province
Sai Wan Container Terminal, Hong Kong
Mr Cheuk,
I've heard so much about you.
Where's Yip?
Let me show you something.
This way.
Mr Cheuk. How's your journey?
I'll treat you to something special.
Shrimps and crabs are local specialties.
After food we'll find two shampoo girls for you.
This way, please.
Type 54 pistols, grenades, AK weapons.
I've got all you want.
Where's Yip?
The truck outside holds a ton of dynamite.
Bang!
You can blow up whatever you want.
Where's Yip?
They were all retired soldiers.
They're fearless veterans in battles!
I want Yip!
Coin!
Give it to me!
Big Bro, let's think it through.
We're doing all right.
Why go back to our old business?
Are you lecturing me?
We're making money!
We can't be robbers for the rest of our lives!
You do it!
You have struck a deal with the Fisherman!
Big Bro, he was just thinking out loud.
Leave if you want!
I won't stop you!
Do you know what time it is? You don't sleep?
Go fuck yourself!
Fuck you!
Come down!
Yip has retired!
He used to be my man!
Am I not a better partner?
Who the hell are you?
Hello?
Hello, Cheuk.
It's Yip Kwok-foon speaking.
Are you kidding me?
Why should I believe you?
I am who I am!
If you don't believe me, let's meet up!
Wait. Got another call.
Fuck you!
Wait for what? Hello?
Hello?
Hey!
You are dead!
Go up!
Hello?
Speak!
Are you Cheuk?
Who's speaking?
Kwai Ching-hung.
Need my help?
Are you kidding me?
Do you have any proof?
I robbed Tung Shing Watch in 1986.
I killed 3 plainclothes
in 1988.
And Landmark in 1992…
Wasn't it Yip who robbed Landmark in 1992!
Don't be so gullible.
Jumbo Watch in 1994
and Lucky Guy Jewellery two years ago.
I did them all.
Do you think only Yip had AK-47?
He loved to be on camera
and the cops were dumb.
- I just took advantage of the situation…
- Hold on! Don't hang up.
What did you just say?
Fuck you!
Are you playing me?
It's you, Yip!
Landmark in 1992, Jumbo in 1994,
and Lucky Guy two years ago.
Are you responsible for all?
No!
I never did my jobs in clandestine!
Why should I hide myself?
We're all here.
Where are you right now?
Hong Kong!
I'll call you when I'm back in Hong Kong.
Hello?
Kwai Ching-hung, you still there?
Yes.
Where are you?
Hong Kong.
Call you when I'm back in Hong Kong.
Let's talk later.
Motherfucker! The 3 Kings
of Thieves have nothing to do with you.
Since you're here,
you can't bail without leaving something.
Yes.
There's less than $10M here.
Mr Cheuk's life
worth at least $100M!
Put your guns down!
Retired soldiers? Go!
Car key.
Car key!
You think I'm bullshitting?
If you don't treat me as your Big Bro,
let's split!
Big Bro, we always follow your orders.
You said “drop the guns,” we dropped the guns.
Is that very hard for you?
No, we always follow you, Big Bro.
We support you no matter what!
Are you looking down on me?
I stoop so low that I need your support?
I don't need you!
You're just my followers!
Hey you!
What are you fighting for?
Sorry, we're tourists.
We got lost, so we quarreled.
The residents upstairs filed a complaint.
- Where are your IDs?
- Here.
We planned to take a boat to Macau
but got lost here.
We couldn't find the pier.
So we quarreled.
Call the station.
PC1844 calling the station. Send.
Quick!
Don't let him flee!
Motherfucker!
He's in the front!
Go after him!
Hello? Uncle Dog, I've found them.
Believe it or not, they called me up!
I even got a whole ton of dynamite!
It will work this time. Get me a boat.
I have an idea!
We'll blow up the Handover ceremony!
We can threaten either the British queen
or the Chinese government.
It will create a stir for sure!
What the fuck!
The night snack is here. Back yet?
Coming back.
We're at the entrance
to the complainant's building.
It's quiet. No one's here. OVER.
Be civilized. Don't talk too loud.
If you go to Macau, take the ferry in Sheung Wan.
This is Sai Wan.
Oh.
Go to the main street and take a cab.
Take a cab!
Mainlanders are numskulls.
Quick!
Mainlanders?
I'm Yip Kwok-foon!
Military Police
Waiter.
Sir, have you reserved a table?
I booked a room under the name of Chen.
Give me a second.
Mr Chen. Please follow me.
This way, please.
Hey.
Where is our rice?
Rice? Give me a second.
Your rice is coming right away.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
Mr Chen. This way, please.
Hey! Haven't you gone to the bathroom just now?
Wait! Don't puke!
Are you all right?
I thought you went to the restroom.
Why are you here?
I'm sorry. This way, please.
We are super busy today.
- Hey!
- This way, please.
The rice is cold!
Give me a second.
- I'm sorry. The rice is cold?
- I want tea.
Give me a second. I'll give you another bowl.
- Quick!
- Tell me the room number. I'll look for it myself.
- I want tea.
- Give me a second.
Sure I'll get you tea.
Give me a second. I'll be right back.
We should not forget you.
And we should watch with the closest interests
as you embark on this new era
of your remarkable history.