When Mrs. Mcsing was in laDour...
A pan appeared in tne Sky.
it flled along Garden Street...
Tumed left, and stopped
at the Beefball King.
rs an
Co I4-,@I re | .
it first arrived at the Market Building...
Lingered a bit...Correction:
it flled over the railway, turned right...
And headed directly for the Bazaar.
it filed on...
At last coming into the matemity ward.
There, on the right hand side of
Mrs. McBing.
y -
Ce ) L-,e! oO | = | |e ia | 2 | re Z- Cc e.
The pan stayed.
Mrs. McBing,
convinced that this was a miracie,
Thinking of her soon-to-be-born son.
Piease make him
a clever and smart boy!
The pan diant seem to hear her words.
So Mrs. McBing amended her wish:
y >
‘ Tene THT & Slat JU IOCOOlaGlt(
Or maybe...
Or make him really handsome.
As handsome as Chow Yun Fat or
Tony Leung!
The pan diant respond.
Virs. Mcping, in panic...
rier boy needed not to be
smart or handsome
As long as luck be with him!
it's nice to depend on oneself...
Of course Chow and Leung are
lucky guys...
Sut then they are smart too!
Finally, the pan dropped to the fioor...
Mrs. McBing,
believing her wish granted...
Thought that was magnificent
But what had the pan granted her?
A smart boy? A lucky boy?
ra ' _
To commemorate this, Mrs. Mcsing ...
Decided to name he r er an MecNificient.
i name nim McDulll
i am the boy, no more MeNilficient...
mm McDuill
“My School"
On dear,
your caives nave grown strong.
ive been desperately...
looking for a schooll
Why not try the one...
at the Emporium?
The Spring Flower Kindergarten’?
Yeani The one at the junction... ...
Right next to Sliver City Food Mall.
The Spring Flower Kindergarten!
Only 10 minutes walk from
the MTR Station!
Spring Flower Kindergarten,
good environment...
With white teachers for English class!
White teachers for English class?
Yeant
Spring Flower offer white teachers!
"We are all Nappy cniidren...-
We sing everyday!
we leam as we grow...
"We are the flowers of spring!”
This piggy kid in a rabbit outfit...
Who doesnt look the least
like Chow or Leung...
Thats me, McDuil.
This is my kindergarten.
The headmaster came from
the countryside...
As a result, ne speaks with an accent.
ror many years...
| had difficulty hearing him.
- fart = arti
- Duck dumpling! - Duck aumpiling!
- [ne 97 Rule... - [ne 97 Ruie...
Shall be replaced by the 98 Rule!
Good, children!
We are snaring an important issue...
this morning:
Children, have you handed In
the school fee?
L371 OGLL INUY Lllwve WW LtG@e.
You mignt conciude tnat
this Is a shabby school.
But, for me and my mates...
This Is the most beautiful paradise!
.. Also, there is Miss Chan.
Who adores us in
her absent-minded way.
Aiso, she is a Faye Wong wannabe.
Actually, Kelly Chan will do!
- McmMug! - Present!
- Fail - Present
- Goosiel - Present!
- Darby! - Present!
- May! - Present!
- June! - Present
- May! - Present
- McmMug! - Present!
May!
Miss Chan, I've been called twice!
Oops!
Good morning, sir!
Good day, sirt
- Fail - Present
- Darby! - Present!
- May! - Present!
- McmMug! - Present!
- Goosiel - Present!
Fave | missed anyone?
MCDull:
riey, | dont understand...
| keep feeling that...
someone Is calling me.
Dont think that I've been daydreaming.
i was contempiating something academic:
' >
nH rey 1 Ae oes | Ig | su | | | ve Se > I i ‘Oo @¢
i mean, | ate 6 oranges that morning...
And my stomacn wouidnt stop.
Then | ate 3 bananas this moming.
Again my stomacn wouiant stop...
it just woulant stop!
Fiow are these two things related’?
There are so many things that
I don't understand.
Rut | am not atraid.
One day, when | finish kindergarten...
i snail move up...
And get my degree.
When | graduate from university, | know...
i snail understand everyining!
Ana tnen ...
i will Duy my mother a house!
LJtuet PL IGGULIIGelo!. TULIS 4G LEG@eLeliU.-«-
Which we kids frequent after class.
- Fishbdall noodle, please.
= No noodle left.
- FisnbDail rice noodie then.
= No fishbaill left.
- Chicken wing noodle then.
= No noocie left.
- How about fisnball congee’?
= No fishbail left.
Nothing left today’?
- How about beef noodle’?
= No noocie left.
Again’?
- Fried chicken wing with fishball...
= No fishbail left.
Hey, fishball and noodle are both gone...
You cant combine them witn other things.
Can't combine them?
(rent tL GOS GiGmit
- A bowl of fishball then.
= No fishball left.
- A bowi of noodle?
= No noodle left.
By now...
you can probably tell now smart | am.
Nothing worried me, all things were fine.
No fishball left? Let's get some noodle.
Shoot, Dulll
Watching myself grow and grow...
Everyday...
| feel Tull of strength!
The word is beautitull
There is a song Miss Chan loves...
Whicn | always want to lear...
But it just comes out different.
You mean
“All Things Bright and Beautiful"?
Yes, all are fine!
All things on earin...
They are finell
"My Motner”
1 eed, 0, fans
No pain no gain!
Monday till Sunday... No pain no gain!
Tne middieaged swine Is Mrs. Mcsing,
my moitner...
A brilliant woman...
Calrying the world!
Yes, sne is reaily something.
she works in insurance,
real estate and trading.
At the height of IT,
she even sets up her cooking site...
www. VvirsMicsing.com
Offering brilliant dishes.
Welcome to"Mrs. Mc Can Cook".
Today were doing a simple dish,
Paper Chicken.
Tne ingregient: a cnicken Dun.
Slowly, we tear the paper away
from the bun
Now we Nave a Dun paper.
Tum the paper over like tis...
Voila! Simple, isn't it?
Tnank you, everyone!
row time flies since last episode!
Now we snail do a Paper Bun.
The ingredient takes oniy a paper.
D6 it like this...
And we nave a Paper Bun.
isn't this a lovely bun’?
A novelty today for everyone:
Chicken Bun Paper Bunning a Bun.
First, unwrap tne cnicxen
from the paper.
Now we Nave a paper and
a piece of chicken.
Use the bun paper to wrap up
the chicken like this...
And then wrap It like tnis...
The delicious Chicken Bun Paper
Bunning a Bun!
Sucn a simple dishi
See if the chicken is good!
today's aisn...
Bunning a Chicken Bun Paper...
Bunning the Paper Chicken.
it takes simpie WOK.
Use tne cnicxen Dun to DUN...
Then use the chicken Dun paper to...
Dun ang DUN...
Paper, Dun, bun, paper, Dun...
Paper, chicken, bun, DUN, CnicKken...
Sut my motner has Ner tender side.
Every nignt,
she tells me a story before sleep.
Once upon a time, a boy lied. One day...
se cle.
Once upon a time, a boy studied hard.
rie grew up and got ricn.
Once upon a time, a boy was naughity.
One day...
=e twisted his ankie.
Mother, | want to sieep.
Once upon a time, a boy siept a lot.
Next day...
se cle.
Tnat is my mother's direct approacn.
-ier love for me is direct.
Fer expectation of me is direct.
For ner, itis always...
“no pain no gain’.
But there are things that
simply cannot be gained.
Days come and go.
Talking about Chow look-alike...
You still think it's going happen’?
When it comes to luCcx...
The lottery numbers tnat
mother obliges to draw...
railed even to Dring her one centi
As for being smart...
i did try hard, Dut then...
But then, | stil have dreams.
"My ideal Worid”
Maldives, a worid outside our WOrid.
The sky Diue, clouds wnite,
the trees tall and water bright.
The colourful worid of the tropical sea.
The primitive ocean of primitive energy.
Experience a worid that
knows no boundary!
Enjoy a trip to your ideal worid.
Sriliiant touring Agency,
license no. 350999
Mother, you know where Maldives is?
-low far’?
You need to fiy there.
Mother will you take me there?
One day when | am rich.
When will you get rich?
in my dream!
Good morning, sir!
Good day, sirt
Where is your favourite place?
My favourite place is Japan.
They have Disneyland and
Hello Kitty Land.
1 Dougnt my Nairpin there.
My favourite place is Canada.
Grandma and my uncies live there.
My favourite place is Bangkok.
They have water sports and
shark's fin soup.
My favourite place is that...
Whats-ts name.
They nave Fun World and Food Mail.
Their chicken rice fills you up.
Right, that's Silver City Centre.
They serve huge bowis of rice.
As for the place | most want to go, wow!
There, the sky Is Diue,
clouds white, the trees tall...
Rise and snine, Kiddo.
Oh?
Take st »me medicine and he'll be fine.
Nol
Need he not wnat for the medicine?
No! I'll give him a snot.
A shot?
nH e's . of e:) f-,8 me re | ots :
is he scared of dying?
row are you doing? Take the medicine.
Piease motner, no.
i dont want the strawbelry drink!
You wont get weil witnout the medicine.
Sweetie, we will go to Maldives once
you get well.
Really?
nH F> Ss | ii ot | e m:) 1e | | eC / 6.) (e. "eo?
Now, drink up.
Yes, Maldives!
Mother, when will we go?
i will DooK the ticket once you get well.
Come on, drink up!
Look, mother!
mother, | am welll
But you've taken everytning edibie
at home.
You see, the whole bottie was filled...
And | guiped it down bit by Dit...
| cia iti
Now | am a good boy!
What?
When are we going to Maldives?
| v Fe] C ves?
You said we wouid go once | get weil.
Maidives, where the trees tall and
water bright...
Thos > WO ras have flare.
| am happy for you.
Motner, yOu promised...
Wed go to Maldives once | get weil.
i meant once | get ricn.
No, that wasnt wnat you mean.
You said we'd go once | get weil.
You promised!
Now stop crying.
we will go to Maldives.
- Really? - Yes.
When?
Once | get rich.
Sut you are ricn.
Sure, sure, | am rich.
We will go next week, ok?
This is McDuill.
riey, i'm leaving tomorrow.
- Yes... - Is that right?
wn e | [@,@, 6 We | / AO; =] Ze / Ss | ve wa | ® e" 4
eo it so!
We couldn't bring our own food, right’?
Still chatting away’?
You need to pack.
Teil them I'm going to Maidives tomorrow.
Where tne trees tall and water Drignt...
riey, you!
Coming]
i need to pack now. laik to you later.
See youl
Moiner, do | need to Dring
my birth certificate?
And school report?
Wow, I'm saved!
| found my birth certificate!
Motner, you keep it and dont lose It...
y
Leave on the moming, retum at nignt.
Motner said thatd make things wortny.
Hence...
The most beautiful day
in my childhood experience...
| ad - ™ = -
Do you think paper is
a good chicken wrapper’?
Maybe.
if only for one small piece.
- Goodnight, mother! - Goodnight
The Fiong Kong...
windsurfing athlete San San LI...
Flas just won the first gold medal
In Hong Kong history!
San San, when confirmed her winning...
Told reporters that ner result...
rielp proves tnat
Hong Kong athletes are horrible...
Excuse me, it should bDe"nonourabie .
riong Kong athietes
are honourable athietes.
End of special report.
Then, mother seemed inspired.
rianasome, lucky, smart...
So much for those plans.
Now how about something physical’?
“Looking for Logan”
And so, wnile one dream lingers on...
Anotner one begins.
= -
"aka: Fiow Does a Calf Become a Calf?"
i know It Is not easy.
| know It is not easy to find Logan.
| know it is not easy for him to take me in.
Nio matter how cifticult this is...
Logan will be my master!
i shall get an Olympic medal
Cheung Chau!
You raised San San,
now you will raise me!
When | receive my Olympic medal...
Cheung Chau, | finally make It here.
i must kiss this Noly lanai
Kiado, this is Lamma isiand.
Lamma Island?
Where Chow Yun Fat grew up?
i came into hiding on this isiand...
To stay away from the paparazzi.
And so many Kids came to seek me out.
So I came to live here.
You want me to be your master’?
rorget Iti
You city kids are ail spoiled...
Good for nothing!
You want to get an Olympic medal too?
Dream ont
Kiddo, look!
This calf...
So thick, so strong]!
Ang so muscular!
Witn steely veins running down...
riair sticking out like wire...
And those tougn toenailis!
riow many hilis must It travel...
riow many seas must it pass...
riow mucn pain must it Dear...
6) ‘Oo -¥: cal rf | RECO ii es g cal 1 ¢
i shall have this call
Master:
Can | take a pee?
Whenever | sing this song, | need to pee.
Taking a pee first would not help.
Sut | must sing it now.
Witn this song, | hope...
Logan will think better of me.
Logan will be my master!
The song goes like fnis...
"Big bun, nave two more..."
"Forget about indigestion.”
“Eat the bun, grow a calf..."
"respect my motner.—
“Eat the bun, toughen my caif...”
“serve my country.”
"Big bun, nave two more..."
"Forget about indigestion.”
Logan looks strange after the song.
i must grab my cnance.
Master! Piease De my master!
y
O po e' a ii e | AT | ee / | e eS | oO reve i
Get up...
Thank you master!
Silly, help me get up.
My calf has gone numb!
| tell mother wnat happened today.
she won't say a word...
| <7 t ste | Pte | ‘OC a | 2678 | - ve | | re Ke | .
At ainner,
mother offers 3 glasses of wine...
Oranges and the chicken to
the ancestral tablet.
she mumbles something when...
we pay our respect to our ancestor.
As mother pours the wine on the floor...
She says in her solemn, tender voice:
Be good,
iearn with the master and
honour the ancestor.
In honour of my master,
mother throws a banquet.
As | am the last disciple of the master...
Everyone on Cheung Chau comes.
San San Is In training and couldn't come.
All my mates are tnere too...
Sringing scnooi report,
medals and big buns.
They nope Logan will take them in aiso.
After the soup, the ceremony begins.
Mother pours a cup of tea and
| offer it to the master.
After all the hardship looking for Logan...
Now | can windsurt together with
San San!
i offer the tea to Logan...
rie arinks tne tea ana
becomes my master.
All the guests look happy.
And everyone from
Cheung Chau applauds.
Thank you for honouring me!
in my life, | have two skills that
I'm proud of.
One Is windsurfing.
That | have passed onto San San.
Tne otner, | snail pass onto
my new disciple...
Can you tell us what skill is that?
Tnat is...
Bun snaicning!
Bun snatching?
“Bun Snatching",
for our uninformed audience...
is a unique Cheung Chau tradition.
Eacn year, in the forth month,
Cheung Chau people...
Set up 3 stacks of bun to celebrate.
Stacks of bun?
Literally speaking...
A stack of bun Is a stack of many buns!
Eacn stack coming up to 6, / storeys.
imagine now hign tnat Is.
Bun snatcning is to snatcn those Duns!
When the time comes,
hundreds of youth would rush up...
The higher the bun you snatcn,
the more blessed you are.
And the more praises you get.
in 1978, 2 stacks tumDied down,
hurting many.
"Bun Snatching” was thus banned!
And the unique tradition Is lost.
The Olympic medal...
it has slipped away.
Every Saturday,
I'd take a ferry to Cheung Chau...
To practice Dun snatcning.
Agame with no medal,
no competitor, no competition...
A game nobody knows of.
A game witn no bun to snatcni
All | do is to go to the master's home...
My win
Keep going, lazy bone!
One day, San San arrives!
san San, my idoll
seeing San San...
Makes me forget all these weeks’
hard work.
San yourseifl Work!
You hear me?
So San San leaves without seeing me.
in despair, | crawi up the sheif.
i have had a lot of things said to me...
But"San yourseit”...
~~) 4-) 8 2,-J] (9) £- 2
iam quitting!
Today Is the first ime
| sit down with Logan.
rie must De around 50,
with a baby face.
Eresh from the oven!)
This thing...
Wr g t C oes | ft | reve ¢ | | | Ke?
Logan then proceeds to teil me a iot...
His ambition, his expectation of Dull.
rie says neil teacn all he knows to Dull.
The more Ne taiks,
the more excited he gets.
rie tells me windsurfing
is not his strongest.
riis strongest is reaily bun snatcning...
something combining Fist,
ritual and gymnastic.
rie says Dun snaicning Is
his lifelong achievement.
Move your feet!
| OOK!
This calf... so thick, so strong!
Ang so muscular!
Witn steely veins running down...
riair sticking out like wire...
And those tougn toenailis!
riow many hilis must It travel...
riow many seas must it pass...
riow mucn pain must it Dear...
6) ‘Oo -¥: cal rf | RECO ii es g cal 1 ¢
Mviy son...
Your son, he will get this caif.
i have no idea wny wouid Dull needa...
SI l re | aca if
But, looking at those steely veins...
| am reminded of Dull's pa, Bing.
The electronic dictionary
cannot be found.
Could it be that...7
so mother has been using the dictionary?
But why is she writing in English’?
Motner must nave transiated It
word by word.
i use the macnine to turn it back
Into Chinese.
It is addressed to
the Olympic Committee Chairman.
"Dear Chairman"
“Flow are you? | am fine.”
"Vou like bun’? | like bun!"
"we Fiong Kong peopie here love Dun.”
"Bins of all sort.”
“Dear friend,
it Is Important to snatcn Duns.”
"It is a game, no joke.”
“One needs energy,
and many night congee.”
"in my stupid opinion...—
“snatching bun is an Olympic game."
"And there will be peace.”
"Do you have children’?”
"| Nave a boy, Dull.”
She's talking about mel!
"Me Is a good boy.”
"One day,
| can see him snatching buns..."
"Ending up snatcning
an Olympic medal."
"That Is the biggest comfort
a mother can get.”
“Let the world know
the talent of your children.”
“Parents will do anything for that.”
~ [Nat is wny | write you this sudden letter.”
"Although you dont know
humble things like me."
"But my boy is Dig, very Dig.”
“One day, you will know him too."
“Thank you for your cooperation."
“Yours faithfully, Mrs. Mc"
After reading mother's letter...
i go back to Cheung Chau to practice.
bk ot | e+e. U Se 20 S: s] | | Se | | .
i dont know why | want to snatcn a Dun.
And | don't think it will ever become
an Olympic item.
Sut | keep learming.
Because | love my moiner.
Master thinks my crawiing has passed.
Now I'll learn the
"42 Bun Snatching Hands".
Master says these 12 hands,
in its prime...
Was mucn admired by Butcner Lin!
Later, | learn from McMug...
Butcher Lin was a disciple of
the great Kung Fu king.
i dont know mucn about Kung Fu Kings...
Sut | must be the ultimate port...
The pork that struts about
My mind boggles as | practice, after all...
| am not a fan of bun snatching.
| am only doing this for mother.
rience | Nang on...
Step by step, claw by claw...
| make it pass
the"12 Bun Snatching Hands".
“There is no deformity,
but saves us from a dream"
This is Dull.
Dull the Dig guy, not Dull the boy.
The two Dulls have different voices,
and then...
Dull the boy's worid is still filled
Filled with hopes.
riope... Disappointment...
riope...
Disappointment.
On and on, he became Dull the big guy.
Sut | snail tell more about Dull the boy.
Dull the boy hoped a iot.
rie hoped there WAS a Santa Claus.
And he hoped to eat a Christmas turkey.
Rignt, | havent eaten any turkey tnen.
Everyining about turkey...
The sparkling tinkling Christmas tree...
Like stars falling from the sky...
Coming down by the fireplace.
Eacn slice of meat looks purer than snow.
Right in front of us...
Tne aroma attacxs Our Soul...
Waking even the guardian angeis.
Who fioat around the aromatic and
holy dish...
Floating in the Christmas night, floating...
All this about turkey was
only my Imagination.
i nad never eaten a turkey.
Motner claimed turkey was too Dig.
The two of us would never finish it.
One Christmas we celebrated with
roast duck.
| was really, really disappointed.
Another year,
she bought a mini-oven at 60% off...
At a ciloseaown sale.
Tnanks to tne oven...
Motner decided one day...
We would go shopping for a turkey.
On the way home, with turkey in hand...
That was the happiest moment in my life.
The turkey was ready.
Following moiner,
with salt on both hands...
| rubbed the turkeys thick cnest.
wien sewing up...
some of the stuffing...
i cried: the turkey's stomacn wont stop!
We managed to stulf the turkey
into the oven.
24tn, December
Rising smoke stirred the stars with
a crunchy smell.
it was like early blessing from the angels.
such a beautiful night!
Mothe -and me sat at the st patront.
Lignts snimmered on the sea.
Beautiful and gente.
So beautifull
i had never tasted anything so strong.
Cup noodles or roast duck
were not as strong.
The taste embedded
every single taste bud...
Then exploded.
Like everytning tonignt...
Most beautiful, brilliant, and tender.
| woke up late tne next day.
The sweetness was still there
after washing.
There was only corn soup for lunch.
| idly found diced turkey...
in the soup.
That night finally came the long awaited...
Christmas turkey dinner!
slices of meat,
accompanied by guard and potato...
Were dressed witn soy sauce.
It was an exciting,
satisfactory moment for us.
The following week,
turkey sandwich for breakfast.
Sunday,
| boldly suggested eating out.
Mother said | was ungrateful...
But took me out anyway.
Then mother got inspired again.
What was left of the turkey was sliced...
Witn me helping out at times.
it was not easy to get rid of...
tne turkey's smeil.
ried noodle witn siiced turkey, yummy.
Steaming chestnut bow! with
sliced turkey.
Peanut congee witn turkey bone.
Paper turkey Dun.
Paper turkey paper Dun.
Turkey pete with bread.
| shoulant Nave said anything about
the turkey's stomach.
Came Dragon Boat Festival,
when | dug into the dumpling...
And found more pieces of turkey...
| iost it. | cned.
Oh please!
When mother finally disposed of
the turkey...
it was already half year later.
My beautiful dream ended with
my nightmare.
Later, | learned tnat...
A serving turkey needs only be raised...
Eor a few months.
The time tne turkey spent with us...
Was in fact longer than Its life.
| realized aiso, witn turkey...
Taking the first bite Is all it matters.
Afterwards,
it is jJust"be over and done with it".
i am no pnhilosopner.
| could not come up with any profundity.
Sut, sucn thougnts...
After | grew up...
On days unrelated to Christmas...
Did come up again a couple of times.
Once, it was at my wedding.
Once...
it was at my mother's cremation.
That day, | was looking at
the smoke rising up.
Suddenly, the smeil of
the turkey returned.
i regretted | made mother
threw the turkey away.
“special Report”
‘special Report”
Olympic medal winner San San L!
will compete again...
To prove to the worid tnat...
Aiso...
The local federation...
Officially announced today:
HK will apply to host the Asian Games.
Response from
all sides has been enthusiastic.
Among them,
the Bamboo Game Association...
is proposing Mahjong for official game.
While Tearoom Serving Groups...
nave VOWESG...
To campaign for" Tart Throwing”.
As for the Cold Cut and
Roasting Association...
They Deileve...
"Duck Fianging”
would make an ideal addition.
More interesting,
CIC Insurance Is joining force with...
Children from...
Spring Flower Primary School...
in support oT...
"Bun Snatchino"...
A game thougnt extinct.
in tne ena...
Nothing came of anything.
" fart Throwing”
was chosen as the highlight.
As for the official slogan...
"HK, One Big Tart" was a logical choice.
Then San San Li lost.
And the hosting right of
the Asian Games...
Went to a piace Fiong Kong peopie
have never heard of.
Tearoom workers,
those aspiring athletes...
Went Dack to wnere
they used to throw thelr tarts.
Everyining went on as usual.
In secondary scnool,
| stopped practicing the 12 hands.
Sometimes, when | went out with mother...
Then they stopped seiling buns.
Carts were replaced by ordering sheet.
Everyining came to nothing.
At times, I'd go to Cheung Chau
for barbecue.
-or environmental reason...
They d changed to snatcn piastic buns.
Master thougnt they stunk.
On Cheung Chau
was a Cheung Po Tsai Cave.
Where legend ciaimed
the pirate hid his treasure.
As i was tne one wno couidc craw...
My mates said | should take a looK and
maybe get rich.
So | crawied along the dark and
narrow cave.
Crawiing.
There was nothing Dut a Dox.
i opened tne Dox...
inside, there was an unfinished bun.
Maybe the pirate didn't get to finish It.
"eatng 6 buns last night..."
“oil left me hungry.”
"Eating 172/b white bread last night... “
“Excelied 6 sets of steps
when | was young..."
“sill left me empty.”
“Brought up San San
when | am old! Still..."
Bun in nand, | suadeniy realized...
There are things that cannot be forced.
Ano is a no.
No fishball, no noodle, no Maidives...
No medal, no pirate’s treasure.
And the pirate took no bite.
Stupid is not funny.
Stupid leads to failure...
To aisappointment.
Disappointed is not funny.
Fatness is not funny too.
Fatness is not powerful.
Power doesnt mean yes.
Sun in nand, | suddenly thougnt...
Growing up, facing this sordid world...
This not so dreamy, not so funny world...
"aa NOtnINg snail be donel”
"| Have Grown Up”
“Fat, Still"
Right, | am McDull the Dig guy.
rat, with raw power.
Not doing too weil.
Negative property.
With a pair of really thick calves.
Very muscular...
Witn steely veins running down.
As | oO | | e | ‘oe na | s...
i got Dored one time and stared at It...
Theyre tough, no Kidding!
Yes, the story ends nere.
This Is a try.
Error... Ify...
No guarantee that one would make It.
in tne ena...
Zero gain? Not really.
i have my calves.
Sut, standing nere like tis...
Wien tne waves nit...
| feel great.
You see, smart guys like me
don't really know...
Fiow to make a lesson out of
his own story.
Witn caives in water...
When the wind bDiows, I'd tink...
oF
| rf ii otr e meet C | Se 2 ii e | | ke | Ig | Ss...
She'd be happy.
ve come up witn a lesson!
Mother got inspired after
her dot com failed.
She published a cookbook.
The last recipe was"Roast Chicken".
A simpie aisn no less.
mi@ obey PBie\- -
ingredient: cnicken.
Tnat way, you Nave a roast cnicken.
Tnere was a remar<x in tne COOkKDOOK:
if you want a delicious chicken...
A cnicxen that wouldnt upset you...
The secret is: please, roast it welll
Tnank you!
One Regular, please.
What's a Regular’?
The same as Special.
What's a Special’?
A Quickie is a Lunch.
What's for Lunch?
The same as Supper.
What's for Supper’?
Same as Regular.
we'll nave tne Reguiar.
Our Regular today Is fantastic!
sorry, Regular is gone.
We can have the Special.
What's a Special’?
A Special is a Lunch.
What's for Lunch?
What you get for Supper.
What's for Supper’?
A Quickie is a Regular.
But you said Regular is gone!
Feguiar sure is gone.
How about the Special?
it's the Special, then.
sorry, Special is gone.
Mother, let's have the Quickie.
A Quickie is a Regular.
What's for Regular?
A Regular is a Luncn.
What's for Lunch?
Same as Supper.
And Supper’?
supper is like Special.
But you said the Special is gone.
The Special sure Is gone.
Try Quickie. It’s the same.
We'll have Quickie.
sorry, Quickie is gone.
This fs too mucni
is there anything we can eat here?
Try the Luncn. It's fantastic!
-low so?
it's like the Supper.
What about the Supper’?
its like the Regular.
And what about the Regular’?
The Regular is gone. Isn't that fantastic?
LJIoau ¥ve eve aa Gas E.
Sorry, Lunch is gone.
Try our Supper. It's all the same.
'm not having supper
under board daylight!
What's In a name’?
is the same as Lunch.
Great! Whatever you say!
And make It quick!
You want it quick? Try Quickie!