When Mrs. McBing was in labour…
A pan appeared in the sky.
It flied along Garden Street…
Turned left, and stopped
at the Beef ball King.
Correction:
It first arrived at the Market Building…
Lingered a bit…Correction:
It flied over the railway, turned right…
And headed directly for the Bazaar.
It flied on…
At last coming into the maternity ward.
There, on the right hand side of
Mrs. McBing.
Correction: Left hand side.
The pan stayed.
Mrs. McBing,
convinced that this was a miracle,
Made a wish…
Thinking of her soon-to-be-born son.
Please make him
a clever and smart boy!
The pan didn't seem to hear her words.
So Mrs. McBing amended her wish:
Or make him a smart businessman?
Or maybe…
Or make him really handsome.
As handsome as Chow Yun Fat or
Tony Leung!
The pan didn't respond.
Mrs. McBing, in panic…
Made a final amendment:
Her boy needed not to be
smart or handsome
As long as luck be with him!
It's nice to depend on oneself…
But luck is essential still.
Of course Chow and Leung are
lucky guys…
But then they are smart too!
Finally, the pan dropped to the floor…
Mrs. McBing,
believing her wish granted…
Thought that was magnificent!
But what had the pan granted her?
A smart boy? A lucky boy?
Or a Chow look-alike?
To commemorate this, Mrs. McBing…
Decided to name her son McNificient.
No! It's better to be humble!
I'll name him McDull!
Dear all…
I am the boy, no more McNificient…
I'm McDull!
"My School"
Oh dear,
your calves have grown strong.
I've been desperately…
looking for a school!
Why not try the one…
at the Emporium?
The Spring Flower Kindergarten?
Yeah! The one at the junction…
Right next to Silver City Food Mall.
The Spring Flower Kindergarten!
Only 10 minutes walk from
the MTR Station!
Spring Flower Kindergarten,
good environment…
With white teachers for English class!
White teachers for English class?
Yeah!
Spring Flower offers white teachers!
"We are all happy children…"
"We sing everyday!"
"We learn as we grow…"
"We are the flowers of spring!"
This piggy kid in a rabbit outfit…
Who doesn't look the least
like Chow or Leung…
That's me, McDull.
This is my kindergarten.
The headmaster came from
the countryside…
As a result, he speaks with an accent.
For many years…
I had difficulty hearing him.
- Tart!    - Tart!
- Duck dumpling!    - Duck dumpling!
- The 97 Rule…    - The 97 Rule…
Shall be replaced by the 98 Rule!
Good, children!
We are sharing an important issue…
this morning:
Children, have you handed in
the school fee?
Yes!
Great! Now move to class.
You might conclude that
this is a shabby school.
But, for me and my mates…
This is the most beautiful paradise!
…Also, there is Miss Chan.
Who adores us in
her absent-minded way.
Also, she is a Faye Wong wannabe.
Actually, Kelly Chan will do!
Roll call now.
- McMug!    - Present!
- Fai!    - Present!
- Goosie!    - Present!
- Darby!    - Present!
- May!
- Present!
- June!    - Present!
- May!
- Present!
- McMug!    - Present!
May!
Miss Chan, I've been called twice!
Oops!
Good morning, sir!
Good day, sir!
Back to roll call.
- Fai!    - Present!
- Darby!    - Present!
- May!
- Present!
- McMug!    - Present!
- Goosie!    - Present!
Have I missed anyone?
McDull!
Hey, I don't understand…
I keep feeling that…
Someone is calling me.
Don't think that I've been daydreaming.
I was contemplating something academic:
How does this universe work?
I mean, I ate 6 oranges that morning…
And my stomach wouldn't stop.
Then I ate 3 bananas this morning.
Again my stomach wouldn't stop…
It just wouldn't stop!
How are these two things related?
There are so many things that
I don't understand.
But I am not afraid.
One day, when I finish kindergarten…
I shall move up…
And get my degree.
When I graduate from university, I know…
I shall understand everything!
And then…
I will buy my mother a house!
Our headmaster runs a tea stand…
Which we kids frequent after class.
- Fishball noodle, please.
- No noodle left.
- Fishball rice noodle then.
- No fishball left.
- Chicken wing noodle then.
- No noodle left.
- How about fishball congee?
- No fishball left.
Nothing left today?
- How about beef noodle?
- No noodle left.
Again?
- Fried chicken wing with fishball…
- No fishball left.
Hey, fishball and noodle are both gone…
You can't combine them with other things.
Can't combine them?
- A bowl of fishball then.
- No fishball left.
- A bowl of noodle?
- No noodle left.
By now…
you can probably tell how smart I am.
Nothing worried me, all things were fine.
No fishball left? Let's get some noodle.
Shoot, Dull!
Watching myself grow and grow…
Everyday…
I feel full of strength!
The world is beautiful!
There is a song Miss Chan loves…
Which I always want to learn…
But it just comes out different.
You mean
"All Things Bright and Beautiful"?
Yes, all are fine!
All things on earth…
They are fine!!
"My Mother"
1,2,3,4,5,6,7…
No pain no gain!
Monday till Sunday… No pain no gain!
The middle-aged swine is Mrs. McBing,
my mother…
A brilliant woman…
carrying the world!