Hey, let's go
I'm happy as can be
Let's go walking
You and me
Ready, set
Come on, let's go
Over the hill
Across the field
Through the tunnel we'll go
We'll run across the bridge
And down the bumpy gravel road
Right beneath the spider's web
Ready, set, let's go
Hey, let's go
I'm happy as can be
Let's go walking
You and me
Ready, set
Come on, let's go
The foxes and the badgers, too
All come out to play
They all want to explore
The deep and wonderful woods all day
Look at all my many friends
Ready, set, let's go
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
-Dad, want some caramel?
-Thanks. How you doing back there?
-Fine.
-Are you tired? Oop!
-—Mmm-mmm.
-We're almost there.
Mei, hide.
Whoops. | thought
that was a policeman.
Hi!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hello there. Are your parents around?
We're your new neighbors.
Great. Thanks.
Hello! Hi, we're the Kusakabes'!
We're moving in down the street.
Why don't you and your family stop by?
MAN: Sure. Good to meet you.
Uh!
Hey, thanks a lot.
(WATER RUNNING)
This is it, girls.
(GRUNTING)
-Wait up!
-Here you go.
Mei, look at this bridge.
A bridge?
There's a fish! Oh, look!
There's another one!
S50, how do you like the new place?
Dad, it's perfect.
Look at this. A tunnel of trees.
Oh, wow! Look!
(GIGGLING)
Dad, hurry!
Wow! It's creepy.
Creepy!
-It looks like it could be haunted.
-What, haunted?
(CREAKING)
Whoa.
(GRUNTS) Whoa.
Look. It's rotten.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING)
-It's collapsing!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(WHOOPING)
(GASPS)
-Mei, look at that.
-Huh?
Look.
-Wow! It's huge, isn't it?
-Ah-choo!
(LAUGHING)
(DOORS SLIDING)
Dad, what's that big tree?
Uh, that's a camphor tree.
-A camphor tree.
-Camphor tree!
Don't forget to take your shoes off, girls.
Huh?
Whoa!
An acorn.
Let me see.
Another one!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Here's one.
Out of the way, Mei.
| can't close the door with you there.
Acorns.
Dad, acorns are falling from the ceiling.
Falling from the ceiling.
Hmm.
Maybe squirrels live here.
-Squirrels?
| think rats eat acorns.
Maybe they're rats.
-No! Squirrels are better!
-Ew!
Mister, where do you want your radio?
Oh, right, the radio.
In here's good, | guess.
-Satsuki, open the back of the house?
-Okay.
-Can you find the back door?
-Of course!
(GIGGLING)
Come on!
Hey, wait for me!
Well, hurry it up, then.
(GASPING)
(WHIMPERING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
-Let's go.
-Hmph!
-The bath.
-Yep.
| think they're gone.
(GASPS)
Hey, you found the bath.
something's running around in here.
-More squirrels?
-| don't think so.
They're not bugs or mice. They were
black and they were all over the place.
Hmm. Let's have a look.
-Ah.
-So?
It's probably just some soot gremlins.
What do you mean, “gremlins"?
Like the ones in my book’?
Well, tt could be ghosts,
but ghosts don't usually like
to come out on nice days like this.
Normally, you can't see soot gremlins,
but once in a while,
when you go from bright places to dark
ones, you catch a glimpse.
So that's It.
Come out, come out...
BOTH: Wherever you are!
BOTH: Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
(WHOOSHING)
(LAUGHING)
Hey, | need your help.
It looks like somebody's hidden
the stairs to the top of the house.
What?
Can you find the stairs and open
the windows up there?
Yeah!
Wait for me!
(GRUNTING)
Nope.
The toilet!
Not here.
-Nothing here.
-Nope.
(LAUGHING)
Ahh!
Nope.
Nope. Hey!
(CREAKING)
Mei, | found the stairs.
(GASPS)
It's pitch-black.
Maybe it's the soot gremlins.
An acorn.
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
(RUSTLING)
Hmph.
BOTH: Ahh!
We know you're in here, soot gremlins.
Come on out.
(GASPS)
Hey!
Huh?
KUSAKABE: (GRUNTS) Okay, lift.
Dad, come here! There's definitely
something weird in this house!
That's great.
I've always wanted to live in a haunted
house ever since | was a little boy.
BOTH: Ohl!
Ahh!
(CRASH)
(SHRIEKS)
| caught one! Satsuki, look!
-Ah!
-Oof!
Hi.
(SHRIEKS)
Mei?
(PANTING)
Oh.
Whoa. Hey!
(LAUGHING)
What a ball of energy!
This is our neighbor.
She takes care of this house.
ohe said you can call her
"Granny" if you'd like.
I'm Satsuki, and that's Mei.
Nice to meet you.
Well, it's nice to meet you, too.
What nice manners you have.
I'm sorry | didn't have time
to clean up more before you got here.
KUSAKABE: No, it's fine.
GRANNY: We've been busy
in the rice fields,
but | did manage to keep the place
well-dusted, aS you can see.
Mei, your hands are filthy.
What on earth did you do?
| caught a soot gremlin, but he got away.
Ahh! Your feet!
(GASPS)
Mine are black, too!
Ah...
You've got soot sprites in your house.
Soot sprites? The black puff balls?
About this big?
They scurry everywhere
when you enter a room?
That's right.
They live in old, empty houses
and run all over the place,
covering everything with dirt.
| used to be able to see them
when | was your age.
SO you've seen them, too.
That's very interesting.
90 they're a kind of ghost, then?
Don't worry, dear.
They're nothing to be afraid of.
lf they decide you're nice people,
they won't harm you,
and after a while, they'll just go away.
| bet they're up in the rafters right now,
having a talk about whether
or not they should move out.
(JABBERING)
-Hear that? They're gonna move out.
-| don't want them to leave.
What if a huge one
came chasing after you?
So what? I'm not afraid.
Right. Then you can go to the bathroom
alone in the middle of the night.
(LAUGHING)
Come on, girls.
Let's get to work.
Who'd like to fetch water for the pump?
ll go get it.
Il go, too!
(LAUGHING)
Mei, wait there, okay?
Did you catch a fish?
(GRUNTING)
(SQUEALING)
Granny, the pump's working!
Keep pumping!
Don't stop until the water gets cold.
Okay.
(LAUGHING)
Oh. Hello again. Can | help you?
Eh... My... mom said
to give this to Granny.
Oh. What is it?
-—Mmm.
-Hmm?
Mmm! Eh...
Hey, wait! What is this?
ls that Kanta?
Hey, you in there!
-Your house is haunted!
-Kanta!
VMimm.
(MEI GIGGLES)
(LAUGHING)
Satsuki, | acted just
like that when | was a boy.
| hate boys, but I'm glad he brought
this cake you made.
It's great, Granny.
(KUSAKABE LAUGHS)
Eat all you like.
SATSUKI: Thanks, moving man!
MEI: Thanks, moving man!
Thanks for everything, Granny.
-Good-bye, Granny!
(CHOPPING)
(WOOD CLATTERING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(CREAKING)
(POTS RATTLING)
Dad, this house is too old.
| think it's gonna fall down.
(LAUGHING)
That would be a problem,
since we just moved in here.
(LOUD CRASH)
Huh?
(SHUTTERS RATTLING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(HOOTING)
(GASPS)
(HOOTING CONTINUES)
(LAUGHING)
Everybody, try laughing.
Then whatever scares you will go away.
(LAUGHING)
But, Dad, I'm not scared.
What? I'm not scared.
(LAUGHING)
(ROARING)
(SHOUTING)
(LAUGHING)
BOTH: One, two, one, two, one, two.
That's it. Stamp that dirt out, girls.
That's It.
Okay. That's all the chores.
-You're done.
-BOTH: Yay!
Ready? Hold on!
Who-o-oa!
(GIRLS SHRIEKING)
KUSAKABE: Whoo-ooo!
SATSUKI: Granny!
GIRLS: Hi, Granny!
KUSAKABE: Good afternoon!
Hello there, Kusakabes!
Where are you headed?
We're going to visit Mom at the hospital!
That's good! Say hi
Tell her | hope she's feeling better.
SATSUKI: We will!
-—Mmm.
-Vimm.
Hey, this way. Whoa!
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
Hey, Dad. There it is.
(DOOR OPENS)
-Good afternoon, ma'am.
-Hello, dear.
-VMommy!
-Hi, Mei. It's so good to see you.
Daddy kept geiting lost
the whole way here, Mom.
Oh, he did? No school?
No, it's a rice-planting day.
Oh, is that so?
Hey, Mom, Dad's talking to the doctor.
lam so happy to see you girls.
SO how do you like it in the country?
Have you settled in?
-Yeah.
-Hmm?
Mel's scared...
-A haunted house?
-VUimm-hmm.
Mommy, do you like haunted houses?
Of course. I'll have to get better soon
so | can meet some ghosis.
-See that, Mei?
-VUimm-hmm.
Mei was worried that you wouldn't
come home if the house was haunted.
-Do you two like it?
-Yeah|
I'm not scared at all.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, what cute hair.
Did you do this, Satsuki?
-Mmm-hmm.
-It's very nice, huh, Mei?
-What a lucky girl you are.
-Yeah, but she yells at me a lot.
-That's because you never sit still.
-Let's see your hair, Satsuki.
You sure it isn't a little too short?
No, | like it this way, Mom.
-Brush my hair! Brush mine!
-Wait your turn, Mei.
Your hair will never cooperate.
It's exactly like my hair
when | was your age.
Do you think it will
start cooperating soon?
| want it to look like yours.
(CHUCKLES)
| think it will.
You and | are a lot alike, Satsuki.
(INAUDIBLE)
-Mom looked great, didn't she, Dad?
-Yeah, she did,
her doctor said she should be able
to come home soon.
-SO she'll be home tomorrow?
-There she goes again with tomorrow.
Tomorrow might be a bit soon.
Mom said she was gonna sleep
in my bed with me.
| thought you weren't scared
to sleep alone.
Can't you sleep by yourself?
She's the one who's scared, not me.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey, Dad! Look, it's morning!
(GROANING)
-Umph!
-Hey, wake up!
(GROANING)
-Sorry. | overslept again.
-| have to take lunch to school today.
Oh, no. | forgot all about that.
That's okay. I'm making
lunch for everyone.
-Hey, it's burning!
-I'm coming. Just a minute.
I'm making this one for you, Mei.
| get one?
Mei, sit down and eat.
There you go. Wrap it up
so it stays fresh. Okay?
(SIGHS)
-Satsuki!
-That's Michiko.
Hi!
SO, you made a friend already, did you?
-Satsuki, time for school!
-She's walking to school with me.
(SLURPING)
| gotta go.
(DISHES CLATTERING)
see you later!
BOTH: Have a nice day!
Hi, Michiko.
-Hi. Ready for school?
-Yep.
(CHILDREN TALKING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(YAWNING)
Hey, Dad.
Do | look like a big girl?
You do. Are you going somewhere?
I'm just off to run some errands.
Dad, is it lunchtime yet?
What? We just ate breakfast.
Dad, you be the flower shop. Okay?
Hey, tadpoles.
(GIGGLES)
What a stupid bucket.
Huh?
Acorn.
Hal!
(GIGGLES)
(GIGGLING)
(GASPS)
Huh?
(GIGGLES)
(LAUGHING)
(QUICK STEPS)
Hal!
(GRUNTING)
(RIPPING)
Hey!
(LAUGHING)
Bleh|!
Ahh!
Hey!
(GIGGLING)
Ahh! Ahh!
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(SNORING)
(SNORING CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
Whoa!
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
(SNORING)
(MOANING)
(GIGGLES)
(SNORING)
(LAUGHING)
(SNUFFLING)
Anh...
Ah-choo!
(MEI GRUNTING)
(SNORING RESUMES)
(MOANING)
(CHUCKLING)
Who are you? A great big soot gremlin?
(GRUMBLING)
(ROARING)
(LAUGHING)
To-to-ro!
(INHALES)
Totoro?
ls that what your name is? Totoro?
(GRUMBLING) Totoro.
Yep, that's your name, all right.
Mmm. Totoro.
(MOANING)
(YAWNING)
(SNORING)
(MOANING)
(PLOP)
-Bye.
-See you later!
-I'm home!
-Hi there.
-Wow. Is it that late already?
-VWhere's Mei?
-Did she like her lunch box?
-We haven't eaten.
she's running around
with that lunch box.
Viel!
Mei?
(GASPS)
Hey, Dad! Come here!
| found Met's hat!
(GASPS)
Mei! Mel!
(MOANING)
Hmm? Hmm.
-Hey, Mei, wake up!
-Huh?
What do you think you're doing,
sleeping out here?
Totoro?
Where's Totoro?
Maybe you were dreaming.
-No, | saw Totoro.
-|otoro?
You mean a troll,
like the one in your storybook?
VMmm-hmm. But he called hisself Totoro.
He was furry, with a great big mouth.
There was a little one, and a bigger one,
and a huge one that kept falling asleep.
(SIGHS)
(TWIGS SNAPPING)
There you are.
(PANTING)
Wow. This would make
a great secret hiding place.
Dad, Mei said that
she saw a [Totoro here.
-A Totoro?
-VUimm-hmm.
This way!
(LAUGHING)
(BREATHING HEAVY)
Hey, wait up!
Huh?
-Here?
-VUimm-mmm.
Last time the tunnel led to Totoro's tree.
| didn't see another path to take.
Hey, where are you going?
SATSUKI: Mei, come back!
(LAUGHING)
Quit laughing! | really did see Totoro!
I'm not lying.
VMimm.
Mei?
It's not a lie, Dad.
Hmm. Don't worry, Mei.
satsuki and | believe you,
and | bet | Know what happened.
You must have met one of
the spirits of the forest.
That means you're a very lucky girl.
But you can't always see the spirits.
You can only see them
when they want you to.
Let's give the forest
spirits a proper greeting.
-A greeting?
-Of course. Come on. Let's go.
(GASPS)
Oh, Mei, you're getting heavy.
Dad, there's that big camphor tree.
It's incredible.
That's It!
SATSUKI: That's Totoro's tree?
MEI Yeah!
Come on, Dad! Can't you go any faster?
Whoa.
Totoro’s hole is gone.
-Are you Sure it was here?
-VUimm-hmm.
Dad, she says the hole disappeared.
Right now the forest
spirits don't want to be seen.
But, Dad, | want to see them, too.
Maybe you will, if you're lucky.
Mmm. Magnificent tree.
It's been around since long ago,
back in the time when trees
and people used to be friends.
When | saw this tree, | Knew this would
be a good place for our family to live.
And | think it will make
your mother feel right at home.
SO, let's give this tree a nice
greeting and go eat our lunch.
| want to write Mom a letter
and tell her about this.
-| will, too!
-Attention!
Thank you for watching over Mel
and making us feel so welcome here.
ALL: Please continue to look after us.
-Last one home's a rotten egg!
-Hey, no fair!
MEI: Wait!
-Uh!
-SATSUKI: Hurry it up!
Wait for me!
SATSUKI: Dear Mom:
We had an exciting day today.
Mei met a big forest spirit called Totoro.
| hope I'll be able
to see him someday, too.
(ROOSTER CROWING)
(CLUCKING)
(INAUDIBLE)
WOMAN: Kanta, hurry up,
or you'll be late for school.
Yeah.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(WHISPERING)
(GIGGLING)
(THUNK)
Back to work.
(LAUGHING)
Oh.
Mei?
Miss Hara!
Yes, Satsuki?
Uh, my sister's here.
CHILDREN: Her sister?
(CLAMORING)
-Granny, what's wrong?
-| don't Know.
she said she wouldn't stop crying
unless | brought her to you.
She said that? Mei, be reasonable.
You know you had to stay with Granny.
| have school and Dad's
teaching at the university.
| only have two more hours
of school to go.
Can't you just stay
with Granny until then?
she's been so good up till now.
Weren't you, Mei?
(SIGHS)
Well, I'll talk to my teacher
and see what we can do.
(LAUGHING)
satsuki's mom is in the hospital,
so her sister Mei is going
to stay with us today, okay, class?
-Let's make her feel welcome.
-ALL: Yes, ma’‘am.
-What are you drawing, Mei?
-It's a big Totoro.
ohh. Mei, try to keep quiet, will you?
VMimm-hmm.
(SIGHS)
(BELL RINGING)
CHILDREN: Bye, Mei!
MICHIKO: Come again soon!
| have to skip our club meeting, Michiko.
I'll let everyone know. Bye!
Hurry up, Mei. It's gonna rain.
Okay.
-Ah! Here it comes!
-Here it comes!
(SPLAT)
(GASPS)
Come on.
| didn't even cry. That's good, huh’?
Hmm.
Yeah, but we're not home yet.
We'd like to share your roof
for a while, sir, if you don't mind.
-—Mmm.
-Huh?
-Don't you...
-Vimm. Mmm!
Vimm!
Hey!
-That was lucky, wasn't it?
-VUimm-hmm.
-MEI: This umbrella has holes.
-Hmm.
(EATING)
(CLOCK CHIMING)
Dad left his umbrella here.
-| better take it to him.
-| wanna go, too.
What? | left It.
(SIGHS)
What kind of fool forgets his umbrella
at school when it's raining?
-Hey!
-| bet you were swinging it around
and you broke it.
No, | didn't.
(GASPS)
Ahn.
Hello! Is anyone home?
Oh, Satsuki and Mei. Come in. Granny!
Thanks for watching Mei today.
Sorry we couldn't keep her happy.
Oh. | wanted to give back this
umbrella that Kanta lent us.
What? He lent you this?
Oh, my. Look how beat up it is.
Mei was walking home
from school with me.
So, it was really nice of him
to help us out. Tell him thank you.
-He must have been drenched.
-That's okay.
Kanta is such a dirty kid.
He can always use a good drenching.
Are you off to meet
your dad at the bus stop?
-SATSUKI: Yes, he forgot his umbrella.
-Such good kids.
-Bye, girls.
-SATSUKI: Bye!
(GIGGLING)
(IMITATES AIRPLANE)
-Who was at the door, Kanta?
-Beats me.
(GASPS) There's the bus, Mei!
Are you getting on?
Drive on.
Satsuki, Dad wasn't on the bus.
He'll be on the next one for sure.
Do you want to go back
to Granny's and wait there?
(WATER DRIPPING)
What's the matter?
(SQUEAKING)
(SIGHS)
What is it, Mei? Are you sleepy?
| Knew this would happen.
Don't you want to wait at Granny's?
VMmm-mmm.
Its okay, Mei. He'll be here soon.
(SIGHS)
That bus sure is late, huh?
Here.
(GRUNTS)
(MOANING)
(GRUNTING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
(PLINKING)
Totoro?
(PLINK)
(GRUMBLING)
Oh, wait a minute.
Here. Try this.
Hurry. Mei's slipping.
(GRUNTS)
Hold it over your head. Like this.
(GIGGLES)
(SPLASH)
(SPLASHING)
(GRUMBLING)
(BELLOWING)
(THUD)
(SHRIEKS)
(DOUSING)
(ROARING)
(GASPS)
Oh.
Here comes the bus.
BOTH: Huh?
(WIND WHISTLING)
(YOWLING)
(MEOWING)
(GASPING)
(HUMMING)
(BELLOWING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
Well, Mei, so much for
bringing Dad his umbrella.
-Hi. Sorry I'm late.
-VWOMAN: Drive on.
My train was delayed,
so | had to wait for the next bus.
Were you worried?
Totoro came back, Dad! | saw him!
We saw a cat bus, too!
-What?
-lt was huge!
With eyes like this.
-It was great!
(LAUGHING)
| saw Totoro! | saw him!
| saw him, too!
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
(CROAKING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
-Hey, Dad, pick us up.
-Come on, Dad.
(GRUNTING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
SATSUKI: Dear Mom:
We had such a weird,
mysterious, spectacular day.
My heart ts still pounding.
Totoro gave us a wonderful present.
it was wrapped in a bamboo leaf
and tied with a ribbon made of grass.
As soon as we got home, we opened it.
It was filled with acorns.
(GASP)
Ahn.
(CHUCKLING)
“We wanted to grow a beautiful
forest with the acorns,
" SO we planted them
in your garden out back, but..."
SATSUKI. ... they just won't grow.
Mei watches them
all day, every day,
waiting for them to sprout,
it's starting to make her crabby.
Here's a picture of Mei as a crab.
(CHUCKLING)
Summer vacation is almost here,
and | can't wait to play
outside with you.
Please get well soon. Love, Satsuki.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Get ready, and... up!
(SHRIEKING)
(LAUGHING)
-Lights out, girls.
-MEI: Wait, Dad.
Do you think that
they'll sprout tomorrow?
| don't Know.
You should ask the Totoro.
He would know.
Good night, girls.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(BUZZING OF INSECTS)
Mel.
(GROANING)
That's where we planted the acorns.
(GRUNTING)
(GIGGLING)
(POP)
(GASPING)
(TOTORO GRUNTING)
(POP)
(GRUNTING)
(POPPING)
(GASPING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
ALL: Ahn!
GIRLS: Yay! We did it! We did it!
GIRLS: Yay!
(BELLOWING)
(HUMMING)
(SQUEALING)
(GRUMBLING)
(GASP)
(WHIRRING)
(ROARING)
(GIRLS ROARING)
(GRUMBLING)
Mei, we're the wind!
(INHALES)
(INSTRUMENT PLAYS)
(SECOND INSTRUMENT PLAYS)
(ALL MAKING MUSIC)
Mmm...
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
Where'd the tree go?
-Ahh!
-Ahnh|!
They're growing! We did it!
We did It!
(LAUGHING)
SATSUKI: | thought it was a dream!
MEI: But it wasn't!
BOTH: | thought it was a dream!
We did it!
Mr. Kusakabe? Telegram!
Vir. Kusakabe?
A telegram for you.
Huh. No one's home.
(TRAMPLING)
MEI: Granny!
I'm over here.
This one's ready to eat.
(GRUNTING)
(SNAP)
What about this one, Granny?
Try it.
(GRUNTING)
(SNAP)
Wow, Granny. Your garden
is just like a market.
We've picked enough,
haven't we? Let's take a rest.
Mmm. Nice and cold.
Mark, get set, go!
It's delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
They're very good for you.
They've soaked up lots
of vitamins and sunshine.
-Would they help Mom get better?
-Of course they would.
lf your mom eats my vegetables,
| bet she'd get well right away.
That's great, Granny.
Mom's coming home on Saturday.
she's going to sleep with me in my bed.
Oh, good! She's finally
leaving the hospital, is she?
No. The doctor wants her to get used to
the new house a little at a time.
-She goes back on Monday.
-ls that so?
We'll feed her lots of
my vegetables while she's here.
I'll give her the corn that | picked.
That will make her better.
-| bet that will do her wonders.
-Yep.
Here. The postman
left us your telegram.
A telegram?
What should | do with it?
Dad wont be home till evening.
Better open it. Might be an emergency.
VMimm-hmm.
“Please contact Shichikokuyama."
shichikokuyama!
It's from Mom's hospital!
something must have happened to her.
We have to get to the hospital
right away, Granny.
Okay. Calm down. First, we need to get
in touch with your father.
| Know his phone number at the
university, but we don't have a phone.
Kanta, take Satsuki to your uncle's
house and let her use the phone.
VMimm-hmm.
Mei, you need to stay here with me!
Mei, go back and stay with Granny!
Uh!
Hello? I'd like to place
a long-distance call, please.
It's to my dad at Tokyo 31-13-82.
Right.
Now, that’s a nice girl, eh, Kanta?
(RINGS)
Hello?
Yes.
Hello? | need to speak to my dad
in the archaeology department.
| mean, | need to speak
to Mr. Kusakabe.
My name is Satsuki Kusakabe.
Hello, Dad? Is that you? It's Satsuki.
-What's wrong?
-We got a telegram.
You're to call Mom's doctor at the
hospital.
What? The hospital?
Okay. I'll call them right away.
Did something happen to her?
Do you think she's okay?
Let's not worry.
ll call the hospital, and
I'll call you right back. Okay?
-Yeah.
-Wait by the phone.
-Mimm-hmm.
-| need to hang up now. Okay?
Excuse me, is it okay if | wait here?
My dad's going to call me back.
Of course. Make yourself at home.
Satsuki!
(PANTING)
(BLEATING)
Back off! Don't touch my corn!
It's for my mommy!
(BLEATING)
Too bad! She needs it
to make her better.
(BLEATING)
Mei, the doctor said
that Mom's not doing well.
So she doesn't get
to come home this weekend.
No fair!
lt can't be helped, Mei.
What if she came
and it made her worse?
It's not fair!
Mei, we just have to wait a little longer.
-No!
-You want her to die, Mei?
-Is that what you want?
-No!
You're such a baby! Just grow up!
(SNIFFLING)
Come on, Mel.
(CRYING)
She's so mean!
Come on, girls.
Let's put the laundry away.
Oh, don't be sad. Granny's here to help.
Don't worry. Your father is
going to stop by the hospital.
The doctors say your mom
just has a cold.
she should be home next Saturday.
This is just like last time.
They said Mom just had a little cold,
she'd be home in a few days.
Granny, what will we do if she dies?
Satsuki!
Maybe she's dead already.
(CRYING)
Now, don't say that, sweetheart.
How could she ever leave
such sweet girls like you?
Oh, don't cry.
Don't cry. It’s all right.
I'll stay here until your father
comes home. Okay? Okay?
Viel!
-Did she come back?
-No.
-She wasn't at the bus stop?
Let's think.
Do you know where else
she might have gone?
| yelled at her this morning.
She wanted Mom to come home.
Granny, | bet she went to see Mom
at the hospital!
You think she'd try
to walk to the hospital?
Why, that’s a three-hour walk
even for grown-ups.
I'll go look.
Kanta! Hurry! Run on home
and get your father!
Mei's disappeared, and we need
all the help we can get!
| shouldn't have yelled at her.
This is all my fault.
Viel!
Excuse me, mister! Hello!
-Yeah?
-I'm looking for my sister.
Did you happen to see
a little girl pass this way?
Let's see. Uh, a little girl?
Mmm, | don't think so.
| would have noticed.
'll try the other road.
MAN: Are you sure that this
is the way she came?
| don't Know.
Viel!
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(PANTING)
(CAR APPROACHING)
Stop! Please, stop!
-Oh! Are you crazy?
-I'm looking for my little sister.
Have you seen a girl walking this way?
Is she lost?
| think she's trying to walk to the
hospital. She's only four years old.
Oh. | didn't see her. Did you?
No. We just came from the hospital,
and there was no sign of
a little girl on the road.
Okay. Thanks.
-Wait. Where'd you say you're from?
-From Matsugo.
Matsugo! Ho!
A four-year-old couldn't walk this far.
(ENGINE STARTS)
MAN: Good luck. | hope you find her.
Satsuki!
Kanta!
-Find her?
-No.
-| guess you didn't, either.
-VUimm-mmm.
My dad's got a bunch of
people looking for her.
| could ride my bike
to the hospital for you.
-You should go back home.
-Check all around.
I'm sure that Mei got lost
on her way to the hospital.
A little while ago,
they found a sandal in the pond.
(GASPS)
They don't know for sure
it's Mel's sandal!
(BREATHING HARD)
Did you find her yet?
MAN: We'll check the irrigation ditch.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MAN: On the far end.
(CHANTING)
It's much deeper over there.
You should try there first!
MAN: Are there more poles?
(CHANTING)
(CLAMORING)
Huh?
WOMAN: It's Satsuki.
Here. Is this Mel's?
-It's not hers.
-On!
(SIGHS)
Onh...
Oh, thank goodness.
| was positively certain
that sandal belonged to Mei.
All right. Granny just got carried away.
Hey! It's not her sandal!
Everyone, | know you've spent
a lot of time here,
but we still need your help.
Satsuki!
Please.
(PANTING)
Let me in to see Totoro. Mel's lost.
Its getting dark,
and she's out there all alone.
Please let me in to see him.
It's an emergency.
(BREATHING HARD)
(THUDDING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Totoro!
Totoro, Mei's lost. | looked everywhere
for her, but | couldn't find her.
Please help me. | have to find her.
I'm sure she's scared
half to death by now.
| don't Know where else to turn.
(SOBBING)
(ROARING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(YOWLING)
No one else can see it, can they?
Huh?
FOREST-SWAMP
CEMETERY-SHRINE
MEI
-Mei.
-Viel!
(LAUGHING)
GRANNY: Mel!
(GASP)
Viel!
The trees are parting!
(BARKING)
(SIGHS)
SATSUKI: Mel!
Satsuki!
-Where are you?
-Viel!
-Me!!
-SatsukIi!
-Oh! You're okay.
-I'm sorry.
Were you trying to take your
corn to Mom at the hospital?
VMimm-hmm.
(YOWLING)
HOSPITAL
You're going to take us to the hospital?
Thank you!
(LAUGHING)
I'm sorry. | don't know why
the hospital sent a telegram.
It's just a cold.
| hope it didn't upset them too much.
I've caused enough grief already.
When they see you're all right,
they'll be fine.
Weill just wait a little
longer for a weekend together.
Don't worry. We've made it this far.
The girls act so strong, but | think
it's harder than they let on.
Especially Satsuki.
-She tries to act so adult.
-That's true.
| can't wait until | get better.
When | get home, I'm going
to spoil the girls rotten.
(LAUGHING)
(INAUDIBLE)
Look at Mom. She's laughing.
-Everything must be okay.
-Yeah.
I'm going to hurry up and get well!
That's the spirit. Huh?
Who left this?
(GASPS)
What is It?
| thought | saw Satsuki and Mei
smiling at us from up in that tree.
It sounds crazy, but maybe you did.
-Look at this.
-"For Mommy.”
Totoro, Totoro
Who leaves the seeds
For you to find
Follow them and you will see
A treasure there
Then plant the seeds
And help them grow
it may seem like a dream
Things are not what they seem
Now begins a new adventure
For you
And you'll be with Totoro
Totoro
Totoro, Totoro
Living in the forest trees
For such a very, very long time
There you'll be with Totoro, Totoro
Totoro, Totoro
You only see him
When you're very young
A magical adventure for you
it's magic for you
Rain tumbles down
The bus ts late
Suddenly, a furry white giant
ls by your side
Don't be afraid
Just open wide
Your umbrella for him
Watch him play in the rain
Now begins a new adventure
For you
And you'll be with Totoro
Totoro
Totoro, Totoro
And on a moonlit night
He plays a magic flute in the sky
There you'll be with Totoro
Totoro
Totoro, Totoro
You only see him
When you're very young
A magical adventure for you
it's magic for you