♪ Hey, let's go ♪
♪ I'm happy as can be ♪
♪ Let's go walking
You and me ♪
♪ Ready, set
Come on, let's go ♪
♪ Over the hill
Across the field ♪
♪ Through the tunnel we'll go ♪
♪ We'll run across the bridge ♪
♪ And down the bumpy gravel road ♪
♪ Right beneath the spider's web ♪
♪ Ready, set, let's go ♪
♪ Hey, let's go ♪
♪ I'm happy as can be ♪
♪ Let's go walking
You and me ♪
♪ Ready, set
Come on, let's go ♪
♪ The foxes and the badgers, too ♪
♪ All come out to play ♪
♪ They all want to explore ♪
♪ The deep and wonderful woods all day ♪
♪ Look at all my many friends ♪
♪ Ready, set, let's go ♪
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
- Hey Dad, want some caramel?
- Thanks. How you doing back there?
- Fine.
- Are you tired? Oop!
- Mmm-mmm.
- We're almost there.
Mei, hide.
Whoops. I thought
that was a policeman.
Hi!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hello there. Are your parents around?
We're your new neighbors.
Great. Thanks.
Hello! Hi, we're the Kusakabes!
We're moving in down the street.
Why don't you and your
family stop by sometime?
MAN: Okay, sure. Good to meet you.
Uh!
Hey, thanks a lot.
(WATER RUNNING)
This is it, girls.
(GRUNTING)
- Wait up!
- Here you go.
Mei, look at this bridge.
A bridge?
There's a fish! Oh, look!
There's another one!
So, how do you like the new place?
Dad, it's perfect.
Look at this. A tunnel of trees.
Oh, wow! Look!
(GIGGLING)
Dad, hurry!