Greetings to your highness
Ministers, why are you so mad?
Queen Mother, you first
Your highness, Dragon Fighter Lo Han
stole all the peaches...
...from my peach tree for the Cowherd's cows
Not only that, he also conspired
with Magpie to arrange...
...the Cowherd & Spinster Maid
rendezvous on the bridge
Damn it! They've bred lots of children now
Your highness, all along I've handled...
...lovers' relationships in the mortal world
Who would have thought he'd mess it up,
such that the emperor woos a whore,
and a princess elopes with a beggar
I reprimanded him gently,
he then stole my Heavenly Dog
and braised it with bamboo shoot
Now who might you be?
I'm God No. 2
Your highness, my eye
was also blinded by that bastard
This is just a substitute for Heavenly Dog
Law and order must be enforced
This Dragon Fighter is outrageous
I hope your highness permits me to beat him up
God of Fortune, stay calm
These are small matters.
He stole my Book of Destiny and messed it up
There hasn't been a death in 18 years
Those undertakers are out of work,
and there's a centuries- old man
Your highness, if you can't control him,
I'll bring up this up with the Ninth Heaven
and make a great fuss
Guards, summon Dragon Fighter to the palace
Yes
Hey... not so hard
I'm taking a nap, brother
Hey... everybody is here
What?
You're not Dragon Fighter,
you're Tiger Fighter
It's just the same
Dragon and Tiger are just the same
Tiger Fighter
Yes, your highness
It doesn't concern you. Why are you here?
I represent Dragon Fighter
to apologize to you all
You speak so loyally,
are you also a part of this?
Hey! What has it to do with me? I...
Do you think fairies can
get away with everything?
Ai! Aiya...
Tiger Fighter, you really are interfering,
yet you're a loyal friend.
I appreciate it
Thanks“.
Hey, as things stand,
just make an apology and leave
Do you think you can leave
just by saying sorry?
Who are you to interrupt our conversation?
God of Hearth, each year- end...
...you seek advantage in the mortal world,
and speak “I of those families who gave you less
- Poke him
Hey! You just did and still hurt,
don't poke again
You, a petty Lo Han,
poke your nose in everybody's business
Outrageous! You better compensate me
for the stolen peaches
Queen Mother, what's the big deal
to share some to others?
What?
You must get fed up with peaches
on your birthday each year
What?
Why not have a change and eat banana this year
Tell me frankly if you're still angry
Don't have your dog howl for you
Don't think just because he has spots
I can sock all the same I'm telling you
Who's next?
You will do
You Moon Match- maker,
you fool humans with several red strings
Take for instance the Butterfly Lovers,
why not tie them together?
Instead you brought them a tragic ending,
what have they done to you to deserve this?
You're old, you should retire...
...before you make a mess
Who knows you may make wacky matches...
...say like a man with a man,
a woman with a woman,
or even a man with a pig,
a roach with a cow
- Worst of all would be a lotus root with a rock
- Yes
Poke him
He's old, spare him
King of Hades, are you standing up
for him?
Poke him
Don't keep saying poke,
we should be reasonable
Your hand...
Why there's a woman in the mortal world
who bore 16 daughters...
...and was denied a boy? Why?
Consequently she jumped into sea to kill herself
Even in hell, he accused her of innocent death,
flung her into a frying pan
and fried her to a crisp
Do you think there's justice?
Lung... Dragon Fighter...
Fainting is no use.
People's fate is predestined
There's nothing wrong about it
So you shouldn't make trouble here
- We're only carrying out orders
- Your highness...
Carrying out orders?
Who set them?
Who dares to say it must be right?
A saying goes, 'There are other heavens'
Your highness, if your rules...
were known by Bodhisattva in the Ninth Heaven,
she'll think this is the joke of a moron
This is out of line
Your highness, fairies,
reckon Dragon Fighter Lo Han is just too rampant
I think, for everybody's advantage,
please allow me to fight him one on one
- Haha...
- Shut up! You better shut up
- I want to fight him one on one
- Don't kill him
I'll not show him mercy
I won't let you go
Scare me
Listen! Even if there's a loophole
in the laws of Heaven,
there must be one that convicts you
Escort them to the mortal world
and make them a pig and a dog
No transmigration for them in 10 lifetimes
Wait
What is it?
Is your word final?
Sure
I say you'll be a roach, let's go together
Escort them down
What?
Wait! Don't...
Greetings to Goddess
Heavenly Highness, each one of us
has been a fairy...
...for at least ten or thousands of years
Worldly affairs to us...
...are distant and trivial
The mess Dragon Fighter Lo Han has caused today
might be an opportunity
Why not use it to understand the mortal world?
To see if humans are still dumb and ignorant,
or they have progressed?
Goddess of Mercy speaks well
What a relief...
Goddess,
this kid offends a superior...
...under the pretext of fighting injustice
Stop speaking nonsense, King of Hades
Matters will be taken care of by the Goddess
Dragon Fighter,
what's your purpose of doing this?
I want these fairies
to get off their high horses,
and experience the mortal world
Humans only live for a few decades,
and they shouldn't be condemned for
a mistake or two
Because, according to my opinion,
regardless of how ignorant and dumb they are,
how evil and deserving of death,
they are after all... after all...
After what...
Go on
I mean... after all...
Subject to sympathy and love
Right, Dragon Fighter?
Yes, that's it
Let's begin with you,
going down to the mortal world
to experience it. Alright?
In fact that's what I intend to do
How are you going to prove it?
We've chosen 3 people
with predestined fates
One will be a beggar for 9 lives
One a prostitute for 9 lives,
and one a villain for 9 lives
Dragon Fighter,
if you can change their fates,
then you win
Since you despise gods, alright,
you'll go as a layman...
...and not allow to use magic
No magic?
That's right, Dragon Fighter
Use your sincerity to reform them
Okay, I'll not fail you
Wait for me
I'll give you 3 days
Thanks
But two and a half days will do
(Southern Heaven Gate)
You don't have to listen
but if you don't act accordingly,
don't expect to return to Heaven
Firstly, unless you have the official permit,
you can't enter Heaven
Secondly, you can't take magic powers with you
Ah Lung... Lung
Bon voyage
Same to you
Good brothers
What else do you have for me?
You're dead
You can't fight and can't use magic
You're bound to die in the mortal world
Thanks
- Don't mention it
- Dragon Fighter,
you won't die
When you re-incarnated in the mortal world,
a golden body has been left behind
Once you find and combine with it,
you can preserve your physical body,
and transmigrate between
the mortal and spiritual worlds
Besides, with it you can return to Heaven too
Splendid
This journey will be filled with danger
I'll present you with a Fan of Wishes...
...which can only be used 3 times daily
A crack will arise after each use
After 3 times, you'll have to wait till the next day
when the cracks vanish
A mere 3 times a day, that's pathetic
It's better than nothing
This fan can't change life and death
nor manipulate freewill
It's just a sleight of hand,
but laymen are often bewitched by what they see
So it would serve you well
Thank you, Goddess
Be careful and don't go astray
I understand
Hey... Goddess does care much about you
You'd be in deep shit without this fan
- Yes...
- Go down
Hey... Dragon Fighter
Hey, you kick him down on purpose
He hasn't got the fan yet
Heavenly Highness has set the deadline
Hey, what's Heavenly Highness ordered?
Hey, have you no sense of responsibility?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Change of shift
Good! Let's go down and
pass the fan to Dragon Fighter
Hey... you don't have approval,
and you have no magical powers in the mortal world
Laymen can't see you
That's why I want you to join me
Besides Heavenly Highness,
only you can come and go as you please
No, this is against heavenly rules
Forget about the rules.
Just fly once
We'll be back soon. Let's go
I'm not going
You've eaten the Heavenly Dog cooked
by Dragon Fighter that day
You've 2 bites of the Queen Mother's peaches too
That day while the Ninth Heaven Fairy's maids
were taking a bath,
you bastard...
...peeped
Hey... Stop it! Don't expose it
Creep!
You won't yield without threats
Come back early
You are sacred, aren't you?
It's not good to let others know
(Guo Ching Temple)
The eighteen Lo Hans are on both sides
Dragon and Tiger Fighters are on this side
To ask for a son,
you need to pray to Goddess of Mercy
Goddess of Mercy,
do bless me with a son
Hope Goddess'll show her power, otherwise...
...I'll be forty next year
I, Li Mau Cheun, have been honest
as an envoy all these years
With a clear conscience,
we don't need to make demands for it
Yes, just because you are honest,
Heaven will not destine us
to be without descendants
Master
The eighteen Lo Hans are on both sides
Dragon and Tiger Fighters on this side
To ask for a son...
- Master, you said just now
- Goodbye...
We haven't prayed to the gods yet
Pray...
Dragon Fighter Lo Han?
Master, we want...
I remember. You want a son, right?
No problem
Hasn't been a delivery even after
18 months' pregnancy
Don't worry, madam
Master, madam, look
- Where did you pluck it?
- Over there
- Master, why?
- Master, madam
Whenever a noble is born,
Ling Tze plant will appear
From the way things look,
our future young master
must be a dignitary
The house is now full of mushrooms
Madam, this child...
Tell him yourself, he's coming out
Congratulations, master!
Madam has given birth
A son or a daughter?
- A son! Congratulations, master
- Congratulations, master...
Hey... why have we landed here?
What's this place?
The main street
Main street? Damn you
I asked you to take me to
Dragon Fighter's birthplace
Just a few streets further
How could you landed on the wrong place
Who asked you to rock so much
Where's our son?
I don't know either
Aiya... damn... it's really painful... really...
Damn, everyone got diarrhea
after eating at that restaurant
- Damn it
Could we please use your manure pit?
- It's urgent
- Yes...
We only have two
Help yourself
I can't hold on
- So graceless
- They run so swiftly
I can hardly hold on
So this is the right place?
Dragon Fighter
Brother, I waited for ages, brother
Not my fault!
This bastard misled me
Never mind, take your fan, here...
- Quick and give them to me
- Hey... Lung...
What took you ages to buy 2 crickets?
- I hand- picked two that fight best
- Brag
Lung... Oh God! He can't see me
He is a layman now.
To contact him,
you must re-incarnate and become human
He's now grown; too late for
re-incarnation I guess
A day in Heaven is ten years in the mortal world
Don't worry! I'll blow you up
Blow me up?
But you'll lose your magic powers
after blowing up,
and you'll become a moron
when back to Heaven
Then it'll be no use contacting him
if I become a moron
When the moon is clouded,
the surveillance in Heaven is the weakest,
understand?
You could secretly steal back
your magical powers then
Why such a soft voice?
Nobody will hear us
Big tummy. This one will do
I'll take this one
Be nimble
I'm going to re-incarnate
So comfortable. Your turn
Coming
Hey... don't go away
Don't let go even a granny
Make my tummy so big
It's tough! Hey... your tummy?
Shit! I've forgotten the fan
Fix it
Coming...
So she's giving birth
Let's get prepared and help them
Darling, a son or a daughter?
- It's a fan
- What?
Ah
- Delivered... I've delivered
You've delivered... Come...
Put this belly-band on. My son Sau Yun...
...wore it when he was a child
It would just fit him now
Blow you up now
What?
- One more time
- What
What?
Done
Demon, run quickly...
Is this some demon or what?
Nonsense! He's just playing magic tricks
Do you know how to perform magic?
Master, how about report it to the magistracy?
What for? I'm a magistrate
Let him stay. Look how cute he is
He should be a nice baby to take care of
They may return to take the kid back some day
Kid?
Beat...
Who are you? Speak up
You must know some magic
C'mon, teach me
- Milk...
- Stop playing dumb
Go and get milk from that lady.
Go over
Let's see how long you can pretend
Milk... no... no milk
He's really a retarded. He's not pretending
You two conspired to make fun of my wife?
Satisfied yet?
Go to hell
- Go on, run
- Brother...
Chop you up
Master, your pay might not be adequate
to sustain him
I'll need to get a part- time job
There's an orphanage near our home
I, Li Mau Cheun, won't do such thing
He's much wiser now,
though a big eater
I've also taught him a lot
He'll soon be able to support himself
Look
Greet me
Abalone
Abalone comes in pieces. Call me brother
Greet her
Little brother
Nonsense! Brother comes in strips
Try again
He's too small to remember
Bakbak (uncle)
Now he said it right
Clean white white
It's affinity. Let's just do our best
Just play with him for a little while
I need to revise some documents
I must rush my embroidery as well
Tiger Fighter Lo Han transfigures
Ah Lung... where're you?
Brother, we're running out of time
Listen, you're a fairy
You don't know...
...because your head's cover is not
yet opened
Remember, hold out your head when it thunders
Let the thunder split up the cover,
then you'll revive your memory
Who's making all that noise there?
Can't even pee in all that chaos
Count the bugs
The bugs fly
Hurray...
So noisy? Must have wet your pants,
let me see
Fan...
- Keep toying with that lousy fan, really...
- Fan...
He's hopeless, poor thing
Fan...
Not this one
Doctor, please see
- if he can be treated?
- Milk...
- No
I see,
- just asking, thanks
- Milk...
Master
Wong Dai Fu's having trouble at home,
they're moving him over here
Really? Go quickly then
- Doctor, also...
- Milk...
You bitch! Don't point at me
Holy cow!
- Streaking in the street
- So what?
Never seen before?
Move the whole bed out
A stroke
- See when it'll be your turn
- What?
- Yes, I cursed you. Crazy
- Just say so
So what
Have you no shame, bitch?
Doing such an immoral thing in broad daylight
How shameful
Hey, will get double pay in daylight,
don't you know?
Crazy! Consider yourselves lucky
to watch this for free
Take a rest
Hey, why are we stopping? Hey, I'm in a hurry
Luckily it wasn't me,
- or I'll suffer
- That guy is so unlucky
Do you like it? Come and have a look
Who did it?
I did
Lady, be a bit more decent
I don't have decent
I only have a navel.
Come and visit us at Yi Heung Brothel
Shameless, you'll be struck by thunder
Hey guys, come and visit me
when you have time
What I just said came true! A real thunder
Heaven has eyes. Strike her
Missed by a mile. Over there
Aim better. Try again
- Are you ok...
- Alright...
Are you alright...
Dragon Fighter has re-incarnated
in the mortal world to save people
Milk...
Tiger Fighter
- Milk
- Take her to dip in a pig cage
You became this just for helping me
You're such a loyal friend
Black
- Don't...
- Streaking in the street
is so immoral
- A prostitute for 9 lives?
- Scum! Really cheap
- Take her to dip in a pig cage
- Don't
You're all women, why fight against each other?
She's a whore
A whore...
...could be patriotic
Right
Thanks
I'll come back to you very soon
Hey, what's your name?
A name is just a label so makes no difference
Up to you
Big brother
She's calling you. Let's go
Milk
Get going
- Go now
- Milk
(Guo Ching Temple)
Milk...
It's here
Brother, I waited for you for a long time
Who are you, sir?
God of Earth
I don't blame you. Your Yun San (spirit)
has not returned
Don't be frightened! You'll be fine
once you get back your golden body
Also, your golden body...
...is sought by both bureaucracy
and the underworld
The most people came last month
Are you God of Earth or local mob?
The golden body is here
Totally understand! The golden body is me
and I am the golden body
No point telling me, tell them instead
Yes
Your heads have been exchanged
Really?
Change back first
What is it?
A wooden fish
Fish
Is this possible?
Please spare some time and listen to me
I don't know you
Thirteenth life cycles ago,
I was a monk in this temple
Then by the eighth life cycles,
I became an abbot
I was the golden body right there
The Sing Ging Abbot before passed away
I then ascended Heaven and became a fairy
Follow me
Guess what happened afterwards?
The fairy became Dragon Fighter Lo Han
That's me
Follow me
I came down on a mission
As regards what the mission is,
you need not know
You are at best a common person
However, considering the length of your service,
you've accumulated some worthiness
so I'll give you some face...
...and address you as master
in front of your pupils
Should give you due respect
Go get me some clothes to change
Master, he is mad
So am
I admire him on sight.
- Bring me the clothes
- Yes
You're lovely
You've eaten all of it so quickly?
There's a bigger one outside
This is made of steel and can't be eaten
Eat the drum behind
I beg you not to bite, please
Master
Give me a priest name as in the
normal procedure
You are so mad, I'll call you Mad Monk
Very good
Help! Don't chase me...
A beggar for 9 lives?
Don't
Horrible! Really horrible
What? Yun Ba Tin
Hide quickly
Hey, Yun is here!
Hide in my home, quick
Hey, God of Earth
A villain of 9 lives?
Save my time
Help
I told you not to let me see you
A mere sight of you makes me so mad
I don't want you to see me either. Keep away
I wanted to avoid you, but couldn't
You can hit my head,
not the back
Run? I'll burn down the temple,
see if you can get away
I'll burn you stinky monk too
I want to burn you, how dare you
blow out my fire?
You...
Does it hurt?
Now you know the agony of being bullied
Lay down the sword and be 3 Buddha
Don't be mad! Give you a kiss
Take my advice and be a new person
Good boy
Impossible...
Think over indoors.
I'll come to you soon
Don't be a beggar anymore. Go home with me
What a horrible monster
What are you afraid of?
No, I'm not going
Get going
Brother. Milk... Brother. Milk.
- Son, what happened to you?
- Bakbak
I changed my hairstyle. Not bad, right?
What happened to the house?
(Li Sau Yun, I vow to kill your whole family)
(Signed by Yun Ba Tin)
Sau Yun, why mess with a character
like Yun Ba Tin?
Bakbak
Clean white white
Li Sau Yun, I vow to kill your whole family
Signed by Yun Ba Tin
Master..., they killed all the poultries,
even rats and roaches
Also include a pregnant roach, so cruel
Luckily you went to the temple
with master and madam
Found out my background so soon. Great!
Unfortunately I'm not Li Sau Yun anymore
His calligraphy is good,
couldn't tell from appearance
He even put down the date,
such an organized person
Son, look at the mess here,
yet you're still concerned with such matters
Master...
Your dad won't make it
Natural death is his good fortune. Let me see,
he'll be an emperor in his next life.
Good for him
Sau Yun..., are you crazy?
Bingo, my new name is Mad Monk
Heaven, what has our family done wrong?
Yes, if you've done nothing wrong,
you should die with him
Madam...
Give her some musk to smell, hurry
Don't move
Master and madam are fine, you shouldn't fiddle
They're destined to become butterfly lover,
and they always die together
They'll continue their romance in the next life
How admirable
Young master, what should we do then?
It's an auspicious affair,
get a chicken to celebrate
And you, get an undertaker to give them a lift
Go... Hurry...
Let's go quickly
- You can't go yet
- What?
But you can sleep for a while
Aiya...
Fan...
Good duckling... You two've lots of kids,
why not give me one to fill my stomach
If you don't shake your head
when I count to 3,
that means you consent
1,2,3
- Aiya
- Outrageous
You again?
Sunk deep to a duck thief?
You keep away! Keep away...
I got the couple's consent
Did you ask?
Did he ask you?
No...
What? Duck can speak too?
What more do you have to say?
Stop pulling me...
His mother must've seduced a parrot
that's why he could speak
His mother has seduced a parrot?
That's totally up to his mother
Who asked you to meddle in it? I tell you,
we must've self-respect as a human
If you want to eat them,
you must get their consent first
Who would consent to being eaten?
Damn
I want to eat you now
Whoever is willing can come with me
80 great
Worth to greet me as Master?
Master, what can I do for you? Just let me know
It's late, you should sleep
Master, I am like a pig. I only sleep in daylight
Dai Jung, your dad is here for you
You mom finds you.
My dad died a long time ago
Have a look
Dad, how are you?
Won't you listen to dad?
Yes
Then I advise you in dad's name,
never go begging again with your bowl
Dad, I've long yearned for this
I want to get a bigger bowl to beg
Outrageous
Just now my dad came to see me
Enough, go in and take a rest
May throw out by the waiter
Lots of gold
Carry them
Then you won't be thrown out
Sir, this way please
Get out, you stinking monk
Have a seat. I'll get some nice tea for you
What would you like to eat? Tell them
I want chicken butts
Damn your ass!
You have money now,
you should order sharks' fins
to rinse your mouth
Yes, right
Order then
Hey, I dare not. You order for me
You lack confidence even in this,
how are you going to be successful?
Summon your courage
Give me 2 days to consider
Making fun of me? Speak
I want...
Louder, I want everyone to hear it
Give me a bowl of butts...
Not butts, sharks' fins
Don't force me...
Don't be silly! Why would I do that?
Just say it and everything will be alright
Do as I say
But I really want to eat chicken butts
Damn it! Fought back!
I insist you to say...
...give me a bowl of sharks' fins
to rinse my mouth. Say it
Give me a bowl of sharks' fins
to rinse my mouth...
You bastard
- Yummy
- Outrageous
Dai Jung, I won't talk any more nonsense
Look
This is my real self, Dragon Fighter Lo Han
Ghost
Stop screaming! A ghost is not like this
It's like this
Have you really passed out?
Who's hitting my mouth?
Disguised yourself in white top,
and hanged two sausages on your mouth
just to scare a beggar?
You're a beast!
Go to hell...
- Stop it
- Don't stop me
Let's go
- Go to hell
- Don't be impetuous
- Let's go
- Don't be mad
- For such nuts, you've to beat him to dead
- Let's go
People nowadays aren't frightened of ghosts
Dai Jung
Don't you understand now?
Are you really a fairy?
100%
If you have any wishes, just let me know,
I can fulfill for you. Tell me
I want you to take me to Heaven
What a fantastic wish
I don't want to beg over here...
any more
At last I see you have pride
I want to be...
...a God of Beggar
Outrageous...
There'll be morning orisons tomorrow,
let's rest early
Master, what to do with the beggar outside?
Buddha is merciful and the temple is
to serve people
Let him stay outside for one night
Milk...
Hurry! Take them all inside
Hey, you get the stuff
Milk... Fish... Ya... Fish...
Walk faster
Brother... Milk...
Bad boy, bearing a piece of BBQ pork
is better than having you
BBQ pork?
No...
BBQ pork...
I'm stunk! Don't eat me
Tiger Fighter Lo Han transfigures
Insulting me?
You scared the piss out of me
Unicorn, why look so miserable?
I dressed up to hide my identity,
so I can come down to inform you
What's up?
Heaven knew you've come down to
the mortal world,
so they sent down God of Plague
to spread disease everywhere
You'll bear the consequence of
the casualties caused
For the evil done, by that time,
you may be demoted 3 grades
Wake up again, Tiger Fighter
Dragon Fighter, this is not my fault
Though it might not be,
you know how it's like with the fools up there
It matters little if one is downgraded,
but to harm so many lives,
it's really a big trouble
That's right...
What rule is that?
Tell me, who ordered to spread the plague?
A high directive
Damn it
Hey, which department?
Tell us,
we promise not to accuse you
The Recreation Department
What? They are responsible for travels though
They are linked to the Accounts Department
- The Accounts Department pays salaries only
- Yes
That's right
The trouble is Accounts and
Advertising Department are brothers,
then Publicity Department...
- Ignore him
and Welfare Department...
Hey, ah Lung,
- I'm going up now
- ...have to show respect to each other
- Take care
- Also Publishing Department...
claimed that we're brothers...
Apologize to see if there's any remedy
- Be careful
- Health Department... They...
- Let's go! Genital
In short they screw up together...
This is most disastrous... do you agree?
Over a hundred died in one night
An evil spirit must be behind this
Damn beggar,
why not die yet for having
so many sores
- Wow
- What?
Yours is worse
Shit...
Sores... I've sores...
I've big sores... I'm finished...
Don't worry, more sores still won't kill you
Dragon Fighter...
...the Supreme of Monkey King is here
I know there's a plague here,
so I negotiated with Heavenly Emperor
He told you to raise 1000 taels.
I'll perform a ceremony...
...to avert the disaster
Doing this ceremony
may shorten 10 years of my life
Spreading misleading fallacies,
you're disturbing my sleep
Why you...
What... I do this for saving people's lives
I don't mind even if my life is
shortened for ten years
Still talking?
It's a big sacrifice, you know?
How big is the sacrifice?
There's one more mole...
Yes... Yes what?
Again! Let me stick your ass to your mouth
- Three times a day,
- There's one way
- lucky you
- to save your life,
get someone to sacrifice to gods
Who...
One to whom life means nothing
Where to find...
You can find many at Yi Heung Brothel
Yes...
Let's go...
Boss
- Those lousy men come so early?
- Yes...
- What if they won't agree?
- Go in...
This concerns the safety of the whole city,
they have no choice
Let's go in together. Chief, you go first
- What happened?
- Go...
Freeze! What's the matter?
Master Tin, you know, the plague
has killed a lot of people
What has it to do with my Yi Heung Brothel?
They want to get some girls as sacrifice
Why don't you send your mother?
That's right
You told me you hated your wife last night
Why don't you send her?
Master Tin, I know it's a hard decision for you
Why? They are all mine
Their lives are in my hands
Right?
That's right...
Take those ones who nobody wants
I can save some cost
No need for so many, one is more than enough
- Come and form a circle...
- So bad...
- Hurry... Quick! Come...
- Outrageous...
Hunchback, lie down
Whoever his toe points to, will be the one
- Turn...
- So scary...
You're cheating
Not me...
Take her away
Not me! You've seen it
- Get going
- Take her away
Remember what you said to me yesterday?
I said you charged a high price. Move
Cut the crap, take her away
You dare create trouble here?
No! No... Not me...
Hey, how should the sacrifice be offered?
Braise
- It'll take a long time then
- Not me...
Leave the left leg for me
I'll take a rest
Clean her up and get changed. Go
No...
She's so beautiful.
What a waste to burn her?
Find a way to save her
To help only the pretty one?
If so, I won't save you then
Your... your fan has to wait until dawn
for its power to return?
Rather than wait until dawn,
better off to wait till my powers are gone
Go
You'll understand once I explain to you
No need. I don't understand anyway
Just do as I say
The auspicious time has come
Wait! How you know that
burning her will stop the plague?
- Heavenly Highness told me in a dream
- Oh...
Queen Mother told me to burn...
- ...your mother in a dream
- It can't be...
And if I scold you three times,
the two moles on your face will disappear
You are crazy, go away
It's time, scold him
I dare not
Bastard, bastard, bastard
It really works...
Look at his face, more divine than god
Everyone, he has made an agreement
with Queen Mother,
there'll be no more plague
Release her now
What if there'll be plague again
after she is released?
Right...
What to do? Tell me...
None of my business! Don't! I don't know
Can't release her
However, If the plague still persists
after she's burnt to death
I'll burn you all
Hear that? Release her now
The fire is so fierce. How to release?
Bring some water to put it out
The well nearby is blocked.
Where can we find water?
Any kind of water will do
Got it
You're so bold, you don't even flinch
It's just saliva, no need to be scared
Thank you
My pleasure
I...
Take a rest
Don't go
Don't worry, they won't burn you again
Those lousy men were nice to me when in bed
Why did they want to burn me to death?
It's simple
Those men who come to you,
treat you like a shit bowl
They feel comfortable when sitting on it,
but they're not emotionally tied to it
What do you mean?
That is... to say never be a shit bowl anymore
Get it?
Yes
What are you doing?
I want to repay you
Don't! Your whorish nature is incorrigible
It's free
Big brother, you don't charge,
but I do
Worse than a shit bowl
What else can you do
besides lying down for money?
You can do it upside down? No way...
I don't mean that
What I mean is can you find another job...
...like selling bean curd?
Should I put the stall at the door
or beside the bed?
Master... I got half piece of preserved bean curd
Smells good, any for me?
Keep the bean curd for yourself
Oh no, finish the sauce too
It's a foreign dog, not much taste
There's one left. Try and I'll know
This dog has bitten two people to death before
Eating it means I'm honoring its dead spirit
You're not qualified yet to eat it
Not really, Master.
Your pupil is very hungry
Be kind enough to leave me at least
a piece of bone
Please... be kind... please...
Go away
Be kind! Hey! Why not? Hey
Don't play! I know you haven't swallowed it
You bastard,
how come you ain't that persist
apart from begging?
Help... C'mon...
I need to get the rack.
Remember to get back your underpants
Get it
Why took so long? It's my turn
Come
Yuk
It's you
You aren't listening to me
and get even worse now
You have no self- respect at all
I've done as you told me
You are simply hawking yourself in the street
How dare you say you're doing as I said
Wrong! I'm selling bean curd...
Really?
Hurry up, are you doing business or not?
We agreed to do once for buying
a bowl of bean curd
No? Give me back the money...
No... I'll do it... Coming...
Thanks for your advice
My business is good now
She's willing to change, just in the wrong way
Dai Jung, follow me
Hey... help... Please do me a favor
Don't mention
my nick name here. Thanks
What did I call you?
Beggar Dai Jung
Is your name Beggar Dai Jung?
Your name is Chow Yat Cheung... Go to hell...
Don't beat me...
If you want to beat me, let's go to
the back alley
Beat freely. Siu Yuk will see us here
I'll show you the way
So your pride will only appear
in the presence of Siu Yuk
I Got it
Got it
Who says they have no remedy?
They all have remedy
Listen, fairies above, I'll surely win
I won't marry any man except him in this world
You're naughty, you peeping- tom
Bad boy, I forbid you to say this
This is the style
A decent girl should be like this
Not hurt? I know it's a dream
Or else this couldn't have happened
You can
What's it? So ugly...
Look
So beautiful...
Yuk, since a caterpillar can become a butterfly,
a chicken... can also become a phoenix
I want to be a phoenix, can I?
A phoenix?
Lord, you have good foresight
That monk has done all that you anticipated
If you need anything, just tell me
(Yi Heung Brothel)
Call a whore? Maybe another day
I have no time
I can push you, but you push me back...
come here
Don't hit me
You've gone to the toilet,
and you don't need a bath
What else do you need to do?
But calling a whore... I don't know how
Siu Yuk is waiting for her lover upstairs
Who is it?
His name is... Chow Yat Cheung
Me?
A good- looking and presentable man
Yeah”.
Dai Jung, you must remember
to leave on the 1st watch
Otherwise, gold will turn back to dog shit,
and the sores will emerge again
It'd be bad to scare people away
Do you have any familiar lady in mind?
Siu Yuk
She is having her period
Her period has just ended
She's only a temporary lodger here,
not taking any client
Never mind,
she sometimes makes guest appearances
Sir, follow me
Siu Yuk
Call me Phoenix
Sir, how about I order the kitchen to cook
some dishes for you?
What would you like?
A plate of chicken butts would be nice
Anything wrong?
You're an epicure
What do you do?
- I'm a beggar
- What?
So it's you
Do you mind?
Why would I?
When I see you it's like seeing that guy
Where's that guy?
That guy asked me to come
Why he asked you to come?
That guy asks me here to...
...buy bean curd
You're so naughty
Good! I'll fix you too
With the possession of Shaolin Patriarch Dhama,
in a lamp's time,
there's no reason I can't fix you
Halt
Sock him
Yes
What happened... Look...what happened?
Really powerful
Patriarch Dhama?
Are you scared?
You are deep in sin
Consider this as doing charity,
I'll take you back to be a monk
Damn you
I'll beat you till you come with me
Joking... A rattan cane
Look down on me?
Scared now?
I'm tired
Go...
See where you can run to?
Damn it! Never listen
- Reconciled to defeat yet?
- Reconciled to the hell of you
So, that guy is a fairy?
I thought you knew
Sorry for troubling you
Never mind. I enjoy it...
How many?
For a situation like this, two will suffice
Remember to tell that guy I'll sell soy milk
as well tomorrow
Really?
Do you think he'll like it salty or sweet?
Salty
Best to add some preserved savory vegetables
Even better with sesame seeds
Lo Han soy milk
He likes dog meat
Dog meat Lo Han soy milk
Yeah”.
Siu Yuk's unbeatable soy milk
I've come for a whore
As matters stand, I have to fight
violence with violence
Iron Head
Reconciled to defeat now?
I only want you to be a monk, not go to hell
Be good and come with me now
You're simply incorrigible
Ok... forget about being a monk
Just refrain from killing people, okay?
Damn! Are you a human being or a beast?
Do you like me?
I do
But, make it next life
This life, I've to marry that guy
You're right. I found my self-respect
after knowing him too
OK, you're on the upside tonight
Let's compromise! If you back off
and leave Siu Yuk alone tonight,
we'll settle our score later
If I hadn't changed to Patriarch Dhama,
I'd have been killed by you
You bastard
Can't bear with it anymore
Buddha is merciful! Good luck
Shit! Dai Jung, it's time
ls someone selling rice dumplings?
That stand's there every day.
- Never mind it
- Ok
Magic is over! Let's go
Shit! Time is up
Aiya... I changed back to a beggar
Why shout? You are in fact a beggar
I have to go
Hey, are we good friends?
Why haven't you come down yet... you really...
Hey man
Have you seen someone with a big beard?
Yes, he seems over there in the toilet
After him
Halt
Man, you look familiar
Heroes, you're mistaken
Outrageous!
I warned you not to let me see you
Don't...
Sponge as well?
No, I didn't
I have money
Shit! The gold changed...
Don't beat him! He's not a sponger
He's my boyfriend
That cheap? You even want one with sores?
Look
Big brother, I told you it wasn't me
You still deny it?
Don't be mad! Maybe it's just likeness
You're pretending
Do I look like that moustached Singh?
Maybe you shaved it off?
Who could do it so quickly?
You're siding with a stranger
I talk sense
Go to hell
See! You've hurt someone
What? Getting mad?
What? Should I stand here and let you hit me?
What? You dare disobey what the big brother
tells you to do?
What? A big one bullies a small one?
- I've endured for a long time.
- Go to hell
Don't beat my big brother! Go away
Damn it! Again! Don't... Hey...
Don't
Help
Don't, master
Let her go please, master
Siu Yuk...
Help
Big head
Dai Jung
Why didn't you knock?
Sorry, I got the wrong place
Close the door
Have a banana
Sorry...
Master...
What's taken you so long? Wanna die?
Things changed back to original! Let's go
Master, I can't move
What? Yun Ba Tin
Go to hell, Beggar Dai Jung
Don't call me Dai Jung
Call me Chow Yat Cheung
Dai Jung
You've made us suffer a lot
Dai Jung... you can't die!
You must hang on
Dai Jung... you can't die! Dai Jung
You've no more magical powers?
Tomorrow, I'll show you tomorrow
Kill you, son of the bitch
- Turn his face over
- Turn his face
Look
Open his eyes
Master Tin said to let you go,
but be careful in future
What a show it was just now
You didn't even blink
Frankly... it was fascinating
Yes
You'll surely die this time
God of Earth
God of Earth, where are you? Come out quickly
Hey... I'm here. Why shouting so loud?
How can I save Dai Jung?
A man's fate is pre- determined
One can't change Heaven's rules
But he has suffered
an innocent death because of me
I've to bring him back no matter what
Help me to think some ways
An innocent death means going to hell
King of Hades is strict
But...
Speak up
Before entering the City of Innocent Deaths,
There's an area governed by
evil god Hak Lo Sat
He admits stray spirits
Anyone in his hands never gets reincarnated
But you may talk it over with him
Bring me down to him quickly
Hey... I'm only a junior god and thus
not eligible to go down
Unlike you, you've a golden body for protection
which makes you invulnerable
I'll go and get back the golden body now
Hey... don't make fun of the golden body
I must do what's necessary
What're you doing? Let go
Master said this golden body cannot
leave the temple
What if it does?
- I don't know
- Then that means it's okay
Let me borrow it, I'll pay you lots of interest
- No
- For just one night
- One hour
- No
- Ok, then a cross
What cross?
Hey man, halt
Stand still
What's the matter?
Let him go
Are you the Buddha?
No
Damn
Man, you're so rude. Let me tell you
I'm friends with the Buddha
I'll retrieve this person's spirit
on his behalf,
understand?
How dare you? Stop
Stop
Rubbish! Ask Sakyamuni to see me
Don't go...
In fact, I'm not on good terms with Buddha
I didn't know you and he had a grudge
I'll take you for big brother
Since you've so many men under you,
having one more doesn't make a difference
This one... treat this as a gift to me
What's in it for me?
What's in it?
How about... I'll pedicure for you,
the nails are so long,
okay?
Damn! Unless you exchange it
with your golden body
Golden body? I can't give it to you
Besides, you've no use for it
Just as a display
Bastard, you're going too far
Okay, exchange
Dai Jung, I must bring you back by any means
Don't worry
Put down your golden body
You promised to exchange with me
Why have you taken his spirit?
I'm a baddie
Stinking monk, why appeared so sudden
Damn, I'm back
If you don't like it, you can go back down
How could I go down without the golden body?
What a pity!
He's even cheated me out of my golden body
Dai Jung...
Lord, I'll do as you instruct me
and help accomplish your mission
Hey... don't be like that?
Hey... brothers...
Won't give me a face?
I'm in charge here
I told you not to do this
What's the matter?
As you have consorted with evil spirits,
the fairies inside said...
...they don't want to be with you
They've all gone
These just returned to get their luggage
Sorry, for my life-long emoluments,
I have to follow them... goodbye
What's happening? Where's the stuff?
Mad Monk, where's the golden body?
Oh no! You've caused a big trouble
On no! Even God of Earth is gone.
We're in deep shit now
Oh no...
Master, where are you going?
Mad Monk, as I told you,
the golden body cannot leave the temple
Now you've caused anger among men and gods
how can I bear this responsibility?
Master, leave quickly
A thunder may split the temple
- You blame me too?
- Let's go... even the Goddess are down.
Go...
Back to original form
You really leave me no way out?
Siu Yuk, I heard you were messed up
by Master Tin last night
Is that true?
Ignoring us! What's so special?
You're rotten. We'll look for Siu Hung
Wait
What's the matter, Miss Siu Yuk?
If I don't charge you money, would you take me?
Yes, do it now
Me too
Hey... She asked me first
- Me first...
Who says it's your turn?
Tell me, what will make you happy?
Marrying you
You're naughty
If I marry you, will you stop being a whore?
Yes
Really?
We'll marry then
I am Dragon Fighter Lo Han,
priest name Mad Monk
I'll take Bak Siu Yuk as my wife today
Whatever comes in this life
or came in the past life,
I'll not regret it
Even I've been pillowed
and kissed by thousands of people,
you still...
Never mind, I can take it
Yeah”.
You really love me?
I love you very much
How deep is your love?
As deep as I love Beggar Dai Jung
Beggar Dai Jung?
Who do you love more?
The same
Scare me! I thought you loved him more
No... the same
Yeah”.
Why are you not happy?
No... Yeah...
Great... Let's worship the ancestors
Good--- go-.-.
After that we'll consummate our marriage...
- We must be quick...
- ...then we'll have kids
I'm afraid there's not enough time
Why?
If we fairies join earthlings in marriage,
Heavens will punish me
I'll gradually turn into a log
Don't say that...
Your foot
It's changing
Bloody punk, are you making fun of me?
Hey... let's not talk about this now
Let's carry on with the worship
Why should I marry a piece of wood?
You take me for a fool?
It's alright... As long as you don't back out
on your promise
Marry yourself
I vowed
It's your vow
I don't care if you marry me or not
You promised you won't be a whore anymore
That's none of your business now
Bloody punk... are you playing a joke on me?
Yes, I am
Do you think fairy can get away
with everything?
You've no feelings for me
You thought I don't know?
I know everything
A total loss this time
I've nothing now. Really, nothing at all
Since you don't love me,
I don't want love ever again in this life
Don't...
I don't want love again in this life
Help...
Killing you will just make enough blood
from 77491 people
Lord, I'll immerse with the golden
body of Mad Monk
Even if he find here, his kung fu would be gone
Here at last? But it's no use anymore
You're like a dead dog
Gods appear
Lo Han on top
Heaven Soldiers reinforce
Get that bastard for me
Villain of 9 lives, let's see which of us is tougher?
You can't kill me
Really?
See which of us is tougher...
I'll kill you...
Dragon Fighter, we came to terms with Heaven
If you admit losing and downgrade three levels,
you can be a fairy again
Time is running out, go back quickly
Let me get rid of him first
Hurry
Bastard, had I killed you
many lives would have been spared
The skin of Hak Lo Sat?
Lord has given me an immortal heart
you guys can't kill me
Look clearly at your immortal heart
What? A stone? How can this be?
My lord...
This is a fatal heart
He just wants your dedication to him
Lord... you fool me...
So what?
You're such an ideal fool to be cheated
What treachery has Hak Lo Sat planned, speak
You fool me...
Speak... I'll chop you
Don't... Ok! I'll speak
To stop Hak Lo Sat
from going to the mortal world,
Buddha placed his scepter
under the Goddess statue in Guo Ching Temple
To cheat you out of your golden body
such that all the fairies fled
This is all part of his treachery...
...to rid the temple of heavenly protection
Then at the time when the moon is
in eclipse tonight,
he plans to get back the scepter
That will cost many lives...
Dragon Fighter, we're running out of time
If we don't go up now,
we've to stay on earth to sell banana
Go
It's hurt! Give me back my heart
I don't want to die
You don't want to die?
Beggar Dai Jung and the other lives here,
do they want to die either?
You're already lifeless.
Even you take back this lousy piece of stone
you can only be the puppet of Hak Lo Sat,
and continue killing innocent folk.
Is that what you want?
If so, get it back! Take...
Don't let me be a man in a next life then...
Fixed! Let's go
Dragon Fighter, go
Not yet
Are you crazy?
Go now or never
Hak Lo Sat's the ringleader.
I must finish him off
You go up first
Dragon Fighter...
Hey... can't wait anymore
Really here
I'll now endow you with spiritual powers
from my thirteen life cycles' training
Everything depends on you today, understand?
Come on
Good
Wow
Damn
- Mad Monk...
- Master...
- Master
We meet again, let's get out of here quickly
Master, why are you here?
At such a critical moment,
I shouldn't have left you on your own
Why care to come back for me
if you know the danger?
Because you're the one person I admire most
Come again! Let's go quickly
Master, there's not much left of my golden body
I must use the last resort
I'll fight the remainder into his body
to overpower him
You'll perish too
when your golden body is used up
No time to be bothered with that
How are you going to do it?
Just help me to open his mouth
That simple?
Can you?
Of course not
Master... Are you alright, master?
My bowl
Where's the golden powder?
Master, didn't you...
Yes, I swallowed it all
At such a critical moment, you...
I didn't want to either.
My stomach feels strange now
Master, think of a quick way
to defecate the golden powder
But I'm always constipated
I remember now
I've still got two golden teeth
You stole them?
I have no teeth so I just borrowed them
I can't hang on any longer...
please do my last favor
- What?
- Find a way to open his mouth
I decide to use all my magic to overpower you
I feel very scared
Scared?
Kneel and bow three times
and I'll spare you
Haha“.
What a funny laugh
Mad Monk...
Amida Buddha...
See, I said he's bound to lose
- I also said he'll lose
- Loss for sure,
no argument...
Lose? Why would you think that?
Just like Beggar Dai Jung,
he could have twenty more years
to beg for his living
Now he's not only dead, he died as a beggar
Also, that whore was disfigured
What a pity
The case of Yun Ba Tin is worse still
Tens of lives were lost before he died
So... it's so... so...
How should I say it?
What a failure
Yes, failure
Not only a failure.
If let me beat him
in a duel on that day,
things wouldn't have been such a mess
Nonsense”.
Stop mentioning the duel
No doubt that Beggar Dai Jung
suffered an innocent death
But before he died, he knew his name is
Chow Yat Cheung
It means he got back his pride
- Look...
- Something to watch...
- He doesn't have to be a beggar this life
- Right...
Though Siu Yuk was defaced,
she's no longer a whore
She's really selling bean curd now
As for the villain Yun Ba Tin
We all know that when he died
he said he didn't want to be
a human being anymore
He's now re-incarnated
In this life he's a pig, he's got a bright future
Let us think did Dragon Fighter win or lose?
Well...
No matter what, Dragon Fighter Lo Han
no longer exists
You've dropped something
Lucky I pick up for you
But now we have a senior Dragon Fighter
Why are you here?
- He'll be a senior
- Could he be a senior?
Right
A promotion for a few grades only
The coronation ceremony begins
Congratulations
Thank you
What's your goal being made
a senior Dragon Fighter today?
I want to be an emissary of peace and be
Heavens' envoy to spread love throughout the world
And let them know that with love,
anywhere is a paradise.